<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Potentially controversial on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/category/potentially-controversial/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Potentially controversial on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/category/potentially-controversial/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Holy bubbles</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/04/15/its-too-serious-to-be-funny/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/04/15/its-too-serious-to-be-funny/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been searching for a preschool for Laurelin for a couple of mornings a week. I think it’ll be good for her, and it will help the two older girls and me get a bit more done in school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I quit Facebook (for now)</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/10/why-i-quit-facebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/10/why-i-quit-facebook/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: this is simply my reasoning for giving up Facebook for the foreseeable future. I’m not saying any of this to make you feel like you should quit Facebook too.
&amp;nbsp;
I thought I’d give a bit of an explanation to those who might be interested on why I deactivated my Facebook account 3 months ago (since a few people have asked).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hacker Christianity</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/12/22/hacker-christianity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/12/22/hacker-christianity/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This is a written version of a pre-Christmas talk I gave at work recently, about the intersection between Christianity and hacker culture. There’s also a video available here — the sound quality’s not brilliant, but feel free to watch it there!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips for new New Yorkers</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/29/tips-for-new-new-yorkers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/29/tips-for-new-new-yorkers/</guid>
      <description>It takes a lot of adjusting to live in the greatest city in the world, and there are some protocols that you should follow if you want to survive in this city. You might be a kind, generous and gentle person in the privacy of your own home, but follow these tips for how to act in public, and within a couple of weeks you will not only feel like a real New Yorker, but look like it to anyone watching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caring for Creation</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/02/caring-for-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/02/caring-for-creation/</guid>
      <description>My friend Matthew Bartlett recently started his own publishing company, and his first book is The Biblical Mandate for Caring for Creation by retired New Zealand minister Dick Tripp. The 158-page book, which can be yours for a mere $24.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Christianity sexist?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/19/is-christianity-sexist/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/19/is-christianity-sexist/</guid>
      <description>Perhaps the most-prayed Christian prayer is the Lord’s Prayer: “Our Father who art in heaven…” But why Father and not person or parent? Is Christianity sexist?
Our home church denomination recently held a national Synod meeting, and one of the things they discussed was the updated 2011 translation of the NIV Bible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Person’s Prayer</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/17/the-persons-prayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/17/the-persons-prayer/</guid>
      <description>Our Caregiver in the spiritual realm,
Transparent be your name.
Your democracy be voted in,
Your social policy be implemented,
In reality as it is in the spiritual realm.
Give us every day our organic tofu,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luth3r hacks iChurch, makes Bible open source</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/30/luth3r-hacks-ichurch-makes-bible-open-source/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/30/luth3r-hacks-ichurch-makes-bible-open-source/</guid>
      <description>GENEVA TRIBUNE, August 1517.
New things are afoot in the world of Scripture freedom. Two days ago a hacker, who goes under the pseudonym Mart1n Luth3r, released a set of 95 bullet points outlining how to hack iChurch’s core systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I stopped reading a classic</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/22/why-i-stopped-reading-a-classic/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/22/why-i-stopped-reading-a-classic/</guid>
      <description>The Brothers Karamazov by Fyodor Dostoyevsky is a classic, or so I’ve heard. It’s one of those books so great and so worth reading that no one you talk to has actually read it.
A 700-page novel is something of a commitment, but I approached this one with an open mind and a daily subway commute.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proof that we are Americanizing</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/20/proof-that-we-are-americanizing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/20/proof-that-we-are-americanizing/</guid>
      <description>I have Uncrustables in my freezer. Yes, ma’am, I tell no lie. Uncrustables in your freezer means that you have attained to the great feat of crossing over to The Other Side. For any of you ignorant folk who do not know about the beauty of Uncrustables, let me introduce you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An uncultured laugh (specially for April Fool’s day)</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/01/an-uncultured-laugh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/01/an-uncultured-laugh/</guid>
      <description>When I went to The Cloisters with Hannah and Eva, there were a few sculptures/carvings that I took pictures of purely to post on here with funny comments, because they sure made us crack up. My apologies go to the artists who did not create their masterpieces for us to laugh at, and to those of you who find Roman Catholic artefacts more meaningful than un-cultured moi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Barbie is a big deal</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/24/why-barbie-is-a-big-deal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/24/why-barbie-is-a-big-deal/</guid>
      <description>Today’s post goes out on a limb a bit. It’s probably going to be controversial and many of you won’t agree with me, but these are some thoughts that have been swirling around in my mind for many months, and that some of you might find beneficial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Should churches care about branding?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/11/should-churches-care-about-branding/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/11/should-churches-care-about-branding/</guid>
      <description>Centuries ago (in internet time) graphic designer David Airey wrote a blog post asking folks whether they’d seen any good church logos. My brother Bryan responded with a thought-provoking comment asking whether churches should even be concerned about “branding”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scaling down</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/07/scaling-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/07/scaling-down/</guid>
      <description>Some of you have probably seen this coming, but this is just a little announcement to say that I’m going to scale back a bit on blogging. In fact, I’m scaling down whatever time I’m spending on the computer in general.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The One True BDFL</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/14/the-one-true-bdfl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/14/the-one-true-bdfl/</guid>
      <description>Note: This blog is mostly read by family and friends, but I wrote this more for my fellow programmers. Knowing me, it’ll be taken the wrong way by both groups of people. :-) By the way, see the first comment for a book give-away!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
