<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jaunts out of NYC on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/category/jaunts-out-of-nyc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jaunts out of NYC on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/category/jaunts-out-of-nyc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A little time travel into the past: April</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/09/24/a-little-time-travel-into-the-past-april/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/09/24/a-little-time-travel-into-the-past-april/</guid>
      <description>In April, we had a wonderful visit from my parents. It was great to spend time together again — especially for the grandkids to have their grandparents around! Spring really was a great time for a visit — not too hot and not too cold, and it’s so beautiful with all the blossoms and flowers out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MeRF Getaway</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/09/02/merf-getaway/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/09/02/merf-getaway/</guid>
      <description>Back in June, some folks in our church (MeRF = Messiah’s Reformed Fellowship) headed out to Pennsylvania for a getaway at Kirby House, a beautiful old house that was once used by the Kirby family as their summer home in the mountains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s been a decade</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/02/13/its-been-a-decade/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/02/13/its-been-a-decade/</guid>
      <description>Like I said last week, it’s been cold here! However, Ben and I did have a blessed little escape from the cold back in January for 3 nights, when we eloped to Jamaica while my parents looked after our kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camping in the wilds of New Jersey</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/03/camping-in-the-wilds-of-new-jersey/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/03/camping-in-the-wilds-of-new-jersey/</guid>
      <description>The first weekend in September we went camping with Lillian and Jeremy and Shanna at High Point State Park. We didn’t really know what to expect, seeing that we had never been there before, but we were up for trying it — our very first camping trip in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fruit picking in Princeton</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/09/26/fruit-picking-in-princeton/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/09/26/fruit-picking-in-princeton/</guid>
      <description>At the end of July (boy, how is it that the end of July is already months ago??) I took the girls fruit picking at Terhune Orchards just outside of Princeton. It’s a lovely place, and it’s always so nice to pick your own produce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A morning in Montclair</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/06/27/a-morning-in-montclair/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/06/27/a-morning-in-montclair/</guid>
      <description>A few Saturdays ago, we headed about 20 minutes west to Montclair for a bit of a greenery and suburban fix. We just had a little picnic morning tea in a park, the girls ran around, and we admired the big mansions surrounding the park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cool wood grain</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/15/cool-wood-grain/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/15/cool-wood-grain/</guid>
      <description>I saw this beam at the farm we stayed at when we took Lizel to Lancaster County, and really liked the way the wood grain showed up on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 years of friendship, and still going strong</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/10/20-years-of-friendship-and-still-going-strong/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/10/20-years-of-friendship-and-still-going-strong/</guid>
      <description>In March, my friend Lizel visited us from South Africa.
Lizel and I have been close friends since we were seven years old, despite living apart for 15 of those. As kids, we would do all sorts of crazy things like pelt the neighbour’s house with mud cookies, or knock on people’s doors and run away, or take whoopie cushions into shops and walk through the aisles making farting noises.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A few post-earthquake photos</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/22/a-few-post-earthquake-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/22/a-few-post-earthquake-photos/</guid>
      <description>This is my last post about my trip to Christchurch in January. It’s about time, I think! This post is largely for our US readers who have expressed interest in the earthquake side of things back home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reconnecting with friends and family</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/08/reconnecting-with-friends-and-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/08/reconnecting-with-friends-and-family/</guid>
      <description>When the girls and I were in New Zealand, we had quite the social time visiting friends and family. The kids got so used to going out and visiting people that if we had the odd morning where we weren’t going out they’d ask, “aren’t we going to visit someone today?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More wedding pictures</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/16/more-wedding-pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/16/more-wedding-pictures/</guid>
      <description>Well, I said I’d share some more wedding pictures when I got some time to get them on here. I didn’t get the time, but I made the time, so here they are.
The first lot of photos were taken outside in the harsh sunlight (always a bad move), so unfortunately everyone has sunglass shadows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeremy and Lillian’s wedding day</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/14/jeremy-and-lillians-wedding-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/14/jeremy-and-lillians-wedding-day/</guid>
      <description>On January the 21st Jeremy and Lillian tied the knot, and it was a beautiful day in all respects. It was lovely and sunny (even it if was a bit windy), everything went smoothly and it was just such a joyous day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another wonderful Christmas</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/04/another-wonderful-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/04/another-wonderful-christmas/</guid>
      <description>Christmas feels like such a long time ago… but I really want to share these photos with you from our time with Jeremy’s folks.
We took the bus to Philadelphia from where Jeremy picked us up and drove us out to his parents’ place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More good times</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/17/more-good-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/17/more-good-times/</guid>
      <description>Our last overnight stop on our roadtrip with my parents was at Mr &amp;amp; Mrs Brauning’s place. Mr Brauning is a pastor who came and filled our pulpit for a few months while our home congregation was vacant and the Braunings are loved by many back home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If looks could kill…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/14/if-looks-could-kill/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/14/if-looks-could-kill/</guid>
      <description>then this cheeky face kills me with laughter almost every time I see it.
Figuratively, of course.
She was putting on her pretend grouchy face, only to dissolve into giggles herself!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stop 3 on the trip</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/14/stop-3-on-the-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/14/stop-3-on-the-trip/</guid>
      <description>Just a little note: I’m not blogging real-time. I think I might have blogged about something on the same day it happened about twice in the whole time I’ve had this blog. I just don’t have the luxury of lots of time to be able to do that!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magnificent Niagara Falls</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/10/magnificent-niagara-falls/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/10/magnificent-niagara-falls/</guid>
      <description>After our 3 nights in the Adirondack mountains, we drove to Niagara Falls. The scenery on the way was beautiful!
Crossing the border into Canada.
We arrived on a cold, windy, overcast afternoon, but didn’t know whether the weather would clear up over the weekend, so decided to brave it and go look at the falls regardless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some nature shots from the Adirondacks</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/07/some-nature-shots-from-the-adirondacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/07/some-nature-shots-from-the-adirondacks/</guid>
      <description>During our time in the Adirondacks it rained most of the time, except for our first afternoon there. There were some breaks in the rain, though, and I took my chances to go outside and take some ‘nature shots’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October, a wonderful month with family</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/03/october-a-wonderful-month-with-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/03/october-a-wonderful-month-with-family/</guid>
      <description>For most of the month of October we had my parents visiting with us, and we had a very good time together.
The highlight of their time here was probably our road trip that we took to the Adirondack mountains, Niagara Falls, Toronto and Pennsylvania to visit our friends the Tysons and the Braunings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road trip report, Days 5 and 6</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/06/road-trip-report-days-5-and-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/06/road-trip-report-days-5-and-6/</guid>
      <description>We left Washington D.C. on a Friday afternoon and drove up to Baltimore. I’m not sure if we saw the wrong side of Baltimore or what, but neither of us were particularly impressed. I guess that wasn’t helped by a fire drill going on at the Art Museum as soon as we walked in, and nobody knowing what was going on, including the staff, which meant we just walked straight back out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Baltimore hotel window view</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/04/a-baltimore-hotel-window-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/04/a-baltimore-hotel-window-view/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been just a little bit busy lately, preparing for another roadtrip (yay!), this time with my parents (double yay!) who should have arrived in San Francisco by now. I hope. I realised I never gave my parents my contact details here in the States before they left.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road trip report, Day 4</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/30/road-trip-report-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/30/road-trip-report-day-4/</guid>
      <description>So you’re all dying to hear how we became chummy with the President, right? Well, it happened like this: we were walking outside the fence of his big fancy house, admiring the well kept garden and lawns, all lonesome and deserted when suddenly he jumped out of the bushes and shouted “BOO!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road trip report, Day 3</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/26/road-trip-report-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/26/road-trip-report-day-3/</guid>
      <description>Just a little note: I’ve switched to uploading smaller photos on here, to make things faster for me while editing blog posts, and hopefully also for you as subscribers having to download the posts. As far as I can tell the quality is still pretty good, but let me know what you think.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road trip report, Day 1 and 2</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/24/road-trip-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/24/road-trip-report/</guid>
      <description>So like I said, Margaret took me and the girls on a week-long road trip (thanks, Gary!) and boy did we have fun! There was a good amount of banter and hilarity and also some really good conversations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turning 30</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/08/turning-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/08/turning-30/</guid>
      <description>Last Thursday I (Ben) turned 30, and an otherwise ordinary workday was turned into Something Special by my lovely wife. She’d been being secretive about something for a few weeks, so I guessed something was going to happen, but I had no idea what.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lorraine, the not-so Divine</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/20/lorraine-the-not-so-divine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/20/lorraine-the-not-so-divine/</guid>
      <description>Saw this old building on our way to Jeremy’s place in Philadelphia, and couldn’t help noticing the irony.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to Mr. J</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/15/visit-to-mr-j/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/15/visit-to-mr-j/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weekends ago, we visited our good friend, Jeremy, in Philadelphia.
What a blast — we did some sight-seeing, but also my favourite pastime: having good discussions over good food.
There was of course also an appropriate amount of teasing which Jeremy thrived upon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to Connecticut</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/04/visit-to-connecticut/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/04/visit-to-connecticut/</guid>
      <description>A few weekends ago we drove up to Connecticut to visit fellow Kiwis, Ron and Judy Snoek and their son Troy. They very kindly hosted us for a night with some good ol’ home-like hospitality. It was so nice to spend time with them and get to know them a bit better (I (Franci) hadn’t even met them before this!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Franci the judge</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/10/franci-the-judge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/10/franci-the-judge/</guid>
      <description>Now that’s a catchy title if I ever saw one! :-)
This past Saturday I took the train up to a little town called Irvington on the bank of the Hudson river where there was a huge homeschoolers debating tournament going on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Punta Cana!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/11/punta-cana/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/11/punta-cana/</guid>
      <description>Ben and I have always dreamed of going on a romantic tropical island holiday. This has partly been inspired by the total un-tropical-ness of our honeymoon destination (Stewart Island! I don’t know why we ever thought it would be tropical.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back to reality</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/09/back-to-reality/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/09/back-to-reality/</guid>
      <description>This past weekend Ben and I flew off into the Tropical sunset and had a total blast. We came back on Monday night and since then we’ve been right back into things here. I wasn’t organised enough to have self-publishing posts past Monday’s post on here, and things have been busy since we’ve been back, so you’ll all have to wait a little while till Friday to hear all about our trip and see a whole bunch of photos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A few lovely photos</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/07/a-few-lovely-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/07/a-few-lovely-photos/</guid>
      <description>I thought I’d share a few photos of our time with the Braunings. We were so blessed by their hospitality, company, conversation and great food. Thanks again for inviting us, Mr &amp;amp; Mrs Brauning, and putting up with our changed plans and an invalid!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And then there was Texas</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/22/and-then-there-was-texas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/22/and-then-there-was-texas/</guid>
      <description>After the Tschetter family reunion in Colorado, I caught a ride with Ben’s parents to Smolan, Kansas, where Grandma and Grandpa Tschetter live. (Ben had to head back to NYC for work.) It was really special to spend 2 nights in their home, see Grandma’s cool kitchen wallpaper and eat out of her pretty china.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to Colorado</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/16/visit-to-colorado/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/16/visit-to-colorado/</guid>
      <description>The last week of July we headed off to Colorado for a Tschetter family reunion (Ben’s mum’s side of the family) to specially celebrate Ben’s grandparents’ 70th wedding anniversary. We flew to Denver and then Mum and Dad Hoyt picked us up from the airport and we drove into the mountains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We’re back!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/12/were-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/12/were-back/</guid>
      <description>I’ve you’re an avid follower of our blog, you will have noticed that our posts have been rather sparse the last 2 and a half weeks. We’ve had a great time away traipsing over the country visiting family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend trip to New Jersey</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/24/weekend-trip-to-new-jersey/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/24/weekend-trip-to-new-jersey/</guid>
      <description>I promised that I’d share about our time with the Stoltes in New Jersey this past weekend. I can’t believe it’s already Wednesday — and I’m only getting around to this now.
Public transport around here is really good.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
