<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2014s on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2014s on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas from the Hoyts</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/12/25/merry-christmas-from-the-hoyts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/12/25/merry-christmas-from-the-hoyts/</guid>
      <description>May your Christmas be blessed with much peace and joy.
Kind of like this:
Just maybe a bit more peaceful. :-)
&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/12/19/thanksgiving-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/12/19/thanksgiving-3/</guid>
      <description>This year, we celebrated Thanksgiving on the day after Thanksgiving, which actually gave us a good opportunity to go to the Macy’s Thanksgiving parade in New York City. Our friend Peter lives right by where the parade went past (and right next to the Empire State Building!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Esther’s 5th birthday</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/12/12/esthers-5th-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/12/12/esthers-5th-birthday/</guid>
      <description>It is hard to believe that my little baby Esther…
has grown into a big FIVE year old. How did that happen??
Well, in early November we celebrated her 5th birthday with much less fanfare than I had hoped and planned due to a bunch of us getting super nasty colds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In lieu of Halloween</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/12/05/in-lieu-of-halloween/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/12/05/in-lieu-of-halloween/</guid>
      <description>This year, instead of celebrating Halloween, which is such a massive deal here in the States and which we don’t feel particularly comfortable with joining in on for various reasons, we decided to do things a little differently and have a Fall Party with our good friends, Alfredo and Damaris and their kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/11/28/thanksgiving-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/11/28/thanksgiving-2/</guid>
      <description>Here in the States, people celebrated Thanksgiving yesterday. We’re actually celebrating it today, so that it could work out for Jeremy and Lillian to be here with us.
So, for that reason, and because there’s cooking to be done, I’ll keep this short and leave you with the lyrics of a hymn whose tune I dislike, but that has powerful words.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October Fest</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/11/21/october-fest/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/11/21/october-fest/</guid>
      <description>One weekend in October we went to an October Fest (not the beer-drinking kind) hosted by the Essex County Environmental Center, the same place where the girls go for their Frog Pond Science Club. It was a lovely community event where all the things on offer were free — crafts, a petting zoo, a snake man, music, and even some snacks!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frog Pond Science Club</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/11/14/frog-pond-science-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/11/14/frog-pond-science-club/</guid>
      <description>I signed Marica and Esther up for a “Frog Pond Science Club” class at the Essex County Environmental Center, which is about a half hour drive from our house heading into the mountains. Once you get past Newark, it’s a beautiful drive, especially this time of the year with all the autumn colours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cooking with friends</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/11/07/cooking-with-friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/11/07/cooking-with-friends/</guid>
      <description>When I was in high school, a woman in our church (hi, Jantina!) got a bunch of us young’uns together for a day of cooking at her house. She gave us some basic recipes and tips and together we spent the day cooking and baking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some nice things</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/31/some-nice-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/31/some-nice-things/</guid>
      <description>I like autumn. It’s not so hot, there are pretty colors everywhere, and the change of season brings all sorts of nice things like warm slippers and hot drinks, nice decorations and good smelling candles, and fun kids’ crafts…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If your daughter asks you for french toast…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/24/if-your-daughter-asks-you-for-french-toast/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/24/if-your-daughter-asks-you-for-french-toast/</guid>
      <description>If your daughter asks you for French toast, then you’ll be tempted to just say ‘no’. It’s a weekday, after all. But then you’ll remember that you want to be more of a ‘yes’ parent than a ‘no’ parent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marica the entrepreneur</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/13/marica-the-entrepreneur/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/13/marica-the-entrepreneur/</guid>
      <description>When Marica was 4, I got a fancy new camera as a very generous gift. Marica then got our old camera, which was a little point and shoot that was on its way out but still in good condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I quit Facebook (for now)</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/10/why-i-quit-facebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/10/why-i-quit-facebook/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: this is simply my reasoning for giving up Facebook for the foreseeable future. I’m not saying any of this to make you feel like you should quit Facebook too.
&amp;nbsp;
I thought I’d give a bit of an explanation to those who might be interested on why I deactivated my Facebook account 3 months ago (since a few people have asked).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camping in the wilds of New Jersey</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/03/camping-in-the-wilds-of-new-jersey/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/03/camping-in-the-wilds-of-new-jersey/</guid>
      <description>The first weekend in September we went camping with Lillian and Jeremy and Shanna at High Point State Park. We didn’t really know what to expect, seeing that we had never been there before, but we were up for trying it — our very first camping trip in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fruit picking in Princeton</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/09/26/fruit-picking-in-princeton/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/09/26/fruit-picking-in-princeton/</guid>
      <description>At the end of July (boy, how is it that the end of July is already months ago??) I took the girls fruit picking at Terhune Orchards just outside of Princeton. It’s a lovely place, and it’s always so nice to pick your own produce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer fun</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/09/12/summer-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/09/12/summer-fun/</guid>
      <description>The summer is coming to an end, and we are back in the full swing of homeschooling. We took a nice long summer break. I had great intentions of schooling through the summer, but somehow as it warmed up outside we all just lost steam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A prize-winning photo!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/09/05/a-prize-winning-photo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/09/05/a-prize-winning-photo/</guid>
      <description>With such a sensationalist title, you’d think this is something really special, right? Well, not quite! TripAdvisor (where Ben works) had this internal competition over the summer where you could send in a photo with a TripAdvisor fridge magnet on your vehicle, and every week they picked a winner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enthralled by the TV</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/29/enthralled-by-the-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/29/enthralled-by-the-tv/</guid>
      <description>My computer desk is just next to the couch, and one day while I was doing things on the computer and the girls were watching a show, I looked over and just had to quickly snap a picture of the girls enjoying it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The squishy baby with the hair</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/22/the-squishy-baby-with-the-hair/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/22/the-squishy-baby-with-the-hair/</guid>
      <description>Laurelin Grace,
you have a sweet face,
I love your squishy fatness
to cuddle and to kiss,
But what makes me fondly stare
is your light, unruly hair!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miss Communication</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/19/miss-communication/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/19/miss-communication/</guid>
      <description>I was folding washing this morning listening to Marica and Esther talk, and just had to share this funny:
E: “Mawica, dose are nithe octoputheth.”
M: “They aren’t octopuses, they’re decorations!
E: “Dey look like octoputheth…”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun day at the Fair</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/15/fun-day-at-the-fair/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/15/fun-day-at-the-fair/</guid>
      <description>On the first weekend of July we took the kids to the Meadowlands State Fair which is pretty close to where we live. The kids were giddy with excitement!
We got there as soon as it opened in the afternoon so it wouldn’t be too busy, and that was a good idea because there weren’t many lines to wait in, but everything got progressively busier during the late afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A hobbit comes of age</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/08/a-hobbit-comes-of-age/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/08/a-hobbit-comes-of-age/</guid>
      <description>As everyone knows — well, at least everyone who’s a fan of Tolkien — a hobbit comes of age at 33. I turned this ripe old age the other day, and had a fabulous party, mostly organized by Franci, my lovely hobbit-wife.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A visit from cousins</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/01/a-visit-from-cousins/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/01/a-visit-from-cousins/</guid>
      <description>The last weekend in June, we had two of Ben’s cousins, Chris and Laura Lee, visit us from Texas. That weekend was a real blast! Packed full of sight-seeing and talking and fun! Here’s some of what we did with them:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A visit from the Baneks</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/07/25/a-visit-from-the-baneks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/07/25/a-visit-from-the-baneks/</guid>
      <description>In June, we had a lovely visit from Ben’s Uncle Walter, Aunt Nelda and cousin Alexander from Texas. They were here for 4 days and we got a really good amount of sight-seeing done with them, balanced by a nice lot of calmly visiting at home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marica’s recital at Steinway Hall</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/07/18/maricas-recital-at-steinway-hall/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/07/18/maricas-recital-at-steinway-hall/</guid>
      <description>Marica and Esther started piano lessons the week after our piano arrived, and have both been enjoying it a lot, no doubt because of their excellent teacher (who also happens to be our friend!), Shannon Murphy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A bonus Laurelin feature</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/07/15/a-bonus-laurelin-feature/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/07/15/a-bonus-laurelin-feature/</guid>
      <description>This post is specially for grandparents, aunties and other such doting people who would be interested in these videos of our little Lorax.
Marica loves to play rough and tumble with Laurelin, but she’s very careful not to be too rough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reaga</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/07/11/reaga/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/07/11/reaga/</guid>
      <description>Reaga is a mix between reading and yoga. Marica has invented it without even knowing!
The other day I was sitting at the computer doing stuff when I saw something out of the corner of my eye that didn’t look quite right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pretty little gift</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/07/04/pretty-little-gift/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/07/04/pretty-little-gift/</guid>
      <description>Where we live now, we have no garden, which is a bit of a shame. The other day, though, we were outside and the girls were riding their bikes on the sidewalk when Esther brought these little flowers to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A morning in Montclair</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/06/27/a-morning-in-montclair/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/06/27/a-morning-in-montclair/</guid>
      <description>A few Saturdays ago, we headed about 20 minutes west to Montclair for a bit of a greenery and suburban fix. We just had a little picnic morning tea in a park, the girls ran around, and we admired the big mansions surrounding the park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflecting on a year</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/06/20/reflecting-on-a-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/06/20/reflecting-on-a-year/</guid>
      <description>Laurelin Grace, our youngest, turned one recently. The first year of her life has been an eventful one for our family. She was born 3 weeks early, induced in a bit of a rush. For the first 5 weeks of her life, she nursed every 2 hours or less and developed strong lungs from all her colic-induced crying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurelin’s first birthday</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/06/13/laurelins-first-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/06/13/laurelins-first-birthday/</guid>
      <description>Three weeks ago, Laurelin turned 1. Crazy stuff, how did that happen?
We had a really low-key day, church in the morning, and then a little party with our lovely friends Alfredo and Damaris and their kids (whom I didn’t get a good photo of, sorry!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A general update. About time too</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/06/06/a-general-update-about-time-too/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/06/06/a-general-update-about-time-too/</guid>
      <description>Three weeks ago, Laurelin turned one. I started writing a post the week before her birthday and got about two paragraphs in. Life is a bit like that at the moment — some people have hinted or asked directly if we will post regularly again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr Rubik’s back</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/05/08/mr-rubiks-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/05/08/mr-rubiks-back/</guid>
      <description>Marica and I went to the Liberty Science Center in Jersey City last Saturday to see their new Rubik’s Cube exhibition, which was being opened by Ernő Rubik, the inventor of the cube. I own a cube, but still have no idea how to solve it…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elisabeth Elliot, you’re being milked!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/05/05/elisabeth-elliot-youre-being-milked/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/05/05/elisabeth-elliot-youre-being-milked/</guid>
      <description>Reference: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Passion_and_Purity :-)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My daddy’s stronger than your daddy!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/05/02/my-daddys-stronger-than-your-daddy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/05/02/my-daddys-stronger-than-your-daddy/</guid>
      <description>And handsomer too. So there! :-)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Woody’s disgrace</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/04/28/woodys-disgrace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/04/28/woodys-disgrace/</guid>
      <description>The other day I found this:
It just tickled my funny bone that Esther would dress Woody in a dress! Despite the brave face he’s putting on, he’s secretly mortified.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Settling in. Or at least trying to</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/04/24/settling-in-or-at-least-trying-to/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/04/24/settling-in-or-at-least-trying-to/</guid>
      <description>Our container with all our stuff arrived last Wednesday from New Zealand. It’s great to have our things again, but also very odd. It all seems so out of place. The furniture looks about as comfortable in our apartment as a fat girl in a skinny girl’s clothes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things I forgot</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/04/16/things-i-forgot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/04/16/things-i-forgot/</guid>
      <description>When you live somewhere and move away, it’s easy to forget the things that were strange, funny or hard, especially if they’re just small details of life. There are a few things that have struck me again, this time around, in no particular order:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everyday beauty</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/04/10/everyday-beauty/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/04/10/everyday-beauty/</guid>
      <description>It’s so easy to become complacent, to not notice the beauty around us.
The beauty in the messes of little kids, because those kids are kids you love, and because they won’t be little forever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Living with a veneer of glamour</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/04/07/living-with-a-veneer-of-glamour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/04/07/living-with-a-veneer-of-glamour/</guid>
      <description>The chandeliers in the apartment we stayed at for the first month reminded me (by way of trying to appear more beautiful than they actually are) of a piece I wrote a while back that I’ve meant to put up here on the blog and never got around to doing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We’ve moved in!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/04/05/weve-moved-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/04/05/weve-moved-in/</guid>
      <description>Just a quick note to let you all know that we’ve moved into our new apartment where we hope to be for the next year (or more) in Jersey City Heights. We moved in on Monday and it’s been a bit of a shambles around here that is slowly turning into order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful berries</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/04/02/beautiful-berries/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/04/02/beautiful-berries/</guid>
      <description>I was washing berries for dessert the other night and just had to stop and marvel that God didn’t just make food useful, He also made it beautiful.
And they tasted delicious!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting out of a tight spot</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/03/31/getting-out-of-a-tight-spot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/03/31/getting-out-of-a-tight-spot/</guid>
      <description>The other day Ben and I were walking along when we spotted a car that had been very tightly parked in.
The back:
The front:
Lo and behold, imagine our disbelief and glee when we see the person whose car it is come along and get in the car and proceed to get out of the spot!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another birthday</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/03/27/another-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/03/27/another-birthday/</guid>
      <description>Last week, I celebrated another birthday. The last one of my 20’s. Marica very tactfully said, “Mum, it’s good that you’re not turning 30. Thirty is too old for a woman!”
Ben took the morning off so that we could go to the MVC to get our New Jersey driver’s licences, but the unfortunately the proof of address we took along was not good enough in their books, so we had to leave without the licences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>East Wind Over Weehawken</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/03/24/east-wind-over-weehawken/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/03/24/east-wind-over-weehawken/</guid>
      <description>The other night we had our temporary landlord over for dinner and as well as having a lovely time, we also found out a bit about some of the art around here. The big painting in the dining room is a replica of The Storm by Pierre Auguste Cot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Peach Fuzz</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/03/14/little-peach-fuzz/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/03/14/little-peach-fuzz/</guid>
      <description>It’s so much fun to have a baby in the house! (Especially now that I’m getting more sleep.)
Laurelin is the cause of many laughs, hugs and smiles.
Her sisters dote on her (and so do her parents!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life in limbo</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/03/10/life-in-limbo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/03/10/life-in-limbo/</guid>
      <description>Since the last time I posted, we’ve moved into our temporary apartment for the month of March, settled into a daily routine with homeschooling in the mornings, and all of us have gotten sick. New climate, new bugs — it was to be expected!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Aliens are back in the Apple</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/02/26/the-aliens-are-back-in-the-apple/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/02/26/the-aliens-are-back-in-the-apple/</guid>
      <description>After two long, but pretty good flights, we’re back in New York. If you told me a year ago that I’d be here now, I would have laughed and said, “Yeah, right!” But here we are after a few whirlwind weeks of getting ready to move.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going, going, (almost) gone!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/02/19/going-going-almost-gone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/02/19/going-going-almost-gone/</guid>
      <description>We’re on our way to the States: our house is under offer, we’ve traveled to Auckland and have had our Green Cards approved, and tomorrow, Lord willing, we fly out to New York.
The last few weeks have been a super busy time, and a bit of an emotional roller coaster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gearing up to go</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/02/10/gearing-up-to-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/02/10/gearing-up-to-go/</guid>
      <description>The last few weeks have gotten exponentially busier as we’re getting ready for our move back to the States. It is strange how something can feel so unreal even in the midst of the busyness. I have days where it’s almost a surprise to me when people ask when we’re leaving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The solution</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/01/30/the-solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/01/30/the-solution/</guid>
      <description>Oops… that must have been the longest 48 hours in the history of the world. And I know you’re all just bursting to know the answer to the riddle. (Not!)
What can see light but has never seen the sun;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A little riddle for you</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/01/26/a-little-riddle-for-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/01/26/a-little-riddle-for-you/</guid>
      <description>Last night I was sitting down and my mind thought up a riddle all by itself. It’s useful like that. See if you can figure it out:
What can see light but has never seen the sun;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flights booked, date set!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/01/25/flights-booked-date-set/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/01/25/flights-booked-date-set/</guid>
      <description>We started this blog almost four years ago with the words “so we’re going overseas in a month”. They do say history repeats itself…
About six months ago, Ben got a job offer with TripAdvisor who was hoping to acquire Oyster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A weekend visit to Oamaru</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/01/07/a-weekend-visit-to-oamaru/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/01/07/a-weekend-visit-to-oamaru/</guid>
      <description>The last weekend of last year we made the three hour drive down to Oamaru to visit Mum and Dad Hoyt. We always love visiting them! This time around Bevan and Elrike were there with us, and the girls had a great time playing together in a different setting.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
