<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Food on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/category/food/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Food on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/category/food/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A decade old!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/05/02/a-decade-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/05/02/a-decade-old/</guid>
      <description>In February, Marica turned 10. TEN?? How does a decade go by so fast? Marica is growing up — both taller and also growing in maturity little by little. Or maybe not so little! Her independence in the kitchen is growing, and she’s becoming quite the cook and baker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/01/26/advent/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/01/26/advent/</guid>
      <description>Advent is such a great time of the year. It’s filled with the anticipation of Christmas, warm kitchens overflowing with delicious smells, Christmas crafts, Christmas music playing in the background, parties, friends… (and it’s unfortunately also filled with busyness, usually mostly my own doing!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful autumn</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/12/23/beautiful-autumn-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/12/23/beautiful-autumn-2/</guid>
      <description>Autumn this year was beautiful and mild and felt like a sort of nicer continuation of summer. We were, of course, back at doing school, but we tried to enjoy the nice weather as much as we could.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banana Cake with chocolate cream cheese icing</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/11/11/banana-cake-with-chocolate-cream-cheese-icing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/11/11/banana-cake-with-chocolate-cream-cheese-icing/</guid>
      <description>I built a cake earlier this week. I’m doing really well at blogging about it while the cake is still in existence on the kitchen counter! I’m still playing catch-up with blogging about news from the summer, but I wanted to share this before it died in my drafts folder like so many other recipes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Co-op class pizza night</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/05/20/co-op-class-pizza-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/05/20/co-op-class-pizza-night/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp;
I teach a Narnia literature class at our homeschool co-op, which has been really fun. For me, anyway. Not quite sure what the kids think, seeing that it’s a discussion class and I make them talk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Spring Tea Party</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/05/13/a-spring-tea-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/05/13/a-spring-tea-party/</guid>
      <description>In our living room stands a beautiful wooden display cabinet that has been in my family for 3 generations. It displays a selection of pretty tea cups, teapots, milk pitchers and sugar pots I have been given from my grandma, my mum, and Ben’s grandma Tschetter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easter 2016</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/05/06/easter-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/05/06/easter-2016/</guid>
      <description>This year’s Easter was a busy but lovely one. We kept up the tradition of making hot cross buns and egg dying, which the kids always love,
&amp;nbsp;
and on Easter Sunday we hosted a large crowd of church folk for a yummy dinner, followed by some rousing hymn singing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April Fool’s Day</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/04/29/april-fools-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/04/29/april-fools-day/</guid>
      <description>Our family, especially the kids, have taken a real liking to April 1st. The kids plan pranks for weeks in advance, which they then gleefully execute on the day. We also have a little tradition of having waffles for dinner on that night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pie Day</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/01/01/pie-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/01/01/pie-day/</guid>
      <description>Back in mid-November I had a few girls from church over at our house for a pie making day. We worked hard, had lots of fun and got to enjoy some pretty yummy pies.
For those of you who might be interested, here are the recipes of what we made.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple picking day</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/12/04/apple-picking-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/12/04/apple-picking-day/</guid>
      <description>On a lovely warm day back in October, the girls and I took a field trip to a farm about an hour’s drive from where we live to go apple and pumpkin picking. The weather was fantastic — it was nice and sunny and not too hot or cold, a real Goldilocks kind of day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marica’s newest yummy dish</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/10/30/maricas-newest-yummy-dish/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/10/30/maricas-newest-yummy-dish/</guid>
      <description>Marica recently got a cookbook out of the library and was looking through it one afternoon. She came to me and said, “I’m going to make Stromboli, and I don’t want you to help me.” Sure!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April Fool’s Dinner</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/04/03/april-fools-dinner/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/04/03/april-fools-dinner/</guid>
      <description>A few years back, on a whim, I decided to start a fun tradition for April Fool’s Day dinner: dessert for dinner (and no need to have dinner for dessert!). Turns out the kids think this is great, but the adults give a little groan at the thought.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas 2014</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/30/christmas-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/30/christmas-2014/</guid>
      <description>This year was the first year I hosted all of Christmas (meaning both our Christmas Eve and Christmas Day celebrations), and it was fun! We had my parents with us, which was very special, and we also hosted James and Laura Williams and Laura’s friend, Ella.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homemade nutella</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/16/homemade-nutella/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/16/homemade-nutella/</guid>
      <description>I’ve always wanted to try making a version of Nutella at home, so recently I tried it. There are oodles of recipes online, and the one I tried is from here. It calls for coconut sugar, which I think is a bit of a fad food (not to mention its sustainability is questionable), so I used regular sugar and maple syrup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/12/19/thanksgiving-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/12/19/thanksgiving-3/</guid>
      <description>This year, we celebrated Thanksgiving on the day after Thanksgiving, which actually gave us a good opportunity to go to the Macy’s Thanksgiving parade in New York City. Our friend Peter lives right by where the parade went past (and right next to the Empire State Building!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Esther’s 5th birthday</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/12/12/esthers-5th-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/12/12/esthers-5th-birthday/</guid>
      <description>It is hard to believe that my little baby Esther…
has grown into a big FIVE year old. How did that happen??
Well, in early November we celebrated her 5th birthday with much less fanfare than I had hoped and planned due to a bunch of us getting super nasty colds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cooking with friends</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/11/07/cooking-with-friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/11/07/cooking-with-friends/</guid>
      <description>When I was in high school, a woman in our church (hi, Jantina!) got a bunch of us young’uns together for a day of cooking at her house. She gave us some basic recipes and tips and together we spent the day cooking and baking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some nice things</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/31/some-nice-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/31/some-nice-things/</guid>
      <description>I like autumn. It’s not so hot, there are pretty colors everywhere, and the change of season brings all sorts of nice things like warm slippers and hot drinks, nice decorations and good smelling candles, and fun kids’ crafts…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If your daughter asks you for french toast…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/24/if-your-daughter-asks-you-for-french-toast/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/24/if-your-daughter-asks-you-for-french-toast/</guid>
      <description>If your daughter asks you for French toast, then you’ll be tempted to just say ‘no’. It’s a weekday, after all. But then you’ll remember that you want to be more of a ‘yes’ parent than a ‘no’ parent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A hobbit comes of age</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/08/a-hobbit-comes-of-age/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/08/a-hobbit-comes-of-age/</guid>
      <description>As everyone knows — well, at least everyone who’s a fan of Tolkien — a hobbit comes of age at 33. I turned this ripe old age the other day, and had a fabulous party, mostly organized by Franci, my lovely hobbit-wife.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another birthday</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/03/27/another-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/03/27/another-birthday/</guid>
      <description>Last week, I celebrated another birthday. The last one of my 20’s. Marica very tactfully said, “Mum, it’s good that you’re not turning 30. Thirty is too old for a woman!”
Ben took the morning off so that we could go to the MVC to get our New Jersey driver’s licences, but the unfortunately the proof of address we took along was not good enough in their books, so we had to leave without the licences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Return to the Roadtrip: On to the Tschetter Reunion</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/08/27/return-to-the-roadtrip-on-to-the-tschetter-reunion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/08/27/return-to-the-roadtrip-on-to-the-tschetter-reunion/</guid>
      <description>Some of you might recall that it was at the Tschetter reunion (Ben’s mum’s side of the family) that my laptop hard drive died, so I lost photos of the first half of that stop as well, which is a real shame because Ben’s mum’s Uncle Herb and Aunt Susan came to visit one evening and I got some really nice shots of them, but hey, so’s life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Knoxville Farmers’ Market</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/18/the-knoxville-farmers-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/18/the-knoxville-farmers-market/</guid>
      <description>Today is our second day at the Hoyt reunion in Georgia. Since I’ve last blogged we’ve visited the Holders in Knoxville, and some friends in Atlanta. I hope to blog about that soon, but I need to catch up with sharing some of the things we did in Knoxville first!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some people just can’t eat cake like normal people</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/30/some-people-just-cant-eat-cake-like-normal-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/30/some-people-just-cant-eat-cake-like-normal-people/</guid>
      <description>Some of you might remember Jeremy and Lillian’s bizarre cake eating rituals at their wedding ceremony in New Zealand. Well, it would seem the strangeness just keeps on going.
Just look at the mess they made of my beautiful lemon cake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marica turned 5</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/12/marica-turned-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/12/marica-turned-5/</guid>
      <description>How is it that they go from this…
to this…
so unbelievably fast?
Too fast, that’s what. I’m sure someone’s been speeding up the time.
Marica turned 5 in February, but when we were in New Zealand, my mum (Ouma to the kids) threw a birthday party for Marica.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Malboro Man sandwich</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/20/a-malboro-man-sandwich/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/20/a-malboro-man-sandwich/</guid>
      <description>I’m subsribed to The Pioneer Woman Cooks blog, and with every recipe that comes from there I’m almost drooling. I’ve never had one of her recipes fail, and they’re always a hit. The Malboro Man Sandwich was especially a hit with Ben, and I loved it too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Fat Bacon Sliders</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/11/big-fat-bacon-sliders/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/11/big-fat-bacon-sliders/</guid>
      <description>Bacon is a beautiful thing. Whoever invented it needs a medal. Bacon and eggs, bacon on pizza, bacon in pasta, bacon with pretty much anything is just wonderful. (I’ve even seen bacon chocolate here in New York!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Christmas goodie report, with recipes</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/06/a-christmas-goodie-report-with-recipes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/06/a-christmas-goodie-report-with-recipes/</guid>
      <description>I love baking. I love sharing baking. I love receiving baking. I love eating baking. Who doesn’t?!
Christmas is always a time of the year that I excitedly go totally overboard in the baking department, making way too many goodies and loving every minute of it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gingerbread House fun</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/22/gingerbread-house-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/22/gingerbread-house-fun/</guid>
      <description>Our much loved pastor’s wife, Julie, invited a few moms over to her house last Friday to make gingerbread houses. What a total blast! We made the houses out of graham crackers instead of baked sheets of gingerbread, which was much easier and less time consuming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nanaimo Bars</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/19/nanaimo-bars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/19/nanaimo-bars/</guid>
      <description>Let me introduce you to a lovely piece of goodness. This little bite of joy is apparently a Canadian treat, and when I saw a recipe for it online some months back, I knew it would be something Ben would enjoy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pizza!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/08/pizza/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/08/pizza/</guid>
      <description>I guess most of you know that there’s nothing much to homemade pizza, except that it can be time consuming. You can put pretty much anything on it, and cover it with cheese and you can call it pizza.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving yumminess</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/28/thanksgiving-yumminess/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/28/thanksgiving-yumminess/</guid>
      <description>Well, Thanksgiving came and went, and we had a lovely day. It was great to have a bonus day where Ben had the day off, and we enjoyed getting to know a friend from church a bit better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The beauty of gratitude</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/23/the-beauty-of-gratitude/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/23/the-beauty-of-gratitude/</guid>
      <description>What a great gift to have a whole feast day dedicated to giving thanks! I’m relishing the opportunity to celebrate Thanksgiving while we’re here in the States. It might even be a tradition we take home to New Zealand with us!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More good times</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/17/more-good-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/17/more-good-times/</guid>
      <description>Our last overnight stop on our roadtrip with my parents was at Mr &amp;amp; Mrs Brauning’s place. Mr Brauning is a pastor who came and filled our pulpit for a few months while our home congregation was vacant and the Braunings are loved by many back home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green and glorious</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/09/green-and-glorious/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/09/green-and-glorious/</guid>
      <description>Hooray for pesto! What a beautiful thing pesto is. Easy to make, and it gives a wonderful flavour to sandwiches, pastas, risotto, pizza, baked potatoes, salads, chocolate cake, wait, what? Just trust me, it’s good stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A pre-engagement visit</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/07/a-pre-engagement-visit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/07/a-pre-engagement-visit/</guid>
      <description>Now that you all know that Lillian and Jeremy are engaged, we can all happily say “Hooray!”. Lillian was here for a very short visit (just under 2 weeks) and flew into JFK, so we got the privilege of hosting the two of them for a few nights before they went off to Philadelphia to go get engaged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A quiet Saturday morning</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/06/a-quiet-saturday-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/06/a-quiet-saturday-morning/</guid>
      <description>It’s quiet because I’m home alone, which is a rare event indeed! Ben took the girls to Prospect Park this morning and I have some time to myself here at home. Guess what I’ve chosen to spend my time doing?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Jeremy eats a mushroom</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/18/how-jeremy-eats-a-mushroom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/18/how-jeremy-eats-a-mushroom/</guid>
      <description>When we were visiting Jeremy in Philly, I made some grilled mushrooms on the barbecue with fresh parmesan, salt, pepper, butter and fresh mozzarella cheese, garnished with a fresh basil leaf. Are your mouths watering yet?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to Mr. J</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/15/visit-to-mr-j/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/15/visit-to-mr-j/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weekends ago, we visited our good friend, Jeremy, in Philadelphia.
What a blast — we did some sight-seeing, but also my favourite pastime: having good discussions over good food.
There was of course also an appropriate amount of teasing which Jeremy thrived upon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blueberry pancakes worth eating</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/11/blueberry-pancakes-worth-eating/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/11/blueberry-pancakes-worth-eating/</guid>
      <description>Blueberries are in season now here in the States and they’re plentiful and cheap. They’re also ridiculously good for you, but that’s really beside the point — what matters is that they taste so good! It’s hard to believe that they can taste better in any way other than plain from the punnet, but these pancakes bring out the blueberry flavour very well and they melt in your mouth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glimpses into the last couple of weeks</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/27/glimpses-into-the-last-couple-of-weeks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/27/glimpses-into-the-last-couple-of-weeks/</guid>
      <description>I don’t know why the weeks go by so fast. I have a bunch of photos to share with you from when Ben’s cousin Sharon visited us a month ago, our trip to Connecticut 2 weeks ago and our trip to visit Jeremy in Philadelphia last weekend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proof that we are Americanizing</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/20/proof-that-we-are-americanizing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/20/proof-that-we-are-americanizing/</guid>
      <description>I have Uncrustables in my freezer. Yes, ma’am, I tell no lie. Uncrustables in your freezer means that you have attained to the great feat of crossing over to The Other Side. For any of you ignorant folk who do not know about the beauty of Uncrustables, let me introduce you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fish Parcels</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/11/fish-parcels/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/11/fish-parcels/</guid>
      <description>I have a quick and easy recipe to share with you. We’re not big fans of fish around here. Yes, I know we should be, it’s healthy and all that… omega 3’s and a bunch of other healthy bits and bobs, but fish just doesn’t really feature on our favourites list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When you don’t have a sandwich press…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/26/when-you-dont-have-a-sandwich-press/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/26/when-you-dont-have-a-sandwich-press/</guid>
      <description>… make your own with whatever you have on hand!
See, it works pretty well!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some other New York sights (and eats) with Hannah and Eva</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/05/some-other-new-york-sights-and-eats-with-hannah-and-eva/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/05/some-other-new-york-sights-and-eats-with-hannah-and-eva/</guid>
      <description>As you can tell, I’m waaay behind on sight-seeing posts! When Hannah and Eva were here way back in March, we did quite a few fun things I haven’t shared here yet, so here’s a photo post of some of the things we did and ate!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yummy muesli</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/07/yummy-muesli/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/07/yummy-muesli/</guid>
      <description>Guess what I’m making today? Muesli! If you’ve never tried your hand at making your own, may I gently prod you in that direction? You will be done with it and with cleaning your kitchen within half an hour, and you’ll be thanking yourself for doing it every breakfast for the next few weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheesecake and getting old</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/28/cheesecake-and-getting-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/28/cheesecake-and-getting-old/</guid>
      <description>Last Sunday (a week and a half ago, almost), I got another year older. It’s funny how birthday excitement has the tendency to wane as you get older! Though perhaps that’s not a good way for me to look at it — it would be better to think about being blessed with another year instead of having a hum-ho attitude of ‘oh, just another year’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Salmon and Couscous Salad</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/14/spring-salmon-and-couscous-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/14/spring-salmon-and-couscous-salad/</guid>
      <description>I know that I’ve had a lot of recipes on here recently. Maybe that can partly be attributed to the weather — the more time we have inside, the more time I have to do fun stuff in the kitchen, plus it’s not so insanely hot when the oven goes on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuscan Pork with beans</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/04/tuscan-pork-with-beans/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/04/tuscan-pork-with-beans/</guid>
      <description>Can I just draw your attention to something rather delicious?
Slow-cooked Tuscan Pork is the thing! I got the recipe on Femina, so you’d better hop over there if you want it. Let me just tell you that this is worth making.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The beauty of bread</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/21/the-beauty-of-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/21/the-beauty-of-bread/</guid>
      <description>Here in the States, I’ve taken to baking most of our bread from scratch by hand, because I can’t stand the taste of the bread here. Specialty breads here taste great, but I do still have a grocery budget to stick to!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cherry Delight on the menu tonight</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/26/cherry-delight-on-the-menu-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/26/cherry-delight-on-the-menu-tonight/</guid>
      <description>Cherry Delight was introduced to us by Lillian, who made it for one of our Advent dinner desserts. She, in turn, got it from her Grandma Tschetter. It is very delicious, and therefore I feel compelled to share the goodness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A visit to Wonderland</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/21/a-visit-to-wonderland/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/21/a-visit-to-wonderland/</guid>
      <description>Last Friday, a few friends from church met up at Alice’s Tea Cup with their daughters for a fun, girly time of drinking tea, eating good food and some good conversation.
Alice’s Tea Cup is definitely a girly tea room, decorated in pretty colours with cool chandeliers and fairy wings on the walls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Having a bad day parenting? Sue McDonald’s!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/19/having-a-bad-day-parenting-sue-mcdonalds/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/19/having-a-bad-day-parenting-sue-mcdonalds/</guid>
      <description>Warning: This article may contain traces of sarcasm.
Maybe she was just having a bad day as a parent. Or who knows, maybe she is getting paid by an advocacy group. But one Mizz Parham from California seems to have a thing against Happy Meals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Chocolate Monkster</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/13/the-chocolate-monkster/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/13/the-chocolate-monkster/</guid>
      <description>Since turning one, Esther has been introduced to the wonders of chocolate. She loves that stuff with a passion!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food is so beautiful</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/07/food-is-so-beautiful-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/07/food-is-so-beautiful-2/</guid>
      <description>In preparing our Christmas dessert I twice had to stop and take pictures because the food was so beautiful.
First up, just admire the beauty of butter, sugar and eggs creamed together:
And when you cook up a syrup of sugar, butter and water, you get pretty swirls!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our first New York Christmas</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/30/our-first-new-york-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/30/our-first-new-york-christmas/</guid>
      <description>This year was the first year our little family did not celebrate Christmas with grandparents. I was going to say that we didn’t celebrate with any extended family, but we do have Lillian here, so we’re not entirely family-less!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy self-crusting pie recipe</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/27/easy-self-crusting-pie-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/27/easy-self-crusting-pie-recipe/</guid>
      <description>I have another easy and yummy recipe to share with you. This is kind of like a quiche, and kind of like a pie… and it is so fast it almost feels like cheating! It’s a Jo Seagar recipe, one that I acquired at the same time as the fudge recipe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>High class mac ‘n cheese recipe (done)</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/10/high-class-mac--n-cheese-recipe-done/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/10/high-class-mac--n-cheese-recipe-done/</guid>
      <description>We recently had an Italian-themed pot-luck lunch at church (we have pot-lucks once a month on the Sunday we have Lord’s Supper) and I wanted to find a recipe that was not just another lasagne. In my online search I came across this recipe, which I thought tasted very yummy indeed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sugar snap pea salad</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/03/sugar-snap-pea-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/03/sugar-snap-pea-salad/</guid>
      <description>When we visited aunt Sharon and uncle Sherwood Hoyt, aunt Sharon made a really nice salad for dinner one evening. I thought it was absolutely delicious and so I’m going to share it here. The recipe can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grocery challenge: week 4. I’m done!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/01/week-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/01/week-4/</guid>
      <description>Let’s just say I’m glad to have life returning to normal! It was a good little exercise in sticking to a budget (or close to, anyway), but I don’t think I’ll be doing that again any time soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grocery Challenge: week 3</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/25/grocery-challenge-week-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/25/grocery-challenge-week-3/</guid>
      <description>This past week seems to have been shorter than the others. Strange how that happens sometimes. Maybe it was because I didn’t have to cook very often! The flu was still having a field day, uh, week at our house and even Ben stayed home for 2 days from work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grocery Challenge: week 2</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/18/grocery-challenge-week-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/18/grocery-challenge-week-2/</guid>
      <description>In some ways, week 2 was a lot easier than week 1. I only bought what I needed, but it seemed that I needed more than $25 worth of stuff a week. You’re probably all thinking “I knew she couldn’t do it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October grocery challenge: week 1</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/11/grocery-challenge-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/11/grocery-challenge-1/</guid>
      <description>I had a very interesting moment on the first day of the challenge. I had hopped over to Tim Challies’ blog and read an article about The Heart of Frugality. I almost immediately wanted to forget about this challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mmmm, white chocolate and Macadamia cookies</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/06/mmmm-white-chocolate-and-macadamia-cookies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/06/mmmm-white-chocolate-and-macadamia-cookies/</guid>
      <description>Macadamia nuts are my absolutely no-doubt-about-it favourite nut! They also seem to be about the most expensive, though. However, I recently discovered that we have an organic grocer nearby and they have bulk bins (unlike the supermarket) and their nuts and pretty much everything else are very well priced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My October grocery challenge</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/05/my-october-grocery-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/05/my-october-grocery-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes I feel like challenging myself in areas I’m not very good at. Like spending a small amount of money on groceries. Which is why it is a challenge! Here’s what I’m doing:
I’ve decided to try to reach the end of October and spend no more than $100 on groceries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Really good fudge</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/23/really-good-fudge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/23/really-good-fudge/</guid>
      <description>I haven’t made fudge many times before, but whenever I’ve tried, it’s turned out terribly. Either too soft and runny, or hard and crystallised. Until the day I made this recipe that I obtained in a dubious way…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grilled chicken open sandwich</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/17/grilled-chicken-open-sandwich/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/17/grilled-chicken-open-sandwich/</guid>
      <description>The other night I didn’t feel much like cooking, but didn’t want to spend money on take-aways either. I also had some chicken in the fridge that had thawed that needed to be used. What I thought would end up as a slap-together quick dinner, ended up being really yummy, so I decided to share it with you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tasty Recipe and more</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/01/tasty-recipe-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/01/tasty-recipe-and-more/</guid>
      <description>Last night we had some company (a work colleague of Ben’s) and I made a new recipe. I have a very bad habit of trying new recipes when we have people over, but this time it was definitely a winner!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My new book</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/07/my-new-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/07/my-new-book/</guid>
      <description>My lovely husband has recently bought me Julia Child’s Mastering the Art of French Cooking. I have read the preface and all the introductory remarks. Now I need to start cooking from it. It’s just been so hot that cooking anything that isn’t a hamburger patty is not very appealing, even if it is French.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our very first dinner guests, and the second lot too</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/18/our-very-first-dinner-guests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/18/our-very-first-dinner-guests/</guid>
      <description>Meeting Rick and Susanna was one of those amazing cases of providence. Both our families happened to be visiting Park Slope Presbyterian Church on the same Sunday, we got talking, we clicked, and a friendship was formed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
