<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Birthday on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/category/birthday/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Birthday on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/category/birthday/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A cool video Marica made</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2018/02/12/a-cool-video-marica-made/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2018/02/12/a-cool-video-marica-made/</guid>
      <description>Marica has been taking photos of everyday beauty (mostly during our time in NZ), editing them, and has turned them into a nice little video, which I’d like to share with you below. Proud Mama moment!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A little time travel into the past: May</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/10/10/a-little-time-travel-into-the-past-may/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/10/10/a-little-time-travel-into-the-past-may/</guid>
      <description>May brought an end to our homeschool co-op (but not to our schooling at home — that we continued until the end of June, much to the kids’ chagrin). We have a little tradition where our family takes a few friends out to a local chocolate shop where each of the kids (and moms) can choose a treat on the last day of co-op for the school year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A little time travel into the past: March</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/08/25/a-little-time-travel-into-the-past-march/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/08/25/a-little-time-travel-into-the-past-march/</guid>
      <description>There used to be a time I blogged several times a week. Then it turned into twice a week, then once a week, then once every two weeks, then… whenever I happen to write a blog post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A decade old!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/05/02/a-decade-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/05/02/a-decade-old/</guid>
      <description>In February, Marica turned 10. TEN?? How does a decade go by so fast? Marica is growing up — both taller and also growing in maturity little by little. Or maybe not so little! Her independence in the kitchen is growing, and she’s becoming quite the cook and baker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurelin’s 3rd birthday</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/08/26/laurelins-3rd-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/08/26/laurelins-3rd-birthday/</guid>
      <description>In all the bustle of the end of the school year and then summer vacation, I’ve neglected to post photos of Laurelin’s 3rd birthday.
Laurelin is now a full-blown 3-year-old and no push-over, in every sense of the word.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marica’s 9th birthday</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/03/11/maricas-9th-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/03/11/maricas-9th-birthday/</guid>
      <description>My oldest turned 9 last month. Where did the time go? I know all mothers always say that, but my oh my, they grow up fast. Gone is the little girl who liked her hair braided all pretty, and who would wear whatever her mother put out for her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Esther’s 6th birthday</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/11/27/esthers-6th-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/11/27/esthers-6th-birthday/</guid>
      <description>Esther turned 6 in November. Hard to believe, isn’t it?! Her birthday celebrations were spread out over two days — on Friday at co-op the kids sang Happy Birthday to her and she and Marica handed out cupcakes that Marica had baked (no, Mum, you’re not allowed to help me!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>She’s 8!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/03/13/beautiful-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/03/13/beautiful-snow/</guid>
      <description>Marica turned 8 in February. It’s been so fun to see her grow up a bit more over the last year! I’ve especially enjoyed seeing her sense of humor develop a bit more (starting to understand and appreciate puns and subtleties), and to see her get a little bit more mature and responsible.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
