<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NYC on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/category/nyc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in NYC on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/category/nyc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A visit from cousins</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/01/a-visit-from-cousins/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/01/a-visit-from-cousins/</guid>
      <description>The last weekend in June, we had two of Ben’s cousins, Chris and Laura Lee, visit us from Texas. That weekend was a real blast! Packed full of sight-seeing and talking and fun! Here’s some of what we did with them:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A visit from the Baneks</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/07/25/a-visit-from-the-baneks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/07/25/a-visit-from-the-baneks/</guid>
      <description>In June, we had a lovely visit from Ben’s Uncle Walter, Aunt Nelda and cousin Alexander from Texas. They were here for 4 days and we got a really good amount of sight-seeing done with them, balanced by a nice lot of calmly visiting at home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marica’s recital at Steinway Hall</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/07/18/maricas-recital-at-steinway-hall/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/07/18/maricas-recital-at-steinway-hall/</guid>
      <description>Marica and Esther started piano lessons the week after our piano arrived, and have both been enjoying it a lot, no doubt because of their excellent teacher (who also happens to be our friend!), Shannon Murphy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life in limbo</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/03/10/life-in-limbo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/03/10/life-in-limbo/</guid>
      <description>Since the last time I posted, we’ve moved into our temporary apartment for the month of March, settled into a daily routine with homeschooling in the mornings, and all of us have gotten sick. New climate, new bugs — it was to be expected!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Aliens are back in the Apple</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/02/26/the-aliens-are-back-in-the-apple/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/02/26/the-aliens-are-back-in-the-apple/</guid>
      <description>After two long, but pretty good flights, we’re back in New York. If you told me a year ago that I’d be here now, I would have laughed and said, “Yeah, right!” But here we are after a few whirlwind weeks of getting ready to move.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flights booked, date set!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/01/25/flights-booked-date-set/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/01/25/flights-booked-date-set/</guid>
      <description>We started this blog almost four years ago with the words “so we’re going overseas in a month”. They do say history repeats itself…
About six months ago, Ben got a job offer with TripAdvisor who was hoping to acquire Oyster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The start of The Roadtrip</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/06/the-start-of-the-roadtrip/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/06/the-start-of-the-roadtrip/</guid>
      <description>We had a rather stressful start to our roadtrip. I was overly optimistic (or foolish?) and hoped that everything might just fit into 6 suitcases plus a bunch of little bits and pieces. My reasoning for this was that I couldn’t see us parting with much more — I only kept the things I really wanted to and had gotten rid of more than felt comfortable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We’ve hit the road!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/04/weve-hit-the-road/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/04/weve-hit-the-road/</guid>
      <description>The last week has been a crazy whirlwind of activity. We got rid of a lot of stuff, selling some things on Craigslist, selling a bunch of things at our stoop sale and giving loads of stuff away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love poem to New York</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/31/love-poem-to-new-york/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/31/love-poem-to-new-york/</guid>
      <description>New York…
Your name invoked images, awe, presumptions
of ghetto, gangster, glamour, glitz.
Yet many will be surprised to know
I found in you much goodness and grace
just as ingrained
as the grit and grime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Packing up, cleaning out, giving away, selling…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/24/packing-up-cleaning-out-giving-away-selling/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/24/packing-up-cleaning-out-giving-away-selling/</guid>
      <description>That’s what I’m doing a lot of at the moment. And I’m seriously worried about this 4 suitcase limit. I’m just praying that our rental car can fit more than that because just our family’s clothing takes up 3 suitcases!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The beauty of a farmers’ market</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/18/the-beauty-of-a-farmers-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/18/the-beauty-of-a-farmers-market/</guid>
      <description>I love markets of any kind, but I especially like farmers’ markets. I can’t explain it — they just make me happy in the same way that flowers make me happy. On Saturdays there is a farmers’ market at Prospect Park, and we’ve been there a couple of times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Because your dog is worth it</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/14/because-your-dog-is-worth-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/14/because-your-dog-is-worth-it/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 years of friendship, and still going strong</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/10/20-years-of-friendship-and-still-going-strong/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/10/20-years-of-friendship-and-still-going-strong/</guid>
      <description>In March, my friend Lizel visited us from South Africa.
Lizel and I have been close friends since we were seven years old, despite living apart for 15 of those. As kids, we would do all sorts of crazy things like pelt the neighbour’s house with mud cookies, or knock on people’s doors and run away, or take whoopie cushions into shops and walk through the aisles making farting noises.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I met The Pioneer Woman!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/05/i-met-the-pioneer-woman/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/05/i-met-the-pioneer-woman/</guid>
      <description>I recently had the fun experience of going to a book signing. It was fun, because I got to head out by myself for an evening, and fun because I got to meet someone semi-famous. I say semi-famous because if you don’t frequent food blogs or watch food shows on TV, you’ve probably never heard of The Pioneer Woman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blessed hands, broken grammar</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/02/blessed-hands-broken-grammar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/02/blessed-hands-broken-grammar/</guid>
      <description>Saw this the other day near where we live and couldn’t help but chuckle a little. You need to read the sign in the window too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black and white, day 16</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/31/black-and-white-day-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/31/black-and-white-day-16/</guid>
      <description>Today is the last day of the black and white series. Thanks for bearing with me. I hope you’re not all now sick and tired of black and white photographs — I love them!
Today’s photos are from when Ben and Marica attended the Nutcracker ballet, December 2011.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black and white, day 13</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/28/black-and-white-day-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/28/black-and-white-day-13/</guid>
      <description>Brooklyn Bridge. October 2011.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pics from Jeremy’s bachelor party</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/14/pics-from-jeremys-bachelor-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/14/pics-from-jeremys-bachelor-party/</guid>
      <description>Last Saturday afternoon and evening, a few of Jeremy’s Philadelphia friends organized a bachelor party for him. They captured him, got in a little bit of trouble with the Philly police, and drove him blind-folded all the way to New York, where I joined them for dinner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips for new New Yorkers</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/29/tips-for-new-new-yorkers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/29/tips-for-new-new-yorkers/</guid>
      <description>It takes a lot of adjusting to live in the greatest city in the world, and there are some protocols that you should follow if you want to survive in this city. You might be a kind, generous and gentle person in the privacy of your own home, but follow these tips for how to act in public, and within a couple of weeks you will not only feel like a real New Yorker, but look like it to anyone watching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas in New York</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/27/christmas-in-new-york/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/27/christmas-in-new-york/</guid>
      <description>On Wednesday evening the kids and I met Ben at work and had a special treat of eating out (there’s a decent diner near his work) and then going to look at some of the Christmas light displays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A visit to the New York City Ballet</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/15/a-visit-to-the-new-york-city-ballet-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/15/a-visit-to-the-new-york-city-ballet-2/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend our friend Megan, who dances in the New York City Ballet, gave us two tickets to attend The Nutcracker ballet at the Lincoln Centre, and Ben took Marica to go watch her dance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting excited about Christmas</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/12/getting-excited-about-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/12/getting-excited-about-christmas/</guid>
      <description>I love the month of December here in New York — I think it’s even my favourite time of the year, even better than beautiful spring-time April. It’s cold, but everyone seems to be in good spirits (as opposed to grumpy January!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More good times</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/17/more-good-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/17/more-good-times/</guid>
      <description>Our last overnight stop on our roadtrip with my parents was at Mr &amp;amp; Mrs Brauning’s place. Mr Brauning is a pastor who came and filled our pulpit for a few months while our home congregation was vacant and the Braunings are loved by many back home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A hairy theme at the Met</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/31/a-hairy-theme-at-the-met/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/31/a-hairy-theme-at-the-met/</guid>
      <description>Every time I go to the Metropolitan Museum of Art I see something I haven’t seen before, and I certainly go back to old favourites. Recently I took some photos with a hairy theme. Some of them are so ridiculous, you’d have to be an old stodge not to even get a slight smile at the lips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some cool photos of the Guggenheim</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/27/some-cool-photos-of-the-guggenheim/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/27/some-cool-photos-of-the-guggenheim/</guid>
      <description>I don’t really care for modern art much, so I’ve never felt a deep desire to go look at what’s inside the Guggenheim museum (I can get my fill at the Met by glimpsing at the modern art section when I walk past there to get to the European sculptures).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What a great 2 weeks it has been!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/20/what-a-great-2-weeks-it-has-been/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/20/what-a-great-2-weeks-it-has-been/</guid>
      <description>As I mentioned a while back, I was anticipating a visit from a good old friend from Christchurch, Margaret Haverland. Today she is getting ready to leave, after almost 2 weeks here. What a blast it has been!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ten years on</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/11/ten-years-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/11/ten-years-on/</guid>
      <description>This week, and especially today, New Yorkers remember the day on which Muslim terrorists hijacked planes and flew into the World Trade Center towers, killing almost 3000 civilians. I’m not going to delve into the politics and debates surrounding it, but rather give you my perspective on what it’s like living here at a time like this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A pre-engagement visit</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/07/a-pre-engagement-visit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/07/a-pre-engagement-visit/</guid>
      <description>Now that you all know that Lillian and Jeremy are engaged, we can all happily say “Hooray!”. Lillian was here for a very short visit (just under 2 weeks) and flew into JFK, so we got the privilege of hosting the two of them for a few nights before they went off to Philadelphia to go get engaged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now for the black and white engagement pics</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/01/now-for-the-black-and-white-engagement-pics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/01/now-for-the-black-and-white-engagement-pics/</guid>
      <description>As I said earlier, my previous post kept freezing up because I had too many photos in there, so I instead made the first post the colour post and this one the black&amp;amp;white post. I personally often prefer black and white, so this was fun for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The last one bites the dust</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/01/the-last-one-bites-the-dust/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/01/the-last-one-bites-the-dust/</guid>
      <description>But that makes it sound like it’s a bad thing when it is indeed a very happy thing — the last of 8 children getting married. Yes, that’s right, Ben’s little sister, Lillian, is engaged to be married to a certain Mr Jeremy Fisher, uh, I mean Mr Jeremy L Eshelman!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We survived Irene</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/28/we-survived-irene/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/28/we-survived-irene/</guid>
      <description>We’re posting this from a rescue boat (with free wireless internet) that lifted us from the roof of our flooded apartment early this morning. We’re sipping complimentary cocktails as we traverse the streets by boat, witnessing how New York has turned into a lake full of broken branches and leaves, a veritable Venice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Irene</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/27/hurricane-irene/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/27/hurricane-irene/</guid>
      <description>Most of you are probably aware that Hurricane Irene is currently moving up the East Coast of the States, and will most likely pass through, or very close to New York City. For those of you who are interested, we are not in an area likely to flood, and we don’t foresee needing to evacuate at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Okay, so it’s just a teensy bit hot here</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/23/okay-so-its-just-a-teensy-bit-hot-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/23/okay-so-its-just-a-teensy-bit-hot-here/</guid>
      <description>You’ve probably heard about the heat wave that has hit us here in the States. It’s a steaming sauna — free! We seem to be spending time here when all the records strike. Record snow, record heat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 4th of July!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/08/the-4th-of-july-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/08/the-4th-of-july-2/</guid>
      <description>This year the 4th of July fell on a Monday so we were very happy that Ben got the day off. We spent a relaxing morning at home and in the afternoon went to Manhattan to view the Macy’s 4th of July fireworks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>White Collar in Clinton Hill!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/07/white-collar-in-clinton-hill/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/07/white-collar-in-clinton-hill/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday and today we’ve had film crews on our street and surrounding neighborhood shooting for the TV series WhiteCollar. It’s been really cool to see a little glimpse of what goes into a production like this — SO many trucks and people doing all sorts of things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A garden grows in Brooklyn</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/06/a-garden-grows-in-brooklyn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/06/a-garden-grows-in-brooklyn/</guid>
      <description>We are among the few privileged New Yorkers who have our own private backyard. Private as in access (no one else uses our backyard), not private in the sense that nobody can see us, because we certainly have plenty of window eyes all around!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo fun</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/02/photo-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/02/photo-fun/</guid>
      <description>The outside of our house at the back is painted in a vivid blue. I’ve planted some zinnias in pots, and the colour contrast is great. I had some fun taking photos of a couple of flowers the other day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shenanigans with Sharon</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/01/shenanigans-with-sharon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/01/shenanigans-with-sharon/</guid>
      <description>Ben’s cousin Sharon visited us over Memorial Weekend, and we had a lot of fun packing in as much sight-seeing as was practical! Here is some photographic evidence.
We walked the Brooklyn Bridge,
sat on cool seats on the way to the Ferry terminal,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer is here!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/16/summer-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/16/summer-is-here/</guid>
      <description>And we’ve well and truly been out and about enjoying it. We’ve only had two very hot days and for the rest of the time it has been pretty much perfect weather (25 - 30 C).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Ground Zero looks like these days</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/07/what-ground-zero-looks-like-these-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/07/what-ground-zero-looks-like-these-days/</guid>
      <description>I don’t think there would be anyone who doesn’t remember the shock they felt at the news of the September 11 attacks. Since then, almost ten years have passed, and much has changed. Ground Zero is now a bustling construction site instead of a heap of rubble.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did I tell you that Esther is now walking?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/03/did-i-tell-you-that-esther-is-now-walking/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/03/did-i-tell-you-that-esther-is-now-walking/</guid>
      <description>Well, she certainly is. And she’s fast too. She’s loving the new independence and so am I. Playgrounds are much more fun, despite the scratched knees she inevitably gets!
Walking down Fulton Street. That big tower in the background under construction is the new One World Trade Center.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who sped up time?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/28/who-sped-up-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/28/who-sped-up-time/</guid>
      <description>How is it possible that we have been in New York City for a year already? Yes, everyone, it’s been a YEAR! When we arrived a year ago, I must admit that I viewed our ‘adventure’ with some trepidation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful Brooklyn Botanic Garden</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/21/beautiful-brooklyn-botanic-garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/21/beautiful-brooklyn-botanic-garden/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weeks ago, we went to the Brooklyn Botanic Garden with our friends Julie and Abby Murphy and Damaris and her 2 cute kids, Elijah and Sophia.
The gardens were amazingly beautiful and dressed in their Spring finest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brooklyn Bridge!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/14/brooklyn-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/14/brooklyn-bridge/</guid>
      <description>When Ben’s dad was here back in April we got a fair bit of sight-seeing done, which even included some things I hadn’t seen or done before, which was pretty exciting. One of those things was walking the Brooklyn Bridge, which is just one of those things you have to do in New York City.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where to find me</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/07/where-to-find-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/07/where-to-find-me/</guid>
      <description>… in a subway station.
Or my initials, at least. :-)
The real place you’ll find me in a subway station is as far away from the tracks as possible, holding onto my kids pretty well!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some other New York sights (and eats) with Hannah and Eva</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/05/some-other-new-york-sights-and-eats-with-hannah-and-eva/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/05/some-other-new-york-sights-and-eats-with-hannah-and-eva/</guid>
      <description>As you can tell, I’m waaay behind on sight-seeing posts! When Hannah and Eva were here way back in March, we did quite a few fun things I haven’t shared here yet, so here’s a photo post of some of the things we did and ate!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musings on New York, the weather, and teeth.</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/26/musings-on-new-york-the-weather-and-teeth/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/26/musings-on-new-york-the-weather-and-teeth/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been sharing a lot of photos and telling you about stuff we’ve seen and experienced lately (and there’s a lot more to come!), but I thought I’d just give you a little update on how we’re all doing, as well as some related thoughts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The importance of a decimal point</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/21/the-importance-of-a-decimal-point/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/21/the-importance-of-a-decimal-point/</guid>
      <description>You might not think it, but it can make quite a big difference!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Up close and personal with Lady Liberty</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/16/up-close-and-personal-with-lady-liberty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/16/up-close-and-personal-with-lady-liberty/</guid>
      <description>The New Colossus By Emma Lazarus, 1883
Not like the brazen giant of Greek fame,
With conquering limbs astride from land to land;
Here at our sea-washed, sunset gates shall stand
A mighty woman with a torch, whose flame</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t be late for class!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/13/dont-be-late-for-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/13/dont-be-late-for-class/</guid>
      <description>Or else…
We saw this on the subway to church the other day and I couldn’t help it — I just had to take a picture! Sometimes graffiti is hilarious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A too-short visit to The Met</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/06/a-too-short-visit-to-the-met/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/06/a-too-short-visit-to-the-met/</guid>
      <description>When Hannah and Eva were here, we went to the Met the same day we went to the Cloisters. The Met really deserves a day or two to itself, and I definitely plan to go back — the two or so hours we had there were only enough to see a few musical instruments and about 3/4 of the European Painters section.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Would you?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/05/would-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/05/would-you/</guid>
      <description>Would you feel confident using a dry cleaner with a name like this? It cracks me up every time I see it!
I took the photo at night, so excuse the poor lighting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting The Cloisters</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/30/revisiting-the-cloisters/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/30/revisiting-the-cloisters/</guid>
      <description>When Ben’s cousins, Hannah and Eva, were here visiting with us, the three of us took a trip up into Manhattan to see The Cloisters and The Met (The Met will be in another post!).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring is knocking on Winter’s door!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/22/spring-is-knocking-on-winters-door/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/22/spring-is-knocking-on-winters-door/</guid>
      <description>The crocuses are out! And some mini irises too. I hope to see some daffodils soon!
We spotted these cuties in Central Park last Saturday.
Aren’t these just so gorgeous? These flowers we saw in Fort Tryon Park near The Cloisters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cute kids’ photos</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/28/cute-kids-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/28/cute-kids-photos/</guid>
      <description>While Ben and I were having a blast in the Caribbean, our kids were having a blast at the Murphys’ place. Julie was kind enough to send me some pictures, so I’ll share them here for you to enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marica is 4!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/16/marica-is-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/16/marica-is-4/</guid>
      <description>On Saturday, Marica turned 4 years old. I find that hard to believe that it’s already been 4 years since she was born. And at the same time it feels as if she’s been my big girl forever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowsational</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/31/snowsational/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/31/snowsational/</guid>
      <description>Snow is beautiful. And fun. It does get messy, and it keeps you indoors more than you’d like, but those are trifles compared to the six foot high piles of white-or-grey frozen stuff all over the streets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Have we mentioned it’s been cold?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/24/have-we-mentioned-its-been-cold/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/24/have-we-mentioned-its-been-cold/</guid>
      <description>Our first blizzard in New York was a very exciting event. Everything was beautiful and white and we were on holiday. The second one was not so exciting, apart from the fact that it kept Lillian with us for a day longer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A visit to Wonderland</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/21/a-visit-to-wonderland/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/21/a-visit-to-wonderland/</guid>
      <description>Last Friday, a few friends from church met up at Alice’s Tea Cup with their daughters for a fun, girly time of drinking tea, eating good food and some good conversation.
Alice’s Tea Cup is definitely a girly tea room, decorated in pretty colours with cool chandeliers and fairy wings on the walls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The penny queen</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/11/the-penny-queen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/11/the-penny-queen/</guid>
      <description>Marica must have either Dutch or Jewish blood in her. She’s always scouting to find coins on the ground, and the number she has picked up is astounding. Here’s one day’s laundromat loot: a quarter and a penny.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sight-seeing with Lillian</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/03/sight-seeing-with-lillian/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/03/sight-seeing-with-lillian/</guid>
      <description>In the few weeks that Lillian has been here we’ve done all sorts of things like Christmas baking, movie watching, eating good food and talking, but we’ve also done some sight-seeing. You can’t leave that out when you’re in New York, even if the weather is freezing!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our first New York Christmas</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/30/our-first-new-york-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/30/our-first-new-york-christmas/</guid>
      <description>This year was the first year our little family did not celebrate Christmas with grandparents. I was going to say that we didn’t celebrate with any extended family, but we do have Lillian here, so we’re not entirely family-less!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Feet of snow!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/27/2-feet-of-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/27/2-feet-of-snow/</guid>
      <description>We have had a great big snow storm that started yesterday and continued through the night. We’re loving it big time! We have a snow drift that goes almost to the top of our fence in the back yard, and this morning when I went outside on the side walk I had snow up to my mid thighs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let it snow, let it snow, let it snow!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/27/let-it-snow-let-it-snow-let-it-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/27/let-it-snow-let-it-snow-let-it-snow/</guid>
      <description>It started snowing on Sunday morning and continued snowing through the night. This morning we woke up to almost 2 feet of snow and a totally transformed neighborhood.
This is what it looked like trying to get out of our metal gate:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New York Christmas</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/23/a-new-york-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/23/a-new-york-christmas/</guid>
      <description>I thought I might share a few New York-ish Christmas moments with you. The city gets decorated quite a lot and there are lights and Christmas trees all over the place. Ben and Lillian and Marica went and had a look at some of the famous Christmas light displays down 5th Avenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cloisters</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/13/the-cloisters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/13/the-cloisters/</guid>
      <description>Some of you have no doubt heard of The Metropolitan Museum of Art, or “The Met”, here in New York City. It’s a massive museum of art and culture, along Museum Mile on the east side of Central Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/22/thanksgiving/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/22/thanksgiving/</guid>
      <description>This week on Thursday it is Thanksgiving. I think it must be my favourite American holiday! A life that is full of thanksgiving is a happy one, no matter what the circumstances, and what can be better than once a year celebrating the good things God has given us with a great big feast?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enjoying Fall</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/15/enjoying-fall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/15/enjoying-fall/</guid>
      <description>Two weekends ago we visited friends from church for lunch who recently got married, Franco and Neli. Franco grew up in NYC and Neli is from Peru. They’re a really lovely couple!
Franco and Neli live in a tall apartment building a block away from Central Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Silly Billy Elliot</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/12/silly-billy-elliot/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/12/silly-billy-elliot/</guid>
      <description>Last Friday, Franci and I went to a Broadway show for the first time: Billy Elliot the Musical at the Imperial Theatre. Here’s a photo we took just before we went in:
It was quite the experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Well there you go!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/11/well-there-you-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/11/well-there-you-go/</guid>
      <description>We saw this billboard with graffiti on on our way home from the Bronx Zoo and I just had to take a picture. What a great commentary on how our society thinks — “it’s all about you”, never mind others, just go ahead and bless yourself!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A little summary</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/05/a-little-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/05/a-little-summary/</guid>
      <description>We’ve been in New York City for just a little over 5 months now. I can hardly believe it’s been that long, and on the other hand it feels much longer! I thought I’d use this post to update you in a bit more detail about how we’re doing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playing tourist again: Bronx Zoo</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/02/playing-tourist-again-bronx-zoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/02/playing-tourist-again-bronx-zoo/</guid>
      <description>A couple of Saturdays ago we bundled up and visited the Bronx Zoo. It is the biggest metropolitan zoo in the world, and we certainly didn’t see all of it in the day we were there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This is the way we wash our clothes…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/26/this-is-the-way-we-wash-our-clothes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/26/this-is-the-way-we-wash-our-clothes/</guid>
      <description>wash our clothes, wash our clothes. This is the way we wash our clothes, living in New York City!
At our apartment, we don’t have facilities to do washing other than by hand. In fact, our rental contract specifies that we are not allowed to have a washing machine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hoyt Street, Brooklyn</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/21/hoyt-street-brooklyn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/21/hoyt-street-brooklyn/</guid>
      <description>Hoyt is a fairly well-established name here in New York. Brooklyn even has a Hoyt Street, and there are two subway stations along it. It’s kinda fun to see our name popping up here and there!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playing tourist again: Little Italy</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/20/playing-tourist-again-little-italy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/20/playing-tourist-again-little-italy/</guid>
      <description>Stepping into Little Italy is like being overseas for a little while. The streets (Mulberry Street in particular) is decorated in Italian colours — red, green and white.
The place is littered with restaurants, and pizza shops and places selling “Italian Specialties” like meats, breads and desserts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playing tourist again: Chinatown</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/01/playing-tourist-again-chinatown/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/01/playing-tourist-again-chinatown/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weekends ago we visited Chinatown and Little Italy. I took so many photos that day that I cannot possibly fit them all into one post, so this one will be about Chinatown. Little Italy will follow eventually.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Firefly</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/30/little-firefly/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/30/little-firefly/</guid>
      <description>A (cheesy) little poem I wrote one very hot night sitting outside in my Brooklyn backyard.
—————————————————————————————————————————————-
Little firefly,
What are you doing here?
Don’t you belong
in open fields
by sliding streams
under uninterrupted skies?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet our church in New York</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/22/meet-our-church-in-new-york/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/22/meet-our-church-in-new-york/</guid>
      <description>Here in New York we attend a URCNA (United Reformed Church of North America) congregation that meets in lower Manhattan near Ground Zero, called Messiah’s Reformed Fellowship (MeRF for short).
MeRF started as a response to the September 11 terrorist attacks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Today I did a really crazy thing…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/21/crazy-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/21/crazy-thing/</guid>
      <description>I think I made some angels work overtime today. I’ve just returned from a shoe shopping experience in a great big shoe store my mother-in-law recommended. The shopping experience was quite fun, but that wasn’t the crazy part.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tornado in Brooklyn</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/18/tornado-in-brooklyn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/18/tornado-in-brooklyn/</guid>
      <description>While Christchurch is still having earthquakes, here in Brooklyn we had our very own tornado (or super-severe storm — the weather service isn’t sure which). The winds and rain whipped up all of a sudden, picked up huge branches and even trees and threw them across the streets, and then twenty minutes later it was dead calm again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who said there’s no such thing as a free lunch?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/15/free-lunch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/15/free-lunch/</guid>
      <description>Autumn (or “fall” as it is called here) has come and school has started up again after a good hot summer. It’s been a full summer for us and we’re glad for things to start settling a bit, not to mention glad for a hint of some cooler weather.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two nights &#43; 14 people &#43; 1 (small) New York apartment = Lots of fun!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/14/two-nights/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/14/two-nights/</guid>
      <description>It’s really hard to believe that it’s almost been two weeks since the van Wichens descended on our place. For those who don’t know, Laurel is Ben’s oldest sister and their family is touring the States for 10 weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A brief history of Hoyt</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/08/a-brief-history-of-hoyt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/08/a-brief-history-of-hoyt/</guid>
      <description>As far as I know, not many Hoyts in my extended family are into family history. I’m not exactly either, but it is interesting when you run across a bit of good old ancestry (actually, an old friend from Masterton put me onto most of this stuff).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tasty Recipe and more</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/01/tasty-recipe-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/01/tasty-recipe-and-more/</guid>
      <description>Last night we had some company (a work colleague of Ben’s) and I made a new recipe. I have a very bad habit of trying new recipes when we have people over, but this time it was definitely a winner!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 4th of July</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/15/the-4th-of-july/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/15/the-4th-of-july/</guid>
      <description>Earlier this month, on the 4th of July, the United States of America celebrated Independence Day. It’s been 234 years since America declared independence from Great Britain, and for the average American England is now just some far away place where people talk funny.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend touristy fun</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/30/weekend-touristy-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/30/weekend-touristy-fun/</guid>
      <description>Ben has already told you that we went to Staten (pronounced Statten, not State-in) Island on Saturday. I have some cool photos to share of our trip there and back, and later in the week I’ll tell and show you all about the stuff we saw in the Financial District.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Statue of Liberty</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/28/the-statue-of-liberty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/28/the-statue-of-liberty/</guid>
      <description>Today we took the Staten Island Ferry from the southern tip of Manhattan to the north-most point on Staten Island (and back, of course). For a long time the ferry cost only 25 cents for a return trip, then it went up to 50 cents in 1990.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ye olde green cards</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/23/ye-olde-green-cards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/23/ye-olde-green-cards/</guid>
      <description>I am happy to report that Marica, Esther and I are now the proud owners of U.S. green cards. (Not just the temporary paperwork, but the Real Thing.) The cards arrived in the mail yesterday, so we are now officially Permanent Residents of the United States of America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quirky New York</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/10/quirky-new-york/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/10/quirky-new-york/</guid>
      <description>So far we’ve noticed a few quirky things here in New York.
For instance, the light switches are the other way around than in NZ - up is on and down is off. I still get confused.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Showing you around (a photo post)</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/07/showing-you-around/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/07/showing-you-around/</guid>
      <description>First off, if you have dail-up, I apologise. This post is going to be laden with photos!
The other day, Ben caught Marica on camera looking out the window of our 5th floor apartment:
The nice building across the road is the HSBC bank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apartment hunting</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/05/apartment-hunting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/05/apartment-hunting/</guid>
      <description>There is not a whole lot to tell you about yet, but finding an apartment in NYC is hard work. Especially without the ease of a car! On Wednesday I packed up the kids and we set of to look at some apartments in Prospect Heights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The city that never sleeps</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/05/31/the-city-that-never-sleeps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/05/31/the-city-that-never-sleeps/</guid>
      <description>I can’t believe we’ve only been in NYC for 4 nights — it feels much longer. I’m sure that this is because we haven’t exactly slept very well. Jet lag aside, we’ve had some interesting night-time sound experiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye Christchurch, Hello New York</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/05/28/goodbye-christchurch-hello-new-york/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/05/28/goodbye-christchurch-hello-new-york/</guid>
      <description>It’s been a hectic last few days! The days leading up to our departure were filled with last-minute packing and cleaning (thanks to everyone who helped!) and lots of goodbyes. I hate goodbyes, but as far as they go, the ones we had were good byes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Big Apple</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/05/24/the-big-apple/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/05/24/the-big-apple/</guid>
      <description>Why is New York City called The Big Apple?
It’s actually one of those old terms that has a sketchy history. Wikipedia tells me it was first used as a term for New York in 1921 by John J Fitz Gerald in a horce-racing context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What you notice when you’re going to NYC</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/05/04/what-you-notice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/05/04/what-you-notice/</guid>
      <description>It’s amazing what you notice about a place you’ve lived in for ages when you’re planning a trip overseas. For one thing, Christchurch has a lot of center-city apartments — never noticed ‘em before, but now they’re everywhere.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
