<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Travelling on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/category/travelling/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Travelling on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/category/travelling/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A little time travel into the past: April</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/09/24/a-little-time-travel-into-the-past-april/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/09/24/a-little-time-travel-into-the-past-april/</guid>
      <description>In April, we had a wonderful visit from my parents. It was great to spend time together again — especially for the grandkids to have their grandparents around! Spring really was a great time for a visit — not too hot and not too cold, and it’s so beautiful with all the blossoms and flowers out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip ’16: Hoyt Reunion</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/09/30/roadtrip-16-hoyt-reunion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/09/30/roadtrip-16-hoyt-reunion/</guid>
      <description>After our great camping experience, we drove down to Columbia, SC, to spend the night and visit Ben’s parents’ old church where we got to meet people who knew them 40 years ago, which was pretty neat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip ’16: Monticello</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/09/09/roadtrip-16-monticello/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/09/09/roadtrip-16-monticello/</guid>
      <description>This year was the happy year where a US Hoyt reunion took place. This time was again in Georgia, so back in June we took a two and a half week long roadtrip down south. It worked out well that Ben happened to be between jobs at that point so he took 3 weeks off, which was so great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to New Zealand, part 4</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/02/19/visit-to-new-zealand-part-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/02/19/visit-to-new-zealand-part-4/</guid>
      <description>A couple of days after Christmas Ben returned to the US, and the girls and I stayed in NZ for another 3 (full, but great) weeks. We met up with lots of family and friends and had such a great time that for the most part I forgot to take my camera along.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to New Zealand, part 2</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/02/05/visit-to-new-zealand-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/02/05/visit-to-new-zealand-part-2/</guid>
      <description>A couple of days after we arrived, we headed out of town to Mt Hutt in the Southern Alps for a Hoyt reunion. I think it had been the first time in almost 6 years that everyone were together again — Mum &amp;amp; Dad, all 8 siblings, plus spouses and kids — and it was fantastic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips on travelling long-haul with little kids</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/12/11/tips-on-travelling-long-haul-with-little-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/12/11/tips-on-travelling-long-haul-with-little-kids/</guid>
      <description>As we prepare to take a trip back to NZ for Christmas, I’m looking back at this post again (originally posted in March 2012) to refresh my memory on what’s useful to take and what to do to make life easier when travelling long haul with kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary of summer, part 4</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/09/25/summary-of-summer-part-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/09/25/summary-of-summer-part-4/</guid>
      <description>So, last week I mentioned how we traveled to Indiana for cousin Sharon’s and Vijo’s wedding in August. Despite the 13 hour trip each way, we were so happy that we could go and also that we could spend time with other Hoyt family members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We’re back</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/08/04/were-back-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/08/04/were-back-3/</guid>
      <description>We’ve arrived safely back in Christchurch, thanks to God. And our home really feels like home already, so thanks everyone for your welcome and your help!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Special time with Pappa</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/24/special-time-with-pappa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/24/special-time-with-pappa/</guid>
      <description>I think the Pennsylvanian countryside is just so beautiful. It seems very peaceful to me, perhaps because I’m usually on holiday when I’m there.
When we took Lizel there when she visited, Marica stayed with dear friends who took her to a ballet concert, so Esther got to be the only child for a weekend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 years of friendship, and still going strong</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/10/20-years-of-friendship-and-still-going-strong/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/10/20-years-of-friendship-and-still-going-strong/</guid>
      <description>In March, my friend Lizel visited us from South Africa.
Lizel and I have been close friends since we were seven years old, despite living apart for 15 of those. As kids, we would do all sorts of crazy things like pelt the neighbour’s house with mud cookies, or knock on people’s doors and run away, or take whoopie cushions into shops and walk through the aisles making farting noises.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
