<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Being tourists on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/category/being-tourists/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Being tourists on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/category/being-tourists/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A little time travel into the past: June</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/10/27/a-little-time-travel-into-the-past-june/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/10/27/a-little-time-travel-into-the-past-june/</guid>
      <description>In early June, Marica and Esther performed and did really well at their annual piano recital. They both played solo pieces and also performed a duet. I was a proud mama!
The highlight of June was a visit from my sister Angelique and nephew Tyson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A little time travel into the past: April</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/09/24/a-little-time-travel-into-the-past-april/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/09/24/a-little-time-travel-into-the-past-april/</guid>
      <description>In April, we had a wonderful visit from my parents. It was great to spend time together again — especially for the grandkids to have their grandparents around! Spring really was a great time for a visit — not too hot and not too cold, and it’s so beautiful with all the blossoms and flowers out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip ’16: Six Flags</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/11/04/roadtrip-16-six-flags/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/11/04/roadtrip-16-six-flags/</guid>
      <description>For the last leg of our roadtrip home, we made a stop at Six Flags in the south of New Jersey. They have a program called Read To Succeed where the kids have to read a total of 600 hours in the year to get free tickets to Six Flags.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip ’16: Camping in TN</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/09/23/roadtrip-16-camping-in-tn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/09/23/roadtrip-16-camping-in-tn/</guid>
      <description>After our visit to Monticello we started the drive down to Cherokee National Forest in east Tennessee where we planned on camping for a couple of nights. We started off in the rain and the rain just got heavier and heavier, and there were predictions for a huge storm to pass over where we were going to camp that night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips on travelling long-haul with little kids</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/12/11/tips-on-travelling-long-haul-with-little-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/12/11/tips-on-travelling-long-haul-with-little-kids/</guid>
      <description>As we prepare to take a trip back to NZ for Christmas, I’m looking back at this post again (originally posted in March 2012) to refresh my memory on what’s useful to take and what to do to make life easier when travelling long haul with kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s been a decade</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/02/13/its-been-a-decade/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/02/13/its-been-a-decade/</guid>
      <description>Like I said last week, it’s been cold here! However, Ben and I did have a blessed little escape from the cold back in January for 3 nights, when we eloped to Jamaica while my parents looked after our kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A visit from cousins</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/01/a-visit-from-cousins/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/01/a-visit-from-cousins/</guid>
      <description>The last weekend in June, we had two of Ben’s cousins, Chris and Laura Lee, visit us from Texas. That weekend was a real blast! Packed full of sight-seeing and talking and fun! Here’s some of what we did with them:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A visit from the Baneks</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/07/25/a-visit-from-the-baneks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/07/25/a-visit-from-the-baneks/</guid>
      <description>In June, we had a lovely visit from Ben’s Uncle Walter, Aunt Nelda and cousin Alexander from Texas. They were here for 4 days and we got a really good amount of sight-seeing done with them, balanced by a nice lot of calmly visiting at home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip: Los Angeles</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/11/05/roadtrip-los-angeles/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/11/05/roadtrip-los-angeles/</guid>
      <description>It’s really happened! This is my last post of our roadtrip, only 16 months after the event. Shocking. Oh well, a beautiful baby girl has been added to our family since then and life’s been busy — that’s the way it is sometimes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yosemite!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/08/09/yosemite/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/08/09/yosemite/</guid>
      <description>Yo’s Mite. That’s how I always thought you pronounced Yosemite (having only ever seen it written). Now I know better. Just think Yo’s Cemetery without the ‘r’ and you’re set. :-)
One of the many things I love about the States is how varied the scenery is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip: Lone Pine</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/04/09/roadtrip-lone-pine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/04/09/roadtrip-lone-pine/</guid>
      <description>The next stop couldn’t have been more different from Las Vegas. Tranquil, rural, isolated, pretty much nobody around, right in nature, and no electricity! We stayed the night in a little cabin/tent outside a small town called Lone Pine, between the Death Valley and the Sierra Nevada Mountains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip: Las Vegas</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/03/19/roadtrip-las-vegas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/03/19/roadtrip-las-vegas/</guid>
      <description>I know there are people who love Vegas. I find this difficult to understand because we didn’t enjoy it at all! It was like a sleazy version of Times Square, but it had good, cheap accommodation that was en route to our next destination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Continuing the roadtrip posts: A visit to Phoenix</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/03/03/continuing-the-roadtrip-posts-a-visit-to-phoenix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/03/03/continuing-the-roadtrip-posts-a-visit-to-phoenix/</guid>
      <description>I know that I stopped our roadtrip posts rather abruptly last year, and for good reason, but I really do want to finish the posts before the baby arrives. That equates to six more posts over the next 3 months — surely I could do that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Grand Canyon</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/11/22/the-grand-canyon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/11/22/the-grand-canyon/</guid>
      <description>No tourist’s visit to the west of the U.S. is complete without a stop at the Grand Canyon, and we were no exception. We stayed in a little village (consisting mostly of the motel and gift shop) called Cameron for a couple of nights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Driving through Monument Valley</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/11/07/driving-through-monument-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/11/07/driving-through-monument-valley/</guid>
      <description>After our time in Moab and Arches National Park, we traveled south to the Grand Canyon. What we didn’t realise was that our road would take us right through Monument Valley, a beautiful and dramatic piece of creation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A visit to Moab and Arches National Park</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/10/25/a-visit-to-moab-and-arches-national-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/10/25/a-visit-to-moab-and-arches-national-park/</guid>
      <description>One of the scenic highlights of our roadtrip was the state of Utah, where we went to Arches National Park, and drove through Monument Valley on our way to the Grand Canyon. We both loved the Grand Canyon (post still coming!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garden of the Gods at sunrise</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/10/09/garden-of-the-gods-at-sunrise/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/10/09/garden-of-the-gods-at-sunrise/</guid>
      <description>When we were visiting the Boonzaaijers’ in Colorado Springs, I decided to get up early one morning to go and take some photos of the Garden of the Gods. I had heard that it was particularly beautiful at sunrise, so I got up at 5am and headed on down there, just as the sky was changing colour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manitou Cliff Dwellings</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/09/11/manitou-cliff-dwellings/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/09/11/manitou-cliff-dwellings/</guid>
      <description>After the Tschetter reunion we stopped at the Manitou cliff dwellings museum on our way to visit Ben’s cousin Erica and her family in Colorado Springs.
Call me thick, but I only just realised after reading wikipedia that the cliff dwellings are not original, but instead have been relocated to their current location.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photoless reporting is not quite my style</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/07/21/photoless-reporting-is-not-quite-my-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/07/21/photoless-reporting-is-not-quite-my-style/</guid>
      <description>I’m finding it hard to keep up the blogging while we’re on the road, as you’ve no doubt realised! Not that it’s going to stop me trying. I’ll start by giving a quick run down of what happened after the Hoyt reunion up to the point where I’ve got photos again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Knoxville Farmers’ Market</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/18/the-knoxville-farmers-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/18/the-knoxville-farmers-market/</guid>
      <description>Today is our second day at the Hoyt reunion in Georgia. Since I’ve last blogged we’ve visited the Holders in Knoxville, and some friends in Atlanta. I hope to blog about that soon, but I need to catch up with sharing some of the things we did in Knoxville first!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Roadtrip, stop 2</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/10/the-roadtrip-stop-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/10/the-roadtrip-stop-2/</guid>
      <description>After our first stop in Connecticut with the Snoeks, we headed down to Philadelphia where we stayed with Lillian and Jeremy and visited with several friends over the course of the weekend.
On the way to Lillian and Jeremy we stopped and Sam and Emily Perez’s home, friends from our church in New York.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 years of friendship, and still going strong</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/10/20-years-of-friendship-and-still-going-strong/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/10/20-years-of-friendship-and-still-going-strong/</guid>
      <description>In March, my friend Lizel visited us from South Africa.
Lizel and I have been close friends since we were seven years old, despite living apart for 15 of those. As kids, we would do all sorts of crazy things like pelt the neighbour’s house with mud cookies, or knock on people’s doors and run away, or take whoopie cushions into shops and walk through the aisles making farting noises.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A few post-earthquake photos</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/22/a-few-post-earthquake-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/22/a-few-post-earthquake-photos/</guid>
      <description>This is my last post about my trip to Christchurch in January. It’s about time, I think! This post is largely for our US readers who have expressed interest in the earthquake side of things back home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas in New York</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/27/christmas-in-new-york/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/27/christmas-in-new-york/</guid>
      <description>On Wednesday evening the kids and I met Ben at work and had a special treat of eating out (there’s a decent diner near his work) and then going to look at some of the Christmas light displays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A visit to the New York City Ballet</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/15/a-visit-to-the-new-york-city-ballet-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/15/a-visit-to-the-new-york-city-ballet-2/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend our friend Megan, who dances in the New York City Ballet, gave us two tickets to attend The Nutcracker ballet at the Lincoln Centre, and Ben took Marica to go watch her dance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More good times</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/17/more-good-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/17/more-good-times/</guid>
      <description>Our last overnight stop on our roadtrip with my parents was at Mr &amp;amp; Mrs Brauning’s place. Mr Brauning is a pastor who came and filled our pulpit for a few months while our home congregation was vacant and the Braunings are loved by many back home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stop 3 on the trip</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/14/stop-3-on-the-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/14/stop-3-on-the-trip/</guid>
      <description>Just a little note: I’m not blogging real-time. I think I might have blogged about something on the same day it happened about twice in the whole time I’ve had this blog. I just don’t have the luxury of lots of time to be able to do that!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magnificent Niagara Falls</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/10/magnificent-niagara-falls/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/10/magnificent-niagara-falls/</guid>
      <description>After our 3 nights in the Adirondack mountains, we drove to Niagara Falls. The scenery on the way was beautiful!
Crossing the border into Canada.
We arrived on a cold, windy, overcast afternoon, but didn’t know whether the weather would clear up over the weekend, so decided to brave it and go look at the falls regardless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October, a wonderful month with family</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/03/october-a-wonderful-month-with-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/03/october-a-wonderful-month-with-family/</guid>
      <description>For most of the month of October we had my parents visiting with us, and we had a very good time together.
The highlight of their time here was probably our road trip that we took to the Adirondack mountains, Niagara Falls, Toronto and Pennsylvania to visit our friends the Tysons and the Braunings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A hairy theme at the Met</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/31/a-hairy-theme-at-the-met/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/31/a-hairy-theme-at-the-met/</guid>
      <description>Every time I go to the Metropolitan Museum of Art I see something I haven’t seen before, and I certainly go back to old favourites. Recently I took some photos with a hairy theme. Some of them are so ridiculous, you’d have to be an old stodge not to even get a slight smile at the lips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some cool photos of the Guggenheim</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/27/some-cool-photos-of-the-guggenheim/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/27/some-cool-photos-of-the-guggenheim/</guid>
      <description>I don’t really care for modern art much, so I’ve never felt a deep desire to go look at what’s inside the Guggenheim museum (I can get my fill at the Met by glimpsing at the modern art section when I walk past there to get to the European sculptures).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accidental coolness</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/13/accidental-coolness/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/13/accidental-coolness/</guid>
      <description>When I was driving through Philly with Margaret, I was just happily snapping pictures of stuff out of the car while we were driving. I happened to take this picture of a city centre sculpture and when I went through the photos afterwards I saw how perfectly (total fluke) the moon was aligned with this thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road trip report, Days 5 and 6</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/06/road-trip-report-days-5-and-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/06/road-trip-report-days-5-and-6/</guid>
      <description>We left Washington D.C. on a Friday afternoon and drove up to Baltimore. I’m not sure if we saw the wrong side of Baltimore or what, but neither of us were particularly impressed. I guess that wasn’t helped by a fire drill going on at the Art Museum as soon as we walked in, and nobody knowing what was going on, including the staff, which meant we just walked straight back out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road trip report, Day 4</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/30/road-trip-report-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/30/road-trip-report-day-4/</guid>
      <description>So you’re all dying to hear how we became chummy with the President, right? Well, it happened like this: we were walking outside the fence of his big fancy house, admiring the well kept garden and lawns, all lonesome and deserted when suddenly he jumped out of the bushes and shouted “BOO!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road trip report, Day 3</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/26/road-trip-report-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/26/road-trip-report-day-3/</guid>
      <description>Just a little note: I’ve switched to uploading smaller photos on here, to make things faster for me while editing blog posts, and hopefully also for you as subscribers having to download the posts. As far as I can tell the quality is still pretty good, but let me know what you think.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road trip report, Day 1 and 2</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/24/road-trip-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/24/road-trip-report/</guid>
      <description>So like I said, Margaret took me and the girls on a week-long road trip (thanks, Gary!) and boy did we have fun! There was a good amount of banter and hilarity and also some really good conversations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What a great 2 weeks it has been!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/20/what-a-great-2-weeks-it-has-been/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/20/what-a-great-2-weeks-it-has-been/</guid>
      <description>As I mentioned a while back, I was anticipating a visit from a good old friend from Christchurch, Margaret Haverland. Today she is getting ready to leave, after almost 2 weeks here. What a blast it has been!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A pre-engagement visit</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/07/a-pre-engagement-visit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/07/a-pre-engagement-visit/</guid>
      <description>Now that you all know that Lillian and Jeremy are engaged, we can all happily say “Hooray!”. Lillian was here for a very short visit (just under 2 weeks) and flew into JFK, so we got the privilege of hosting the two of them for a few nights before they went off to Philadelphia to go get engaged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turning 30</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/08/turning-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/08/turning-30/</guid>
      <description>Last Thursday I (Ben) turned 30, and an otherwise ordinary workday was turned into Something Special by my lovely wife. She’d been being secretive about something for a few weeks, so I guessed something was going to happen, but I had no idea what.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lorraine, the not-so Divine</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/20/lorraine-the-not-so-divine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/20/lorraine-the-not-so-divine/</guid>
      <description>Saw this old building on our way to Jeremy’s place in Philadelphia, and couldn’t help noticing the irony.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to Mr. J</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/15/visit-to-mr-j/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/15/visit-to-mr-j/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weekends ago, we visited our good friend, Jeremy, in Philadelphia.
What a blast — we did some sight-seeing, but also my favourite pastime: having good discussions over good food.
There was of course also an appropriate amount of teasing which Jeremy thrived upon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 4th of July!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/08/the-4th-of-july-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/08/the-4th-of-july-2/</guid>
      <description>This year the 4th of July fell on a Monday so we were very happy that Ben got the day off. We spent a relaxing morning at home and in the afternoon went to Manhattan to view the Macy’s 4th of July fireworks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to Connecticut</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/04/visit-to-connecticut/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/04/visit-to-connecticut/</guid>
      <description>A few weekends ago we drove up to Connecticut to visit fellow Kiwis, Ron and Judy Snoek and their son Troy. They very kindly hosted us for a night with some good ol’ home-like hospitality. It was so nice to spend time with them and get to know them a bit better (I (Franci) hadn’t even met them before this!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shenanigans with Sharon</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/01/shenanigans-with-sharon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/01/shenanigans-with-sharon/</guid>
      <description>Ben’s cousin Sharon visited us over Memorial Weekend, and we had a lot of fun packing in as much sight-seeing as was practical! Here is some photographic evidence.
We walked the Brooklyn Bridge,
sat on cool seats on the way to the Ferry terminal,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who sped up time?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/28/who-sped-up-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/28/who-sped-up-time/</guid>
      <description>How is it possible that we have been in New York City for a year already? Yes, everyone, it’s been a YEAR! When we arrived a year ago, I must admit that I viewed our ‘adventure’ with some trepidation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful Brooklyn Botanic Garden</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/21/beautiful-brooklyn-botanic-garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/21/beautiful-brooklyn-botanic-garden/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weeks ago, we went to the Brooklyn Botanic Garden with our friends Julie and Abby Murphy and Damaris and her 2 cute kids, Elijah and Sophia.
The gardens were amazingly beautiful and dressed in their Spring finest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brooklyn Bridge!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/14/brooklyn-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/14/brooklyn-bridge/</guid>
      <description>When Ben’s dad was here back in April we got a fair bit of sight-seeing done, which even included some things I hadn’t seen or done before, which was pretty exciting. One of those things was walking the Brooklyn Bridge, which is just one of those things you have to do in New York City.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some other New York sights (and eats) with Hannah and Eva</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/05/some-other-new-york-sights-and-eats-with-hannah-and-eva/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/05/some-other-new-york-sights-and-eats-with-hannah-and-eva/</guid>
      <description>As you can tell, I’m waaay behind on sight-seeing posts! When Hannah and Eva were here way back in March, we did quite a few fun things I haven’t shared here yet, so here’s a photo post of some of the things we did and ate!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Up close and personal with Lady Liberty</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/16/up-close-and-personal-with-lady-liberty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/16/up-close-and-personal-with-lady-liberty/</guid>
      <description>The New Colossus By Emma Lazarus, 1883
Not like the brazen giant of Greek fame,
With conquering limbs astride from land to land;
Here at our sea-washed, sunset gates shall stand
A mighty woman with a torch, whose flame</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A too-short visit to The Met</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/06/a-too-short-visit-to-the-met/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/06/a-too-short-visit-to-the-met/</guid>
      <description>When Hannah and Eva were here, we went to the Met the same day we went to the Cloisters. The Met really deserves a day or two to itself, and I definitely plan to go back — the two or so hours we had there were only enough to see a few musical instruments and about 3/4 of the European Painters section.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An uncultured laugh (specially for April Fool’s day)</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/01/an-uncultured-laugh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/01/an-uncultured-laugh/</guid>
      <description>When I went to The Cloisters with Hannah and Eva, there were a few sculptures/carvings that I took pictures of purely to post on here with funny comments, because they sure made us crack up. My apologies go to the artists who did not create their masterpieces for us to laugh at, and to those of you who find Roman Catholic artefacts more meaningful than un-cultured moi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting The Cloisters</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/30/revisiting-the-cloisters/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/30/revisiting-the-cloisters/</guid>
      <description>When Ben’s cousins, Hannah and Eva, were here visiting with us, the three of us took a trip up into Manhattan to see The Cloisters and The Met (The Met will be in another post!).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Punta Cana!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/11/punta-cana/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/11/punta-cana/</guid>
      <description>Ben and I have always dreamed of going on a romantic tropical island holiday. This has partly been inspired by the total un-tropical-ness of our honeymoon destination (Stewart Island! I don’t know why we ever thought it would be tropical.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back to reality</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/09/back-to-reality/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/09/back-to-reality/</guid>
      <description>This past weekend Ben and I flew off into the Tropical sunset and had a total blast. We came back on Monday night and since then we’ve been right back into things here. I wasn’t organised enough to have self-publishing posts past Monday’s post on here, and things have been busy since we’ve been back, so you’ll all have to wait a little while till Friday to hear all about our trip and see a whole bunch of photos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sight-seeing with Lillian</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/03/sight-seeing-with-lillian/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/03/sight-seeing-with-lillian/</guid>
      <description>In the few weeks that Lillian has been here we’ve done all sorts of things like Christmas baking, movie watching, eating good food and talking, but we’ve also done some sight-seeing. You can’t leave that out when you’re in New York, even if the weather is freezing!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let it snow, let it snow, let it snow!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/27/let-it-snow-let-it-snow-let-it-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/27/let-it-snow-let-it-snow-let-it-snow/</guid>
      <description>It started snowing on Sunday morning and continued snowing through the night. This morning we woke up to almost 2 feet of snow and a totally transformed neighborhood.
This is what it looked like trying to get out of our metal gate:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New York Christmas</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/23/a-new-york-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/23/a-new-york-christmas/</guid>
      <description>I thought I might share a few New York-ish Christmas moments with you. The city gets decorated quite a lot and there are lights and Christmas trees all over the place. Ben and Lillian and Marica went and had a look at some of the famous Christmas light displays down 5th Avenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cloisters</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/13/the-cloisters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/13/the-cloisters/</guid>
      <description>Some of you have no doubt heard of The Metropolitan Museum of Art, or “The Met”, here in New York City. It’s a massive museum of art and culture, along Museum Mile on the east side of Central Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A few lovely photos</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/07/a-few-lovely-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/07/a-few-lovely-photos/</guid>
      <description>I thought I’d share a few photos of our time with the Braunings. We were so blessed by their hospitality, company, conversation and great food. Thanks again for inviting us, Mr &amp;amp; Mrs Brauning, and putting up with our changed plans and an invalid!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enjoying Fall</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/15/enjoying-fall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/15/enjoying-fall/</guid>
      <description>Two weekends ago we visited friends from church for lunch who recently got married, Franco and Neli. Franco grew up in NYC and Neli is from Peru. They’re a really lovely couple!
Franco and Neli live in a tall apartment building a block away from Central Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Silly Billy Elliot</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/12/silly-billy-elliot/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/12/silly-billy-elliot/</guid>
      <description>Last Friday, Franci and I went to a Broadway show for the first time: Billy Elliot the Musical at the Imperial Theatre. Here’s a photo we took just before we went in:
It was quite the experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playing tourist again: Bronx Zoo</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/02/playing-tourist-again-bronx-zoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/02/playing-tourist-again-bronx-zoo/</guid>
      <description>A couple of Saturdays ago we bundled up and visited the Bronx Zoo. It is the biggest metropolitan zoo in the world, and we certainly didn’t see all of it in the day we were there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hoyt Street, Brooklyn</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/21/hoyt-street-brooklyn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/21/hoyt-street-brooklyn/</guid>
      <description>Hoyt is a fairly well-established name here in New York. Brooklyn even has a Hoyt Street, and there are two subway stations along it. It’s kinda fun to see our name popping up here and there!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playing tourist again: Little Italy</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/20/playing-tourist-again-little-italy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/20/playing-tourist-again-little-italy/</guid>
      <description>Stepping into Little Italy is like being overseas for a little while. The streets (Mulberry Street in particular) is decorated in Italian colours — red, green and white.
The place is littered with restaurants, and pizza shops and places selling “Italian Specialties” like meats, breads and desserts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend in Pottstown</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/07/weekend-in-pottstown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/07/weekend-in-pottstown/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend we visited Ben’s uncle Sherwood and aunt Sharon in Pottstown, near Philadelphia. It was a very nice restful weekend, just visiting and getting to know them a bit better. Their daughter, Esther, is away at college, but Jonathan was there and the kids loved playing with him — he’s really good with children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playing tourist again: Chinatown</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/01/playing-tourist-again-chinatown/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/01/playing-tourist-again-chinatown/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weekends ago we visited Chinatown and Little Italy. I took so many photos that day that I cannot possibly fit them all into one post, so this one will be about Chinatown. Little Italy will follow eventually.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two nights &#43; 14 people &#43; 1 (small) New York apartment = Lots of fun!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/14/two-nights/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/14/two-nights/</guid>
      <description>It’s really hard to believe that it’s almost been two weeks since the van Wichens descended on our place. For those who don’t know, Laurel is Ben’s oldest sister and their family is touring the States for 10 weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tasty Recipe and more</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/01/tasty-recipe-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/01/tasty-recipe-and-more/</guid>
      <description>Last night we had some company (a work colleague of Ben’s) and I made a new recipe. I have a very bad habit of trying new recipes when we have people over, but this time it was definitely a winner!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saturday at Coney Island</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/30/saturday-at-coney-island/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/30/saturday-at-coney-island/</guid>
      <description>On Saturday we went to Coney Island for the day. We tried to pack in as much as possible and first went to the Aquarium, then for a swim at the beach and then off to the best part: some rides at the amusement parks!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to Colorado</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/16/visit-to-colorado/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/16/visit-to-colorado/</guid>
      <description>The last week of July we headed off to Colorado for a Tschetter family reunion (Ben’s mum’s side of the family) to specially celebrate Ben’s grandparents’ 70th wedding anniversary. We flew to Denver and then Mum and Dad Hoyt picked us up from the airport and we drove into the mountains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We’re back!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/12/were-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/12/were-back/</guid>
      <description>I’ve you’re an avid follower of our blog, you will have noticed that our posts have been rather sparse the last 2 and a half weeks. We’ve had a great time away traipsing over the country visiting family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 4th of July</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/15/the-4th-of-july/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/15/the-4th-of-july/</guid>
      <description>Earlier this month, on the 4th of July, the United States of America celebrated Independence Day. It’s been 234 years since America declared independence from Great Britain, and for the average American England is now just some far away place where people talk funny.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to the New York Aquarium</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/13/visit-to-the-new-york-aquarium/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/13/visit-to-the-new-york-aquarium/</guid>
      <description>We visited the New York Aquarium in Coney Island recently. From where we were at our old place in Brooklyn, it’s about an hour on the subway to get there.
There’s a great board walk with lots of shops selling food and trinkets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Streets of Power</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/30/streets-of-power/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/30/streets-of-power/</guid>
      <description>On Saturday, after our little jaunt to Staten Island, we had a little meander around Wall Street. When dad Hoyt talks about Canyon City, then this is it. I don’t get that feeling in Brooklyn, but boy, down there the streets are quite narrow and the buildings go up so high that if you wanted to take a photo of them you’d have to plaster 2 or 3 together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend touristy fun</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/30/weekend-touristy-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/30/weekend-touristy-fun/</guid>
      <description>Ben has already told you that we went to Staten (pronounced Statten, not State-in) Island on Saturday. I have some cool photos to share of our trip there and back, and later in the week I’ll tell and show you all about the stuff we saw in the Financial District.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Statue of Liberty</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/28/the-statue-of-liberty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/28/the-statue-of-liberty/</guid>
      <description>Today we took the Staten Island Ferry from the southern tip of Manhattan to the north-most point on Staten Island (and back, of course). For a long time the ferry cost only 25 cents for a return trip, then it went up to 50 cents in 1990.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
