<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Christmas on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/category/christmas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Christmas on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/category/christmas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Advent</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/01/26/advent/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/01/26/advent/</guid>
      <description>Advent is such a great time of the year. It’s filled with the anticipation of Christmas, warm kitchens overflowing with delicious smells, Christmas crafts, Christmas music playing in the background, parties, friends… (and it’s unfortunately also filled with busyness, usually mostly my own doing!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Greatest Gift</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/11/14/the-greatest-gift/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/11/14/the-greatest-gift/</guid>
      <description>A couple of years ago, I really enjoyed reading through The Greatest Gift by Ann Voskamp for Advent. This year I’m trying to be organized enough to remind you that if this is something you’d like to buy, now’s a good time, with Advent being just two weeks away and all!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to New Zealand, part 3</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/02/12/visit-to-new-zealand-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/02/12/visit-to-new-zealand-part-3/</guid>
      <description>I know this isn’t technically part of our trip to New Zealand, but I didn’t really want to make a whole separate post for these photos I took before we left. December was unseasonably warm, so one evening while Ben worked late, I took the kids on a post-dinner walk around the neighborhood to enjoy the lights on people’s houses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas 2014</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/30/christmas-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/30/christmas-2014/</guid>
      <description>This year was the first year I hosted all of Christmas (meaning both our Christmas Eve and Christmas Day celebrations), and it was fun! We had my parents with us, which was very special, and we also hosted James and Laura Williams and Laura’s friend, Ella.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas from the Hoyts</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/12/25/merry-christmas-from-the-hoyts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/12/25/merry-christmas-from-the-hoyts/</guid>
      <description>May your Christmas be blessed with much peace and joy.
Kind of like this:
Just maybe a bit more peaceful. :-)
&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hacker Christianity</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/12/22/hacker-christianity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/12/22/hacker-christianity/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This is a written version of a pre-Christmas talk I gave at work recently, about the intersection between Christianity and hacker culture. There’s also a video available here — the sound quality’s not brilliant, but feel free to watch it there!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Christmas goodie report, with recipes</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/06/a-christmas-goodie-report-with-recipes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/06/a-christmas-goodie-report-with-recipes/</guid>
      <description>I love baking. I love sharing baking. I love receiving baking. I love eating baking. Who doesn’t?!
Christmas is always a time of the year that I excitedly go totally overboard in the baking department, making way too many goodies and loving every minute of it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another wonderful Christmas</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/04/another-wonderful-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/04/another-wonderful-christmas/</guid>
      <description>Christmas feels like such a long time ago… but I really want to share these photos with you from our time with Jeremy’s folks.
We took the bus to Philadelphia from where Jeremy picked us up and drove us out to his parents’ place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas in New York</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/27/christmas-in-new-york/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/27/christmas-in-new-york/</guid>
      <description>On Wednesday evening the kids and I met Ben at work and had a special treat of eating out (there’s a decent diner near his work) and then going to look at some of the Christmas light displays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Merry Christmas to you</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/24/a-merry-christmas-to-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/24/a-merry-christmas-to-you/</guid>
      <description>We want to take this opportunity to wish you all a very Merry Christmas as you celebrate with your loved ones. May you abound in joy as you remember the humble birth of the God-man, the King of Kings, our Prince of Peace, our Saviour Jesus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gingerbread House fun</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/22/gingerbread-house-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/22/gingerbread-house-fun/</guid>
      <description>Our much loved pastor’s wife, Julie, invited a few moms over to her house last Friday to make gingerbread houses. What a total blast! We made the houses out of graham crackers instead of baked sheets of gingerbread, which was much easier and less time consuming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A visit to the New York City Ballet</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/15/a-visit-to-the-new-york-city-ballet-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/15/a-visit-to-the-new-york-city-ballet-2/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend our friend Megan, who dances in the New York City Ballet, gave us two tickets to attend The Nutcracker ballet at the Lincoln Centre, and Ben took Marica to go watch her dance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting excited about Christmas</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/12/getting-excited-about-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/12/getting-excited-about-christmas/</guid>
      <description>I love the month of December here in New York — I think it’s even my favourite time of the year, even better than beautiful spring-time April. It’s cold, but everyone seems to be in good spirits (as opposed to grumpy January!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent is here!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/10/advent-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/10/advent-is-here/</guid>
      <description>I started the blog post draft a few weeks back, and now the season of Advent is about halfway through. Last year we decided to start celebrating Advent in a more deliberate way, building the excitement until Christmas, and enjoying the anticipation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our first snowman</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/05/our-first-snowman/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/05/our-first-snowman/</guid>
      <description>It got seriously warm today (almost 10 degrees C), so we went into our snow-covered backyard and colonized it, turning the beautiful fresh snow into a snowman.
Our back “yard” before we started:
Laying the foundation (Marica supervising):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our first New York Christmas</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/30/our-first-new-york-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/30/our-first-new-york-christmas/</guid>
      <description>This year was the first year our little family did not celebrate Christmas with grandparents. I was going to say that we didn’t celebrate with any extended family, but we do have Lillian here, so we’re not entirely family-less!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/24/merry-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/24/merry-christmas/</guid>
      <description>Today we celebrate the birth of The Biggest Present ever given. A Saviour to free us from sin, to take away the wrath we deserve and puts it on Himself, a death-conquering King who calls us His brothers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New York Christmas</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/23/a-new-york-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/23/a-new-york-christmas/</guid>
      <description>I thought I might share a few New York-ish Christmas moments with you. The city gets decorated quite a lot and there are lights and Christmas trees all over the place. Ben and Lillian and Marica went and had a look at some of the famous Christmas light displays down 5th Avenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating Advent</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/21/celebrating-advent/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/21/celebrating-advent/</guid>
      <description>It’s December… This is my favourite time of the year! I love the anticipation of Christmas, the Christmas music (I’ve been listening to a lot of old school Christmas songs on Pandora and we’ve been through The Messiah quite a number of times now too!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
