<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Church on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/category/church/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Church on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/category/church/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Three little flower girls</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/05/09/three-little-flower-girls/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/05/09/three-little-flower-girls/</guid>
      <description>Back in February our 3 girls got to be flower girls for a lovely couple in our church, Kelvin and Joanna. It was a beautiful day — unseasonably warm for February basically the whole week leading up to the wedding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MeRF Getaway</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/09/02/merf-getaway/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/09/02/merf-getaway/</guid>
      <description>Back in June, some folks in our church (MeRF = Messiah’s Reformed Fellowship) headed out to Pennsylvania for a getaway at Kirby House, a beautiful old house that was once used by the Kirby family as their summer home in the mountains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easter 2016</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/05/06/easter-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/05/06/easter-2016/</guid>
      <description>This year’s Easter was a busy but lovely one. We kept up the tradition of making hot cross buns and egg dying, which the kids always love,
&amp;nbsp;
and on Easter Sunday we hosted a large crowd of church folk for a yummy dinner, followed by some rousing hymn singing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pie Day</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/01/01/pie-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/01/01/pie-day/</guid>
      <description>Back in mid-November I had a few girls from church over at our house for a pie making day. We worked hard, had lots of fun and got to enjoy some pretty yummy pies.
For those of you who might be interested, here are the recipes of what we made.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CCEF’s 2015 conference</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/11/06/ccefs-2015-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/11/06/ccefs-2015-conference/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weekends ago, I had the amazing opportunity to travel down to Virginia Beach for this year’s CCEF (Christian Counseling and Educational Foundation) Conference. The topic of this year’s conference was Side by Side: How God helps us help each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presbyterians of the world, unite!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/11/27/presbyterians-of-the-world-unite/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/11/27/presbyterians-of-the-world-unite/</guid>
      <description>After hours of sweatless toil, I present to you the Plain English Westminster, or PEW if you like. It’s my “translation” of the Westminster Confession of Faith into modern English.
This is a project I’ve been working on for the last couple of years, very on and off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 3-step guide for mothers who want to Do It All</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/10/the-3-step-guide-for-mothers-who-want-to-do-it-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/10/the-3-step-guide-for-mothers-who-want-to-do-it-all/</guid>
      <description>Yes, you too can Do It All! Small children? A big workload? Stack of dishes in the sink? Pile of bills to pay? No problem! Just follow my easy 3-step program and soon you too could be one of those special people who can Do It All!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caring for Creation</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/02/caring-for-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/02/caring-for-creation/</guid>
      <description>My friend Matthew Bartlett recently started his own publishing company, and his first book is The Biblical Mandate for Caring for Creation by retired New Zealand minister Dick Tripp. The 158-page book, which can be yours for a mere $24.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Christianity sexist?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/19/is-christianity-sexist/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/19/is-christianity-sexist/</guid>
      <description>Perhaps the most-prayed Christian prayer is the Lord’s Prayer: “Our Father who art in heaven…” But why Father and not person or parent? Is Christianity sexist?
Our home church denomination recently held a national Synod meeting, and one of the things they discussed was the updated 2011 translation of the NIV Bible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Person’s Prayer</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/17/the-persons-prayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/17/the-persons-prayer/</guid>
      <description>Our Caregiver in the spiritual realm,
Transparent be your name.
Your democracy be voted in,
Your social policy be implemented,
In reality as it is in the spiritual realm.
Give us every day our organic tofu,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luth3r hacks iChurch, makes Bible open source</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/30/luth3r-hacks-ichurch-makes-bible-open-source/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/30/luth3r-hacks-ichurch-makes-bible-open-source/</guid>
      <description>GENEVA TRIBUNE, August 1517.
New things are afoot in the world of Scripture freedom. Two days ago a hacker, who goes under the pseudonym Mart1n Luth3r, released a set of 95 bullet points outlining how to hack iChurch’s core systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to Connecticut</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/04/visit-to-connecticut/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/04/visit-to-connecticut/</guid>
      <description>A few weekends ago we drove up to Connecticut to visit fellow Kiwis, Ron and Judy Snoek and their son Troy. They very kindly hosted us for a night with some good ol’ home-like hospitality. It was so nice to spend time with them and get to know them a bit better (I (Franci) hadn’t even met them before this!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easter</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/29/easter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/29/easter/</guid>
      <description>Easter this year was probably the most different for us as a family than what we’ve had before. Ben didn’t get Good Friday off, so it was really strange not to be able to go to church together as a family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Should churches care about branding?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/11/should-churches-care-about-branding/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/11/should-churches-care-about-branding/</guid>
      <description>Centuries ago (in internet time) graphic designer David Airey wrote a blog post asking folks whether they’d seen any good church logos. My brother Bryan responded with a thought-provoking comment asking whether churches should even be concerned about “branding”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The One True BDFL</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/14/the-one-true-bdfl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/14/the-one-true-bdfl/</guid>
      <description>Note: This blog is mostly read by family and friends, but I wrote this more for my fellow programmers. Knowing me, it’ll be taken the wrong way by both groups of people. :-) By the way, see the first comment for a book give-away!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet our church in New York</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/22/meet-our-church-in-new-york/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/22/meet-our-church-in-new-york/</guid>
      <description>Here in New York we attend a URCNA (United Reformed Church of North America) congregation that meets in lower Manhattan near Ground Zero, called Messiah’s Reformed Fellowship (MeRF for short).
MeRF started as a response to the September 11 terrorist attacks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
