<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Weather on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/category/weather/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Weather on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/category/weather/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful autumn</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/12/23/beautiful-autumn-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/12/23/beautiful-autumn-2/</guid>
      <description>Autumn this year was beautiful and mild and felt like a sort of nicer continuation of summer. We were, of course, back at doing school, but we tried to enjoy the nice weather as much as we could.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick, sticky snow</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/04/08/quick-sticky-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/04/08/quick-sticky-snow/</guid>
      <description>It’s been quiet on here for a while. When that happens, it usually means things around here have been a little extra busy, which it indeed has. Some of the highlights of the busyness will be following in the next few weeks, but before the warm weather completely overtakes us I wanted to share some last winter snow pictures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This winter’s first snow</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/03/04/this-winters-first-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/03/04/this-winters-first-snow/</guid>
      <description>I feel like I’m always putting up stuff on here that’s a month or more old. It just seems to be the rate at which I can keep up with things! A few days after we got back from New Zealand mid-January, we had the first big (and the only big, really) snow storm of the winter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A tad on the cool side</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/02/15/a-tad-on-the-cool-side/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/02/15/a-tad-on-the-cool-side/</guid>
      <description>This past weekend was a little nippy. I’d say it was the coldest weather we’ve ever experienced! Most of last week the high during the day didn’t get above 0°C, and by Sunday morning we woke up to this (my phone shows temperature in Celsius):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful autumn</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/11/20/beautiful-autumn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/11/20/beautiful-autumn/</guid>
      <description>I have a love-hate relationship with autumn. I love all the beautiful colors, the cooler weather and the fun things the season brings like apples, cinnamon, pumpkin pie and hot chocolate. But… autumn is the start of a long cold spell that only keeps getting worse for about 5 months before it starts getting better!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black and white trees</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/03/20/black-and-white-trees/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/03/20/black-and-white-trees/</guid>
      <description>I love the way leaf-less trees look so stark in black and white.
These photos were taken in Prospect Park, Brooklyn a couple of years back.
And this one in Lancaster County.
March was heralded in by a snowstorm, and it looked like this in front of our house just a couple of weeks ago:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful snow</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/03/03/beautiful-snow-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/03/03/beautiful-snow-2/</guid>
      <description>Last week we had another bit of snow. (That was the snow before today’s snow, and Sunday’s snow, and then the two snows before that.) It seems every time Boston gets a foot or more of snow, we get about 2 or 3 inches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby, it’s cold outside!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/02/06/baby-its-cold-outside/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/02/06/baby-its-cold-outside/</guid>
      <description>Last night the girls had a lovely surprise of some cards from their cousins (thanks, Ilse, Estelle and Hendrik!). What was funny to us was that they asked how our summer has been, which of course, it very much has not been.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring is here! (and some going away thoughts)</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/27/spring-is-here-and-some-going-away-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/27/spring-is-here-and-some-going-away-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>It seems that spring came a month early this year, after a winter that seemed like it never quite happened. Last year we had so much snow, this year, nothing to speak of. So much for the nice sturdy new toboggan I bought last autumn!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We survived Irene</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/28/we-survived-irene/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/28/we-survived-irene/</guid>
      <description>We’re posting this from a rescue boat (with free wireless internet) that lifted us from the roof of our flooded apartment early this morning. We’re sipping complimentary cocktails as we traverse the streets by boat, witnessing how New York has turned into a lake full of broken branches and leaves, a veritable Venice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Irene</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/27/hurricane-irene/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/27/hurricane-irene/</guid>
      <description>Most of you are probably aware that Hurricane Irene is currently moving up the East Coast of the States, and will most likely pass through, or very close to New York City. For those of you who are interested, we are not in an area likely to flood, and we don’t foresee needing to evacuate at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Okay, so it’s just a teensy bit hot here</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/23/okay-so-its-just-a-teensy-bit-hot-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/23/okay-so-its-just-a-teensy-bit-hot-here/</guid>
      <description>You’ve probably heard about the heat wave that has hit us here in the States. It’s a steaming sauna — free! We seem to be spending time here when all the records strike. Record snow, record heat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful Brooklyn Botanic Garden</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/21/beautiful-brooklyn-botanic-garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/21/beautiful-brooklyn-botanic-garden/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weeks ago, we went to the Brooklyn Botanic Garden with our friends Julie and Abby Murphy and Damaris and her 2 cute kids, Elijah and Sophia.
The gardens were amazingly beautiful and dressed in their Spring finest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preschool poetry</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/05/preschool-poetry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/05/preschool-poetry/</guid>
      <description>Last Friday, Marica’s preschool put on a poetry recital that parents were invited to. The kids had all worked hard at memorising the poems — they recited 3 poems and then sung Mary had a little lamb, and they did really well!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Salmon and Couscous Salad</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/14/spring-salmon-and-couscous-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/14/spring-salmon-and-couscous-salad/</guid>
      <description>I know that I’ve had a lot of recipes on here recently. Maybe that can partly be attributed to the weather — the more time we have inside, the more time I have to do fun stuff in the kitchen, plus it’s not so insanely hot when the oven goes on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh yes, I have a blog.</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/02/oh-yes-i-have-a-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/02/oh-yes-i-have-a-blog/</guid>
      <description>That’s how it feels to me sometimes when I realise that all my scheduled posts have run out, and my drafts folder is looking a bit emaciated. We run this blog mainly to stay in contact with family and friends back home in New Zealand to share what we’ve been up to, what we’re thinking about and stuff we like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting creative with snow</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/02/getting-creative-with-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/02/getting-creative-with-snow/</guid>
      <description>We’ve had a lot of snow here this winter, and today we’ve got snow and ice rain again! Well, life carries on about as normally as it can and we try to get out when we can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowsational</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/31/snowsational/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/31/snowsational/</guid>
      <description>Snow is beautiful. And fun. It does get messy, and it keeps you indoors more than you’d like, but those are trifles compared to the six foot high piles of white-or-grey frozen stuff all over the streets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Have we mentioned it’s been cold?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/24/have-we-mentioned-its-been-cold/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/24/have-we-mentioned-its-been-cold/</guid>
      <description>Our first blizzard in New York was a very exciting event. Everything was beautiful and white and we were on holiday. The second one was not so exciting, apart from the fact that it kept Lillian with us for a day longer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our first snowman</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/05/our-first-snowman/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/05/our-first-snowman/</guid>
      <description>It got seriously warm today (almost 10 degrees C), so we went into our snow-covered backyard and colonized it, turning the beautiful fresh snow into a snowman.
Our back “yard” before we started:
Laying the foundation (Marica supervising):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let it snow, let it snow, let it snow!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/27/let-it-snow-let-it-snow-let-it-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/27/let-it-snow-let-it-snow-let-it-snow/</guid>
      <description>It started snowing on Sunday morning and continued snowing through the night. This morning we woke up to almost 2 feet of snow and a totally transformed neighborhood.
This is what it looked like trying to get out of our metal gate:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
