<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2017s on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2017s on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A little time travel into the past: June</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/10/27/a-little-time-travel-into-the-past-june/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/10/27/a-little-time-travel-into-the-past-june/</guid>
      <description>In early June, Marica and Esther performed and did really well at their annual piano recital. They both played solo pieces and also performed a duet. I was a proud mama!
The highlight of June was a visit from my sister Angelique and nephew Tyson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A little time travel into the past: May</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/10/10/a-little-time-travel-into-the-past-may/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/10/10/a-little-time-travel-into-the-past-may/</guid>
      <description>May brought an end to our homeschool co-op (but not to our schooling at home — that we continued until the end of June, much to the kids’ chagrin). We have a little tradition where our family takes a few friends out to a local chocolate shop where each of the kids (and moms) can choose a treat on the last day of co-op for the school year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A little time travel into the past: April</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/09/24/a-little-time-travel-into-the-past-april/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/09/24/a-little-time-travel-into-the-past-april/</guid>
      <description>In April, we had a wonderful visit from my parents. It was great to spend time together again — especially for the grandkids to have their grandparents around! Spring really was a great time for a visit — not too hot and not too cold, and it’s so beautiful with all the blossoms and flowers out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book review: Mercy Triumphs</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/09/08/book-review-mercy-triumphs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/09/08/book-review-mercy-triumphs/</guid>
      <description>When Jana Kelly published Side by Side in 2015, I got the opportunity to review the book before it hit stores. It was great getting into the stories of Mia, Halimah, and Rania, and then to get deeper into their lives with the next book in the series, Door to Freedom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A little time travel into the past: March</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/08/25/a-little-time-travel-into-the-past-march/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/08/25/a-little-time-travel-into-the-past-march/</guid>
      <description>There used to be a time I blogged several times a week. Then it turned into twice a week, then once a week, then once every two weeks, then… whenever I happen to write a blog post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General update</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/07/28/general-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/07/28/general-update/</guid>
      <description>An update written by Ben for a change. After all, Franci has written almost all of the posts on this blog. As it happens, the last one Ben wrote was almost a year ago.
Ben is busy with various things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three little flower girls</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/05/09/three-little-flower-girls/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/05/09/three-little-flower-girls/</guid>
      <description>Back in February our 3 girls got to be flower girls for a lovely couple in our church, Kelvin and Joanna. It was a beautiful day — unseasonably warm for February basically the whole week leading up to the wedding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A decade old!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/05/02/a-decade-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/05/02/a-decade-old/</guid>
      <description>In February, Marica turned 10. TEN?? How does a decade go by so fast? Marica is growing up — both taller and also growing in maturity little by little. Or maybe not so little! Her independence in the kitchen is growing, and she’s becoming quite the cook and baker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1920’s Day at co-op</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/03/27/1920s-day-at-co-op/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/03/27/1920s-day-at-co-op/</guid>
      <description>In February we had a 1920’s festival at our homeschool co-op where we learned about some things that happened in the 1920’s in general, and in our area (Thomas Edison, who lived nearby, was actively inventing cool things; the Holland Tunnel between NJ and Manhattan was being built); we got to dress up in fun costumes, someone came in to teach us how to dance the Charleston, and we had a 1920’s themed feast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making Marica Grate Again!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/03/08/making-marica-grate-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/03/08/making-marica-grate-again/</guid>
      <description>As the cruel parents we are, tonight we decided to make Marica grate – again:
Sorry, couldn’t resist.
But after I thought of the pun, I think there’s a serious point here, along the lines of that P.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book review: Door to Freedom</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/03/03/book-review-door-to-freedom/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/03/03/book-review-door-to-freedom/</guid>
      <description>Back in 2015, I was given the opportunity to review the book Side by Side by Jana Kelley. It was a realistic and an enjoyable read, which I was excited to hear is turning into a trilogy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rambling thoughts</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/02/22/rambling-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/02/22/rambling-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>The year starts off differently here in the northern hemisphere compared to the southern hemisphere. In some ways it doesn’t really feel like a new year — school and work just keeps going after a short break for Christmas; whereas in NZ just about nothing happens the first few weeks of January because 90% of the country is off somewhere on holiday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/01/26/advent/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/01/26/advent/</guid>
      <description>Advent is such a great time of the year. It’s filled with the anticipation of Christmas, warm kitchens overflowing with delicious smells, Christmas crafts, Christmas music playing in the background, parties, friends… (and it’s unfortunately also filled with busyness, usually mostly my own doing!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
