<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Family on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/category/family/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Family on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/category/family/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Time travel into the past: July 2017</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2018/03/14/time-travel-into-the-past-july-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2018/03/14/time-travel-into-the-past-july-2017/</guid>
      <description>Life’s been happening by the spade full around here, and blogging has been severely neglected, sorry. Here’s an attempt at rectifying that!
Back in July last year… hmmm, let’s see if the photos can remind me that far back!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A little time travel into the past: June</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/10/27/a-little-time-travel-into-the-past-june/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/10/27/a-little-time-travel-into-the-past-june/</guid>
      <description>In early June, Marica and Esther performed and did really well at their annual piano recital. They both played solo pieces and also performed a duet. I was a proud mama!
The highlight of June was a visit from my sister Angelique and nephew Tyson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A little time travel into the past: April</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/09/24/a-little-time-travel-into-the-past-april/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/09/24/a-little-time-travel-into-the-past-april/</guid>
      <description>In April, we had a wonderful visit from my parents. It was great to spend time together again — especially for the grandkids to have their grandparents around! Spring really was a great time for a visit — not too hot and not too cold, and it’s so beautiful with all the blossoms and flowers out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A decade old!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/05/02/a-decade-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/05/02/a-decade-old/</guid>
      <description>In February, Marica turned 10. TEN?? How does a decade go by so fast? Marica is growing up — both taller and also growing in maturity little by little. Or maybe not so little! Her independence in the kitchen is growing, and she’s becoming quite the cook and baker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/01/26/advent/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/01/26/advent/</guid>
      <description>Advent is such a great time of the year. It’s filled with the anticipation of Christmas, warm kitchens overflowing with delicious smells, Christmas crafts, Christmas music playing in the background, parties, friends… (and it’s unfortunately also filled with busyness, usually mostly my own doing!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful autumn</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/12/23/beautiful-autumn-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/12/23/beautiful-autumn-2/</guid>
      <description>Autumn this year was beautiful and mild and felt like a sort of nicer continuation of summer. We were, of course, back at doing school, but we tried to enjoy the nice weather as much as we could.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The rest of the summer</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/12/09/the-rest-of-the-summer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/12/09/the-rest-of-the-summer/</guid>
      <description>(This post is pretty heavy on photos. Just a reminder that if you want to see larger versions of them, to click on a photo and you’ll then be able to view the slideshow of that particular group of photos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip ’16: Six Flags</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/11/04/roadtrip-16-six-flags/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/11/04/roadtrip-16-six-flags/</guid>
      <description>For the last leg of our roadtrip home, we made a stop at Six Flags in the south of New Jersey. They have a program called Read To Succeed where the kids have to read a total of 600 hours in the year to get free tickets to Six Flags.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip ’16: Hoyt Reunion</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/09/30/roadtrip-16-hoyt-reunion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/09/30/roadtrip-16-hoyt-reunion/</guid>
      <description>After our great camping experience, we drove down to Columbia, SC, to spend the night and visit Ben’s parents’ old church where we got to meet people who knew them 40 years ago, which was pretty neat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip ’16: Camping in TN</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/09/23/roadtrip-16-camping-in-tn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/09/23/roadtrip-16-camping-in-tn/</guid>
      <description>After our visit to Monticello we started the drive down to Cherokee National Forest in east Tennessee where we planned on camping for a couple of nights. We started off in the rain and the rain just got heavier and heavier, and there were predictions for a huge storm to pass over where we were going to camp that night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurelin’s 3rd birthday</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/08/26/laurelins-3rd-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/08/26/laurelins-3rd-birthday/</guid>
      <description>In all the bustle of the end of the school year and then summer vacation, I’ve neglected to post photos of Laurelin’s 3rd birthday.
Laurelin is now a full-blown 3-year-old and no push-over, in every sense of the word.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finishing up the school year</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/08/19/finishing-up-the-school-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/08/19/finishing-up-the-school-year/</guid>
      <description>It’s taken us a while to get used to this business of school finishing right in the middle of the calendar year and the starting again in August/September when we are so used to the school year following the calendar year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random thoughts</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/06/10/random-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/06/10/random-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>The last couple of months have looked a little different to our usual routines. I’ve had a relapse of the Epstein-Barr virus which wiped me out but I seem to be feeling a fair bit better the last week or so; Ben’s been looking at different job options and has had multiple interviews with several different companies (no decision yet, though).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easter 2016</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/05/06/easter-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/05/06/easter-2016/</guid>
      <description>This year’s Easter was a busy but lovely one. We kept up the tradition of making hot cross buns and egg dying, which the kids always love,
&amp;nbsp;
and on Easter Sunday we hosted a large crowd of church folk for a yummy dinner, followed by some rousing hymn singing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April Fool’s Day</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/04/29/april-fools-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/04/29/april-fools-day/</guid>
      <description>Our family, especially the kids, have taken a real liking to April 1st. The kids plan pranks for weeks in advance, which they then gleefully execute on the day. We also have a little tradition of having waffles for dinner on that night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some fishy characters</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/04/22/some-fishy-characters/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/04/22/some-fishy-characters/</guid>
      <description>For the first few years of our marriage Ben and I had a little dog, Blitzie. When we came to the States in 2010, we gave her away and she’s been living happily every after on a pig farm since.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marica’s 9th birthday</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/03/11/maricas-9th-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/03/11/maricas-9th-birthday/</guid>
      <description>My oldest turned 9 last month. Where did the time go? I know all mothers always say that, but my oh my, they grow up fast. Gone is the little girl who liked her hair braided all pretty, and who would wear whatever her mother put out for her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to New Zealand, part 4</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/02/19/visit-to-new-zealand-part-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/02/19/visit-to-new-zealand-part-4/</guid>
      <description>A couple of days after Christmas Ben returned to the US, and the girls and I stayed in NZ for another 3 (full, but great) weeks. We met up with lots of family and friends and had such a great time that for the most part I forgot to take my camera along.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to New Zealand, part 3</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/02/12/visit-to-new-zealand-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/02/12/visit-to-new-zealand-part-3/</guid>
      <description>I know this isn’t technically part of our trip to New Zealand, but I didn’t really want to make a whole separate post for these photos I took before we left. December was unseasonably warm, so one evening while Ben worked late, I took the kids on a post-dinner walk around the neighborhood to enjoy the lights on people’s houses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to New Zealand, part 2</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/02/05/visit-to-new-zealand-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/02/05/visit-to-new-zealand-part-2/</guid>
      <description>A couple of days after we arrived, we headed out of town to Mt Hutt in the Southern Alps for a Hoyt reunion. I think it had been the first time in almost 6 years that everyone were together again — Mum &amp;amp; Dad, all 8 siblings, plus spouses and kids — and it was fantastic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Esther’s 6th birthday</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/11/27/esthers-6th-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/11/27/esthers-6th-birthday/</guid>
      <description>Esther turned 6 in November. Hard to believe, isn’t it?! Her birthday celebrations were spread out over two days — on Friday at co-op the kids sang Happy Birthday to her and she and Marica handed out cupcakes that Marica had baked (no, Mum, you’re not allowed to help me!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disclaimer</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/10/02/disclaimer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/10/02/disclaimer/</guid>
      <description>I was recently talking with Ben about a blogger whose blog I follow. I really respect her and appreciate her blog immensely, but the frequency with which she puts out quality blog posts about stuff they’ve done or made, and about the amazing things they do in their homeschool was making me feel like she must be some super woman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary of summer, part 4</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/09/25/summary-of-summer-part-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/09/25/summary-of-summer-part-4/</guid>
      <description>So, last week I mentioned how we traveled to Indiana for cousin Sharon’s and Vijo’s wedding in August. Despite the 13 hour trip each way, we were so happy that we could go and also that we could spend time with other Hoyt family members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A summary of summer, part 3</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/09/19/a-summary-of-summer-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/09/19/a-summary-of-summer-part-3/</guid>
      <description>August was filled to the brim with activity. We said goodbye to our Chinese exchange students, and celebrated Ben’s birthday.
We swam a few times in our friend’s nearby pool, but also did a fun day trip out to go swim at a water hole our friend Sarah knows about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A summary of summer, part 2</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/09/11/a-summary-of-summer-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/09/11/a-summary-of-summer-part-2/</guid>
      <description>A summary of summer, continued.
In July, we hosted the Holtslags, our pastor from NZ and his family, as well as James and Laura (James is Phillipa’s son, Laura is the Holtslags’ daughter). This time we sent them off to do sight-seeing by themselves, but we still got to have some good conversations over the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A summary of summer, part 1</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/09/04/a-summary-of-summer-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/09/04/a-summary-of-summer-part-1/</guid>
      <description>I know our blog posts have been a bit sporadic recently, but we’ve been up to all sorts of mischief. It’s summer after all! We’ve had playdates, we’ve played in the sprinklers, we’ve done lots of swimming, we’ve had sleep-overs, we’ve had visits to the library, we’ve had a couple of road trips, we’ve had homemade lemonade, iced tea and popsicles, eaten tonnes of watermelon and peaches and corn… you know… summer stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April Fool’s Dinner</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/04/03/april-fools-dinner/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/04/03/april-fools-dinner/</guid>
      <description>A few years back, on a whim, I decided to start a fun tradition for April Fool’s Day dinner: dessert for dinner (and no need to have dinner for dessert!). Turns out the kids think this is great, but the adults give a little groan at the thought.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lego Tower version 1</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/03/28/lego-tower-version-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/03/28/lego-tower-version-1/</guid>
      <description>Marica and Esther and I (Ben) have been playing with Lego on Saturdays. Marica’s built up a decent collection of small Lego sets over the past several birthdays and Christmases, and building things with them is one of my favourite inside things to do with the kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas 2014</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/30/christmas-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/30/christmas-2014/</guid>
      <description>This year was the first year I hosted all of Christmas (meaning both our Christmas Eve and Christmas Day celebrations), and it was fun! We had my parents with us, which was very special, and we also hosted James and Laura Williams and Laura’s friend, Ella.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas from the Hoyts</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/12/25/merry-christmas-from-the-hoyts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/12/25/merry-christmas-from-the-hoyts/</guid>
      <description>May your Christmas be blessed with much peace and joy.
Kind of like this:
Just maybe a bit more peaceful. :-)
&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/12/19/thanksgiving-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/12/19/thanksgiving-3/</guid>
      <description>This year, we celebrated Thanksgiving on the day after Thanksgiving, which actually gave us a good opportunity to go to the Macy’s Thanksgiving parade in New York City. Our friend Peter lives right by where the parade went past (and right next to the Empire State Building!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October Fest</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/11/21/october-fest/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/11/21/october-fest/</guid>
      <description>One weekend in October we went to an October Fest (not the beer-drinking kind) hosted by the Essex County Environmental Center, the same place where the girls go for their Frog Pond Science Club. It was a lovely community event where all the things on offer were free — crafts, a petting zoo, a snake man, music, and even some snacks!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camping in the wilds of New Jersey</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/03/camping-in-the-wilds-of-new-jersey/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/03/camping-in-the-wilds-of-new-jersey/</guid>
      <description>The first weekend in September we went camping with Lillian and Jeremy and Shanna at High Point State Park. We didn’t really know what to expect, seeing that we had never been there before, but we were up for trying it — our very first camping trip in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fruit picking in Princeton</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/09/26/fruit-picking-in-princeton/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/09/26/fruit-picking-in-princeton/</guid>
      <description>At the end of July (boy, how is it that the end of July is already months ago??) I took the girls fruit picking at Terhune Orchards just outside of Princeton. It’s a lovely place, and it’s always so nice to pick your own produce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun day at the Fair</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/15/fun-day-at-the-fair/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/15/fun-day-at-the-fair/</guid>
      <description>On the first weekend of July we took the kids to the Meadowlands State Fair which is pretty close to where we live. The kids were giddy with excitement!
We got there as soon as it opened in the afternoon so it wouldn’t be too busy, and that was a good idea because there weren’t many lines to wait in, but everything got progressively busier during the late afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A visit from cousins</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/01/a-visit-from-cousins/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/01/a-visit-from-cousins/</guid>
      <description>The last weekend in June, we had two of Ben’s cousins, Chris and Laura Lee, visit us from Texas. That weekend was a real blast! Packed full of sight-seeing and talking and fun! Here’s some of what we did with them:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A visit from the Baneks</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/07/25/a-visit-from-the-baneks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/07/25/a-visit-from-the-baneks/</guid>
      <description>In June, we had a lovely visit from Ben’s Uncle Walter, Aunt Nelda and cousin Alexander from Texas. They were here for 4 days and we got a really good amount of sight-seeing done with them, balanced by a nice lot of calmly visiting at home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurelin’s first birthday</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/06/13/laurelins-first-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/06/13/laurelins-first-birthday/</guid>
      <description>Three weeks ago, Laurelin turned 1. Crazy stuff, how did that happen?
We had a really low-key day, church in the morning, and then a little party with our lovely friends Alfredo and Damaris and their kids (whom I didn’t get a good photo of, sorry!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My daddy’s stronger than your daddy!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/05/02/my-daddys-stronger-than-your-daddy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/05/02/my-daddys-stronger-than-your-daddy/</guid>
      <description>And handsomer too. So there! :-)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everyday beauty</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/04/10/everyday-beauty/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/04/10/everyday-beauty/</guid>
      <description>It’s so easy to become complacent, to not notice the beauty around us.
The beauty in the messes of little kids, because those kids are kids you love, and because they won’t be little forever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another birthday</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/03/27/another-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/03/27/another-birthday/</guid>
      <description>Last week, I celebrated another birthday. The last one of my 20’s. Marica very tactfully said, “Mum, it’s good that you’re not turning 30. Thirty is too old for a woman!”
Ben took the morning off so that we could go to the MVC to get our New Jersey driver’s licences, but the unfortunately the proof of address we took along was not good enough in their books, so we had to leave without the licences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flights booked, date set!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/01/25/flights-booked-date-set/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/01/25/flights-booked-date-set/</guid>
      <description>We started this blog almost four years ago with the words “so we’re going overseas in a month”. They do say history repeats itself…
About six months ago, Ben got a job offer with TripAdvisor who was hoping to acquire Oyster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A weekend visit to Oamaru</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/01/07/a-weekend-visit-to-oamaru/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/01/07/a-weekend-visit-to-oamaru/</guid>
      <description>The last weekend of last year we made the three hour drive down to Oamaru to visit Mum and Dad Hoyt. We always love visiting them! This time around Bevan and Elrike were there with us, and the girls had a great time playing together in a different setting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2013: A year in photos</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/12/31/2013-a-year-in-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/12/31/2013-a-year-in-photos/</guid>
      <description>In an attempt to get up to date on here, I’m doing a ‘year in photos’, with a few glimpses into some of the highlights of the past year.
It’s one of those years I’m very thankful to see the end of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doing a bit of catch up</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/11/24/doing-a-bit-of-catch-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/11/24/doing-a-bit-of-catch-up/</guid>
      <description>To catch up some of what we’ve been up to over the last year or so, I thought I’d just share some photos of life around here for the last few months of last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What a lovely excuse!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/07/20/what-a-lovely-excuse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/07/20/what-a-lovely-excuse/</guid>
      <description>I’m such a regular blogger, I have to tick the ‘Remember Me’ box every time I log in to the blog! I had high hopes of finishing the road trip blog posts before the baby arrived, but things got in the way (just minor things like a pregnancy, a hospital stay and the like)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip: Lone Pine</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/04/09/roadtrip-lone-pine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/04/09/roadtrip-lone-pine/</guid>
      <description>The next stop couldn’t have been more different from Las Vegas. Tranquil, rural, isolated, pretty much nobody around, right in nature, and no electricity! We stayed the night in a little cabin/tent outside a small town called Lone Pine, between the Death Valley and the Sierra Nevada Mountains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Continuing the roadtrip posts: A visit to Phoenix</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/03/03/continuing-the-roadtrip-posts-a-visit-to-phoenix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/03/03/continuing-the-roadtrip-posts-a-visit-to-phoenix/</guid>
      <description>I know that I stopped our roadtrip posts rather abruptly last year, and for good reason, but I really do want to finish the posts before the baby arrives. That equates to six more posts over the next 3 months — surely I could do that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why the blog has been rather neglected</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/11/26/why-the-blog-has-been-rather-neglected/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/11/26/why-the-blog-has-been-rather-neglected/</guid>
      <description>Those of you who have been following the blog for any time over the last 2.5 years or so will have noticed that there has been a marked drop in the frequency of posts here. The reason for that has partly been that coming back to New Zealand has made life busier in many ways and that the time to blog has diminished.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A visit to Moab and Arches National Park</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/10/25/a-visit-to-moab-and-arches-national-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/10/25/a-visit-to-moab-and-arches-national-park/</guid>
      <description>One of the scenic highlights of our roadtrip was the state of Utah, where we went to Arches National Park, and drove through Monument Valley on our way to the Grand Canyon. We both loved the Grand Canyon (post still coming!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to the Boonzaaijers’</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/09/19/visit-to-the-boonzaaijers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/09/19/visit-to-the-boonzaaijers/</guid>
      <description>So, getting around to posting these last roadtrip posts have crawled to a terribly slow pace, but I’m determined to finish them up. When I get to that point, I’ll evaluate whether or not I keep AliensInTheApple going, or change its name, or just say “So long, and thanks for all the fish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manitou Cliff Dwellings</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/09/11/manitou-cliff-dwellings/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/09/11/manitou-cliff-dwellings/</guid>
      <description>After the Tschetter reunion we stopped at the Manitou cliff dwellings museum on our way to visit Ben’s cousin Erica and her family in Colorado Springs.
Call me thick, but I only just realised after reading wikipedia that the cliff dwellings are not original, but instead have been relocated to their current location.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Return to the Roadtrip: On to the Tschetter Reunion</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/08/27/return-to-the-roadtrip-on-to-the-tschetter-reunion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/08/27/return-to-the-roadtrip-on-to-the-tschetter-reunion/</guid>
      <description>Some of you might recall that it was at the Tschetter reunion (Ben’s mum’s side of the family) that my laptop hard drive died, so I lost photos of the first half of that stop as well, which is a real shame because Ben’s mum’s Uncle Herb and Aunt Susan came to visit one evening and I got some really nice shots of them, but hey, so’s life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On being home</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/08/15/on-being-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/08/15/on-being-home/</guid>
      <description>So yes, as Ben informed you about 2 weeks ago, we’re back in Christchurch! I can hardly believe it’s been two weeks, because it’s been so busy with unpacking and getting right into things here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We’re back</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/08/04/were-back-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/08/04/were-back-3/</guid>
      <description>We’ve arrived safely back in Christchurch, thanks to God. And our home really feels like home already, so thanks everyone for your welcome and your help!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photoless reporting is not quite my style</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/07/21/photoless-reporting-is-not-quite-my-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/07/21/photoless-reporting-is-not-quite-my-style/</guid>
      <description>I’m finding it hard to keep up the blogging while we’re on the road, as you’ve no doubt realised! Not that it’s going to stop me trying. I’ll start by giving a quick run down of what happened after the Hoyt reunion up to the point where I’ve got photos again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip stop 5: Hoyt Reunion in Georgia</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/07/13/roadtrip-stop-5-hoyt-reunion-in-georgia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/07/13/roadtrip-stop-5-hoyt-reunion-in-georgia/</guid>
      <description>In mid-June, we spent a fantastic week in Georgia with some fantastic people at our Hoyt family reunion. Uncle Stan and Aunt Nora hosted us very well. There were great activities, delicious food, lots of fun times joking around, playing games, catching up and having a blast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Knoxville and the Smoky Mountains</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/28/more-knoxville-and-the-smoky-mountains/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/28/more-knoxville-and-the-smoky-mountains/</guid>
      <description>We spent 10 nights in Knoxville with Ben’s Uncle Ron and Aunt Marti, and his cousins Hannah and Eva.
This happened already well over two weeks ago, and I’m only now getting around to telling y’all about it (can you tell I’m in the south?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whimsical</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/27/whimsical/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/27/whimsical/</guid>
      <description>I love this photo — I took it when we were in the Smoky Mountains with the Holders.
Consider this a teaser until I get a post up with the rest of our photos from our time in Knoxville.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Roadtrip, stop 2</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/10/the-roadtrip-stop-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/10/the-roadtrip-stop-2/</guid>
      <description>After our first stop in Connecticut with the Snoeks, we headed down to Philadelphia where we stayed with Lillian and Jeremy and visited with several friends over the course of the weekend.
On the way to Lillian and Jeremy we stopped and Sam and Emily Perez’s home, friends from our church in New York.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some people just can’t eat cake like normal people</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/30/some-people-just-cant-eat-cake-like-normal-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/30/some-people-just-cant-eat-cake-like-normal-people/</guid>
      <description>Some of you might remember Jeremy and Lillian’s bizarre cake eating rituals at their wedding ceremony in New Zealand. Well, it would seem the strangeness just keeps on going.
Just look at the mess they made of my beautiful lemon cake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Special time with Pappa</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/24/special-time-with-pappa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/24/special-time-with-pappa/</guid>
      <description>I think the Pennsylvanian countryside is just so beautiful. It seems very peaceful to me, perhaps because I’m usually on holiday when I’m there.
When we took Lizel there when she visited, Marica stayed with dear friends who took her to a ballet concert, so Esther got to be the only child for a weekend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My daddy is stronger than your daddy</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/16/my-daddy-is-stronger-than-your-daddy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/16/my-daddy-is-stronger-than-your-daddy/</guid>
      <description>I know I’m thoroughly biased, but this photo just melts my heart. Our girls sure are blessed to have such a wonderful daddy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Because we’re so normal</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/15/because-were-so-normal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/15/because-were-so-normal/</guid>
      <description>We sometimes have dinner wearing cabbage leaf hats.
(Well, only if I’m making coleslaw to go with our pulled pork and need to get rid of some cabbage leaves!)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marica turned 5</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/12/marica-turned-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/12/marica-turned-5/</guid>
      <description>How is it that they go from this…
to this…
so unbelievably fast?
Too fast, that’s what. I’m sure someone’s been speeding up the time.
Marica turned 5 in February, but when we were in New Zealand, my mum (Ouma to the kids) threw a birthday party for Marica.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reconnecting with friends and family</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/08/reconnecting-with-friends-and-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/08/reconnecting-with-friends-and-family/</guid>
      <description>When the girls and I were in New Zealand, we had quite the social time visiting friends and family. The kids got so used to going out and visiting people that if we had the odd morning where we weren’t going out they’d ask, “aren’t we going to visit someone today?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More wedding pictures</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/16/more-wedding-pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/16/more-wedding-pictures/</guid>
      <description>Well, I said I’d share some more wedding pictures when I got some time to get them on here. I didn’t get the time, but I made the time, so here they are.
The first lot of photos were taken outside in the harsh sunlight (always a bad move), so unfortunately everyone has sunglass shadows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeremy and Lillian’s wedding day</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/14/jeremy-and-lillians-wedding-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/14/jeremy-and-lillians-wedding-day/</guid>
      <description>On January the 21st Jeremy and Lillian tied the knot, and it was a beautiful day in all respects. It was lovely and sunny (even it if was a bit windy), everything went smoothly and it was just such a joyous day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s been 7 years</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/15/its-been-7-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/15/its-been-7-years/</guid>
      <description>Today Ben and I celebrate 7 wonderful years of marriage. I can truly say that it gets better, deeper, and more beautiful to be married to Ben every single year. God has been so faithful and good to us by blessing our marriage, and we are thankful to Him for His enduring love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pics from Jeremy’s bachelor party</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/14/pics-from-jeremys-bachelor-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/14/pics-from-jeremys-bachelor-party/</guid>
      <description>Last Saturday afternoon and evening, a few of Jeremy’s Philadelphia friends organized a bachelor party for him. They captured him, got in a little bit of trouble with the Philly police, and drove him blind-folded all the way to New York, where I joined them for dinner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting excited about Christmas</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/12/getting-excited-about-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/12/getting-excited-about-christmas/</guid>
      <description>I love the month of December here in New York — I think it’s even my favourite time of the year, even better than beautiful spring-time April. It’s cold, but everyone seems to be in good spirits (as opposed to grumpy January!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent is here!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/10/advent-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/10/advent-is-here/</guid>
      <description>I started the blog post draft a few weeks back, and now the season of Advent is about halfway through. Last year we decided to start celebrating Advent in a more deliberate way, building the excitement until Christmas, and enjoying the anticipation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting into the homeschooling groove</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/05/getting-into-the-homeschooling-groove/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/05/getting-into-the-homeschooling-groove/</guid>
      <description>Since Marica started preschool two days a week last year, I have been doing some casual schoolwork with her at home. When the school year finished and we decided to school her at home rather than send her to yet another school, we started making ‘school work’ more of a part of our daily routine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Esther’s turned two!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/01/esthers-turned-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/01/esthers-turned-two/</guid>
      <description>I was going to start by saying that Esther turned two just last week. But then I realised that it would almost be more accurate to say she turned two just last month. Sometimes I feel disoriented with how fast time goes — my head is still two weeks ago and my body, by default, is here and now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving yumminess</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/28/thanksgiving-yumminess/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/28/thanksgiving-yumminess/</guid>
      <description>Well, Thanksgiving came and went, and we had a lovely day. It was great to have a bonus day where Ben had the day off, and we enjoyed getting to know a friend from church a bit better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The beauty of gratitude</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/23/the-beauty-of-gratitude/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/23/the-beauty-of-gratitude/</guid>
      <description>What a great gift to have a whole feast day dedicated to giving thanks! I’m relishing the opportunity to celebrate Thanksgiving while we’re here in the States. It might even be a tradition we take home to New Zealand with us!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More good times</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/17/more-good-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/17/more-good-times/</guid>
      <description>Our last overnight stop on our roadtrip with my parents was at Mr &amp;amp; Mrs Brauning’s place. Mr Brauning is a pastor who came and filled our pulpit for a few months while our home congregation was vacant and the Braunings are loved by many back home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stop 3 on the trip</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/14/stop-3-on-the-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/14/stop-3-on-the-trip/</guid>
      <description>Just a little note: I’m not blogging real-time. I think I might have blogged about something on the same day it happened about twice in the whole time I’ve had this blog. I just don’t have the luxury of lots of time to be able to do that!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magnificent Niagara Falls</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/10/magnificent-niagara-falls/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/10/magnificent-niagara-falls/</guid>
      <description>After our 3 nights in the Adirondack mountains, we drove to Niagara Falls. The scenery on the way was beautiful!
Crossing the border into Canada.
We arrived on a cold, windy, overcast afternoon, but didn’t know whether the weather would clear up over the weekend, so decided to brave it and go look at the falls regardless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October, a wonderful month with family</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/03/october-a-wonderful-month-with-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/03/october-a-wonderful-month-with-family/</guid>
      <description>For most of the month of October we had my parents visiting with us, and we had a very good time together.
The highlight of their time here was probably our road trip that we took to the Adirondack mountains, Niagara Falls, Toronto and Pennsylvania to visit our friends the Tysons and the Braunings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guess who’s visiting us?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/10/guess-whos-visiting-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/10/guess-whos-visiting-us/</guid>
      <description>My parents! Right now I’m at home waiting for Ben to bring my parents home from the airport. We’re very excited to have them visit! We’re looking forward to taking a road trip with them while they’re here up to the Adirondacks, Niagara Falls and Pennsylvania.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road trip report, Day 1 and 2</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/24/road-trip-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/24/road-trip-report/</guid>
      <description>So like I said, Margaret took me and the girls on a week-long road trip (thanks, Gary!) and boy did we have fun! There was a good amount of banter and hilarity and also some really good conversations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A pre-engagement visit</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/07/a-pre-engagement-visit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/07/a-pre-engagement-visit/</guid>
      <description>Now that you all know that Lillian and Jeremy are engaged, we can all happily say “Hooray!”. Lillian was here for a very short visit (just under 2 weeks) and flew into JFK, so we got the privilege of hosting the two of them for a few nights before they went off to Philadelphia to go get engaged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking kids on a photo shoot can be interesting</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/03/taking-kids-on-a-photo-shoot-can-be-interesting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/03/taking-kids-on-a-photo-shoot-can-be-interesting/</guid>
      <description>And also pretty fun.
Perhaps “photo shoot” is too formal a title for what we did with Jeremy and Lillian, but I still tried to get a heap of photos while at the same time trying to keep an eye on two speedy escape artists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now for the black and white engagement pics</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/01/now-for-the-black-and-white-engagement-pics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/01/now-for-the-black-and-white-engagement-pics/</guid>
      <description>As I said earlier, my previous post kept freezing up because I had too many photos in there, so I instead made the first post the colour post and this one the black&amp;amp;white post. I personally often prefer black and white, so this was fun for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The last one bites the dust</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/01/the-last-one-bites-the-dust/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/01/the-last-one-bites-the-dust/</guid>
      <description>But that makes it sound like it’s a bad thing when it is indeed a very happy thing — the last of 8 children getting married. Yes, that’s right, Ben’s little sister, Lillian, is engaged to be married to a certain Mr Jeremy Fisher, uh, I mean Mr Jeremy L Eshelman!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three peas in  a pod</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/17/three-peas-in-a-pod/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/17/three-peas-in-a-pod/</guid>
      <description>We recently had our friends Rick and Susanna here for dinner while their two oldest kids were visiting grandparents and when bathtime rolled around we stuck our 3 little blondies in the bath. I just had to share the cuteness!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy hammocking</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/01/happy-hammocking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/01/happy-hammocking/</guid>
      <description>Hammocking is a verb, didn’t you know? It does not involve mocking ham. Ham is too good to mock.
Enjoying some mum-and-daughter time in the hammock a while back when we were at Jeremy’s place in Philadelphia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How high do your kids rank?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/27/how-high-do-your-kids-rank/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/27/how-high-do-your-kids-rank/</guid>
      <description>Another excellent article from Rachel Jankovic. A good look at how society views children, where your children rank in your priorities, and the calling of motherhood. I encourage you to go read it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to Mr. J</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/15/visit-to-mr-j/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/15/visit-to-mr-j/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weekends ago, we visited our good friend, Jeremy, in Philadelphia.
What a blast — we did some sight-seeing, but also my favourite pastime: having good discussions over good food.
There was of course also an appropriate amount of teasing which Jeremy thrived upon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 4th of July!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/08/the-4th-of-july-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/08/the-4th-of-july-2/</guid>
      <description>This year the 4th of July fell on a Monday so we were very happy that Ben got the day off. We spent a relaxing morning at home and in the afternoon went to Manhattan to view the Macy’s 4th of July fireworks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to Connecticut</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/04/visit-to-connecticut/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/04/visit-to-connecticut/</guid>
      <description>A few weekends ago we drove up to Connecticut to visit fellow Kiwis, Ron and Judy Snoek and their son Troy. They very kindly hosted us for a night with some good ol’ home-like hospitality. It was so nice to spend time with them and get to know them a bit better (I (Franci) hadn’t even met them before this!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shenanigans with Sharon</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/01/shenanigans-with-sharon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/01/shenanigans-with-sharon/</guid>
      <description>Ben’s cousin Sharon visited us over Memorial Weekend, and we had a lot of fun packing in as much sight-seeing as was practical! Here is some photographic evidence.
We walked the Brooklyn Bridge,
sat on cool seats on the way to the Ferry terminal,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful encouragement for the mothers among us</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/29/beautiful-encouragement-for-the-mothers-among-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/29/beautiful-encouragement-for-the-mothers-among-us/</guid>
      <description>One of my favourite authors and bloggers (I’ve raved about her before) was invited by Desiring God ministries to write an article for them. I found it very encouraging and helpful, and I hope all the mothers who visit this blog will read this article — you will not be sorry!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glimpses into the last couple of weeks</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/27/glimpses-into-the-last-couple-of-weeks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/27/glimpses-into-the-last-couple-of-weeks/</guid>
      <description>I don’t know why the weeks go by so fast. I have a bunch of photos to share with you from when Ben’s cousin Sharon visited us a month ago, our trip to Connecticut 2 weeks ago and our trip to visit Jeremy in Philadelphia last weekend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer is here!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/16/summer-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/16/summer-is-here/</guid>
      <description>And we’ve well and truly been out and about enjoying it. We’ve only had two very hot days and for the rest of the time it has been pretty much perfect weather (25 - 30 C).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who sped up time?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/28/who-sped-up-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/28/who-sped-up-time/</guid>
      <description>How is it possible that we have been in New York City for a year already? Yes, everyone, it’s been a YEAR! When we arrived a year ago, I must admit that I viewed our ‘adventure’ with some trepidation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful Brooklyn Botanic Garden</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/21/beautiful-brooklyn-botanic-garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/21/beautiful-brooklyn-botanic-garden/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weeks ago, we went to the Brooklyn Botanic Garden with our friends Julie and Abby Murphy and Damaris and her 2 cute kids, Elijah and Sophia.
The gardens were amazingly beautiful and dressed in their Spring finest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marica the soccer player</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/19/marica-the-soccer-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/19/marica-the-soccer-player/</guid>
      <description>Friends of ours recently invited Marica to join a little informal ‘soccer’ team that will practice just until the start of the summer. Marica has loved her Saturday morning soccer practices and all the games the coach lets them play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brooklyn Bridge!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/14/brooklyn-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/14/brooklyn-bridge/</guid>
      <description>When Ben’s dad was here back in April we got a fair bit of sight-seeing done, which even included some things I hadn’t seen or done before, which was pretty exciting. One of those things was walking the Brooklyn Bridge, which is just one of those things you have to do in New York City.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About servants and serving</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/07/about-servants/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/07/about-servants/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been thinking about my job (as a mother) a fair bit recently. After Monday’s blog post, I felt that I might have given the wrong impression of what life around here looks like. I have a policy (with myself) not to complain or whine on this blog — not about big city life and not about my family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some other New York sights (and eats) with Hannah and Eva</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/05/some-other-new-york-sights-and-eats-with-hannah-and-eva/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/05/some-other-new-york-sights-and-eats-with-hannah-and-eva/</guid>
      <description>As you can tell, I’m waaay behind on sight-seeing posts! When Hannah and Eva were here way back in March, we did quite a few fun things I haven’t shared here yet, so here’s a photo post of some of the things we did and ate!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beauty is in the eye of the beholder</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/02/beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/02/beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder/</guid>
      <description>Marica said I looked beautiful after she was finished making me beautiful. Ben came home and called me hideous. I’ll let you decide for yourself!
It was cold and rainy a fair bit back in March, so one day when Marica asked if she could make me pretty, I consented.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easter</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/29/easter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/29/easter/</guid>
      <description>Easter this year was probably the most different for us as a family than what we’ve had before. Ben didn’t get Good Friday off, so it was really strange not to be able to go to church together as a family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musings on New York, the weather, and teeth.</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/26/musings-on-new-york-the-weather-and-teeth/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/26/musings-on-new-york-the-weather-and-teeth/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been sharing a lot of photos and telling you about stuff we’ve seen and experienced lately (and there’s a lot more to come!), but I thought I’d just give you a little update on how we’re all doing, as well as some related thoughts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating Easter</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/18/celebrating-easter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/18/celebrating-easter/</guid>
      <description>Let me just start by saying that I loooove living in the northern hemisphere! The seasons and church calendar finally make sense! Christmas with snow, Easter with blossoms, summer holiday that doesn’t mix with Christmas. Celebrating Christmas here was great in that sense, and Easter is looking promising too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Up close and personal with Lady Liberty</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/16/up-close-and-personal-with-lady-liberty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/16/up-close-and-personal-with-lady-liberty/</guid>
      <description>The New Colossus By Emma Lazarus, 1883
Not like the brazen giant of Greek fame,
With conquering limbs astride from land to land;
Here at our sea-washed, sunset gates shall stand
A mighty woman with a torch, whose flame</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting The Cloisters</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/30/revisiting-the-cloisters/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/30/revisiting-the-cloisters/</guid>
      <description>When Ben’s cousins, Hannah and Eva, were here visiting with us, the three of us took a trip up into Manhattan to see The Cloisters and The Met (The Met will be in another post!).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheesecake and getting old</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/28/cheesecake-and-getting-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/28/cheesecake-and-getting-old/</guid>
      <description>Last Sunday (a week and a half ago, almost), I got another year older. It’s funny how birthday excitement has the tendency to wane as you get older! Though perhaps that’s not a good way for me to look at it — it would be better to think about being blessed with another year instead of having a hum-ho attitude of ‘oh, just another year’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scaling down</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/07/scaling-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/07/scaling-down/</guid>
      <description>Some of you have probably seen this coming, but this is just a little announcement to say that I’m going to scale back a bit on blogging. In fact, I’m scaling down whatever time I’m spending on the computer in general.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh yes, I have a blog.</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/02/oh-yes-i-have-a-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/02/oh-yes-i-have-a-blog/</guid>
      <description>That’s how it feels to me sometimes when I realise that all my scheduled posts have run out, and my drafts folder is looking a bit emaciated. We run this blog mainly to stay in contact with family and friends back home in New Zealand to share what we’ve been up to, what we’re thinking about and stuff we like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loving the Little Years</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/07/loving-the-little-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/07/loving-the-little-years/</guid>
      <description>I have recently been reading through Loving the Little Years by Rachel Jankovic. It is GOOD. Every single chapter encourages me and exhorts me and redirects my focus off myself and onto Christ. Off what other people think and onto Christ.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glitches do happen</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/15/glitches-do-happen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/15/glitches-do-happen/</guid>
      <description>For some reason our previous post about the happy occurrence of our 6th wedding anniversary had a few glitches — not the whole post I had done showed up, missing a kind of special part, and for some inexplicable reason comments were turned off (I’ve fixed that now).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Six blessed and beautiful years</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/15/six-blessed-and-beautiful-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/15/six-blessed-and-beautiful-years/</guid>
      <description>Today, 6 years ago, I married my best friend.
Life with Ben has been like a beautiful dance, a dance he leads to help us move forward as one. There has been the odd difficult patch because we are living life in a fallen world, after all, but on the whole it has been six years that God has packed with blessing upon blessing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Chocolate Monkster</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/13/the-chocolate-monkster/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/13/the-chocolate-monkster/</guid>
      <description>Since turning one, Esther has been introduced to the wonders of chocolate. She loves that stuff with a passion!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our first snowman</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/05/our-first-snowman/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/05/our-first-snowman/</guid>
      <description>It got seriously warm today (almost 10 degrees C), so we went into our snow-covered backyard and colonized it, turning the beautiful fresh snow into a snowman.
Our back “yard” before we started:
Laying the foundation (Marica supervising):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sight-seeing with Lillian</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/03/sight-seeing-with-lillian/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/03/sight-seeing-with-lillian/</guid>
      <description>In the few weeks that Lillian has been here we’ve done all sorts of things like Christmas baking, movie watching, eating good food and talking, but we’ve also done some sight-seeing. You can’t leave that out when you’re in New York, even if the weather is freezing!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our first New York Christmas</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/30/our-first-new-york-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/30/our-first-new-york-christmas/</guid>
      <description>This year was the first year our little family did not celebrate Christmas with grandparents. I was going to say that we didn’t celebrate with any extended family, but we do have Lillian here, so we’re not entirely family-less!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating Advent</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/21/celebrating-advent/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/21/celebrating-advent/</guid>
      <description>It’s December… This is my favourite time of the year! I love the anticipation of Christmas, the Christmas music (I’ve been listening to a lot of old school Christmas songs on Pandora and we’ve been through The Messiah quite a number of times now too!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stereotypes, monotony and pain</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/02/stereotypes-monotony-and-pain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/02/stereotypes-monotony-and-pain/</guid>
      <description>It all started on an adventurous Saturday, almost 2 weeks ago. I was excited and a little scared because I was going to be making my biggest driving trip yet — a half an hour drive to our pastor’s house in the south of Brooklyn for a ladies’ Bible study.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another update</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/29/another-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/29/another-update/</guid>
      <description>I’m just now home from a second trip to the hospital and feeling much better than last week! After getting home last week I couldn’t keep food down and felt dizzy all the time. We made a kind of last-minute decision to go to the Braunings after all and spent Friday night with them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Appendix-less Franci, an update</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/23/appendix-less-franci-an-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/23/appendix-less-franci-an-update/</guid>
      <description>Just letting any readers know that the surgeon was able to remove Franci’s inflamed appendix successfully. Apparently it was pretty close to bursting when they operated. She’s sore and tired, but seems to be recovering well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Appendix: Franci won’t have one for much longer</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/22/appendix/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/22/appendix/</guid>
      <description>We got the tummy bug over the weekend — fun for the whole family! But Franci’s “bug” hung around, and then got more and more painful. Turns out she has acute appendicitis. They’re going to cut her open tonight (might as well not “mince” words) and remove her appendix.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/22/thanksgiving/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/22/thanksgiving/</guid>
      <description>This week on Thursday it is Thanksgiving. I think it must be my favourite American holiday! A life that is full of thanksgiving is a happy one, no matter what the circumstances, and what can be better than once a year celebrating the good things God has given us with a great big feast?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snug as a bug…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/16/snug-as-a-bug/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/16/snug-as-a-bug/</guid>
      <description>in a front-pack on Pappa. Now if those silly teeth will just stop bothering me…
This cutie has cut a molar, even though she hasn’t even cut all her front teeth yet! She also seems to have found her voice, especially when her sister is giving her a hard time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Broadway and a birthday</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/09/broadway-and-a-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/09/broadway-and-a-birthday/</guid>
      <description>This past weekend was a full, but very enjoyable one.
On Friday night, our friend Rick babysat the kids while we went to see Billy Elliot on Broadway. We enjoyed our first Broadway experience. The “show” aspect at least — Ben will have more to say about the story later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A little summary</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/05/a-little-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/05/a-little-summary/</guid>
      <description>We’ve been in New York City for just a little over 5 months now. I can hardly believe it’s been that long, and on the other hand it feels much longer! I thought I’d use this post to update you in a bit more detail about how we’re doing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hoyt Street, Brooklyn</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/21/hoyt-street-brooklyn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/21/hoyt-street-brooklyn/</guid>
      <description>Hoyt is a fairly well-established name here in New York. Brooklyn even has a Hoyt Street, and there are two subway stations along it. It’s kinda fun to see our name popping up here and there!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happiness in a box</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/15/happiness-in-a-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/15/happiness-in-a-box/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday afternoon was pretty grey, but then the rainy gloom was seriously cheered up by a special package from Oupa and Ouma Voges. It was filled with special goodies for all of us. Just check this out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We’ve been a bit blah</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/08/weve-been-a-bit-blah/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/08/weve-been-a-bit-blah/</guid>
      <description>The weather has turned colder, there has been a lot of (cold) rain, I’ve unpacked the winter clothes, the heaters have had their first few runs and we’ve all gotten sick. Ben has only had a couple of days where he didn’t feel too great, and Marica’s only had a bit of a runny nose, but Esther’s gotten hit the hardest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend in Pottstown</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/07/weekend-in-pottstown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/07/weekend-in-pottstown/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend we visited Ben’s uncle Sherwood and aunt Sharon in Pottstown, near Philadelphia. It was a very nice restful weekend, just visiting and getting to know them a bit better. Their daughter, Esther, is away at college, but Jonathan was there and the kids loved playing with him — he’s really good with children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HannahHolder.com, fine art from a fine artist</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/20/hannah-holder-fine-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/20/hannah-holder-fine-art/</guid>
      <description>My cousin Hannah Holder has a lovely website detailing some of the fine art she has done (and can do). She now has her very own domain name, so browse on over to HannahHolder.com and see it for yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two nights &#43; 14 people &#43; 1 (small) New York apartment = Lots of fun!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/14/two-nights/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/14/two-nights/</guid>
      <description>It’s really hard to believe that it’s almost been two weeks since the van Wichens descended on our place. For those who don’t know, Laurel is Ben’s oldest sister and their family is touring the States for 10 weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A brief history of Hoyt</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/08/a-brief-history-of-hoyt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/08/a-brief-history-of-hoyt/</guid>
      <description>As far as I know, not many Hoyts in my extended family are into family history. I’m not exactly either, but it is interesting when you run across a bit of good old ancestry (actually, an old friend from Masterton put me onto most of this stuff).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
