<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2015s on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2015s on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/12/25/merry-christmas-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/12/25/merry-christmas-3/</guid>
      <description>To all the lovely readers of our blog, we wish you a very Merry Christmas! May you be blessed today and in the year to come.
God rest ye merry, gentlemen,
Let nothing you dismay</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The twelve days of Homeschooling</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/12/18/the-twelve-days-of-homeschooling/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/12/18/the-twelve-days-of-homeschooling/</guid>
      <description>A homeschool friend shared this video with me recently, and I got such a kick out of it, I just have to share it here too! Enjoy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips on travelling long-haul with little kids</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/12/11/tips-on-travelling-long-haul-with-little-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/12/11/tips-on-travelling-long-haul-with-little-kids/</guid>
      <description>As we prepare to take a trip back to NZ for Christmas, I’m looking back at this post again (originally posted in March 2012) to refresh my memory on what’s useful to take and what to do to make life easier when travelling long haul with kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple picking day</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/12/04/apple-picking-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/12/04/apple-picking-day/</guid>
      <description>On a lovely warm day back in October, the girls and I took a field trip to a farm about an hour’s drive from where we live to go apple and pumpkin picking. The weather was fantastic — it was nice and sunny and not too hot or cold, a real Goldilocks kind of day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Esther’s 6th birthday</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/11/27/esthers-6th-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/11/27/esthers-6th-birthday/</guid>
      <description>Esther turned 6 in November. Hard to believe, isn’t it?! Her birthday celebrations were spread out over two days — on Friday at co-op the kids sang Happy Birthday to her and she and Marica handed out cupcakes that Marica had baked (no, Mum, you’re not allowed to help me!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful autumn</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/11/20/beautiful-autumn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/11/20/beautiful-autumn/</guid>
      <description>I have a love-hate relationship with autumn. I love all the beautiful colors, the cooler weather and the fun things the season brings like apples, cinnamon, pumpkin pie and hot chocolate. But… autumn is the start of a long cold spell that only keeps getting worse for about 5 months before it starts getting better!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What we’re doing in homeschooling this year</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/11/13/what-were-doing-in-homeschooling-this-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/11/13/what-were-doing-in-homeschooling-this-year/</guid>
      <description>We’ve been back in the full swing of the regular school year for a few months now, and I must admit that I find it hard to make the time to blog. It’s great to have the routines of school, but it does leave very little time for extra things, like blogging and other fun stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CCEF’s 2015 conference</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/11/06/ccefs-2015-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/11/06/ccefs-2015-conference/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weekends ago, I had the amazing opportunity to travel down to Virginia Beach for this year’s CCEF (Christian Counseling and Educational Foundation) Conference. The topic of this year’s conference was Side by Side: How God helps us help each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marica’s newest yummy dish</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/10/30/maricas-newest-yummy-dish/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/10/30/maricas-newest-yummy-dish/</guid>
      <description>Marica recently got a cookbook out of the library and was looking through it one afternoon. She came to me and said, “I’m going to make Stromboli, and I don’t want you to help me.” Sure!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disclaimer</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/10/02/disclaimer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/10/02/disclaimer/</guid>
      <description>I was recently talking with Ben about a blogger whose blog I follow. I really respect her and appreciate her blog immensely, but the frequency with which she puts out quality blog posts about stuff they’ve done or made, and about the amazing things they do in their homeschool was making me feel like she must be some super woman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary of summer, part 4</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/09/25/summary-of-summer-part-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/09/25/summary-of-summer-part-4/</guid>
      <description>So, last week I mentioned how we traveled to Indiana for cousin Sharon’s and Vijo’s wedding in August. Despite the 13 hour trip each way, we were so happy that we could go and also that we could spend time with other Hoyt family members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A summary of summer, part 3</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/09/19/a-summary-of-summer-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/09/19/a-summary-of-summer-part-3/</guid>
      <description>August was filled to the brim with activity. We said goodbye to our Chinese exchange students, and celebrated Ben’s birthday.
We swam a few times in our friend’s nearby pool, but also did a fun day trip out to go swim at a water hole our friend Sarah knows about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A summary of summer, part 2</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/09/11/a-summary-of-summer-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/09/11/a-summary-of-summer-part-2/</guid>
      <description>A summary of summer, continued.
In July, we hosted the Holtslags, our pastor from NZ and his family, as well as James and Laura (James is Phillipa’s son, Laura is the Holtslags’ daughter). This time we sent them off to do sight-seeing by themselves, but we still got to have some good conversations over the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A summary of summer, part 1</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/09/04/a-summary-of-summer-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/09/04/a-summary-of-summer-part-1/</guid>
      <description>I know our blog posts have been a bit sporadic recently, but we’ve been up to all sorts of mischief. It’s summer after all! We’ve had playdates, we’ve played in the sprinklers, we’ve done lots of swimming, we’ve had sleep-overs, we’ve had visits to the library, we’ve had a couple of road trips, we’ve had homemade lemonade, iced tea and popsicles, eaten tonnes of watermelon and peaches and corn… you know… summer stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We’re still here…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/07/31/were-still-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/07/31/were-still-here/</guid>
      <description>I’m just taking a break from blogging to enjoy the summer, and spend time with visitors, the kids and to do all those fun activities that only happen in the summer. I hope to resume a regular blogging schedule again in late August.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homeschool field trip</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/07/10/homeschool-field-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/07/10/homeschool-field-trip/</guid>
      <description>One weekend in May we took the girls in to the Ancient Egyptian section of the Metropolitan Museum of Art, because in our history program we’d been studying Ancient Egypt. It was great to see many of the things we (including myself!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A peek at spring</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/07/03/a-peek-at-spring/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/07/03/a-peek-at-spring/</guid>
      <description>April seems like a long time ago… spring seems like a bit of a blur filled with the house buying process and then packing and getting ready to move. But it wasn’t all crazy — we made some time to go enjoy the nice weather outside too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our new place</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/06/26/our-new-place-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/06/26/our-new-place-2/</guid>
      <description>I thought it’s about time I showed you a photo of our new place. We moved in Memorial Day (with the help of some amazing and hard-working friends), and have managed to unpack all the boxes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changing things around</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/05/08/changing-things-around/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/05/08/changing-things-around/</guid>
      <description>You’ll probably have noticed that I’ve been playing around with new blog designs. And you’ll probably also be relieved to know that I’m done now, and that this is what the site will look like for the foreseeable future!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Win a copy of Side by Side!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/05/04/win-a-copy-of-side-by-side/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/05/04/win-a-copy-of-side-by-side/</guid>
      <description>If you are interested in winning a copy of Side by Side, you can click on this link to enter.
I had planned on including the link in my previous post, but completely forgot. You still have some time!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Side by Side</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/05/01/side-by-side/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/05/01/side-by-side/</guid>
      <description>I’m so glad to have been given the opportunity to review the book Side by Side by Jana Kelley. I met Jana back in 2004 when I spent half a year working in Sudan. Although Jana was not a part of the team I was working with, our paths crossed fairly regularly: we taught a conversational English class together at a tea house for women; and I taught and helped out at the school where her boys attended.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Well done, good and faithful servant</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/04/24/well-done-good-and-faithful-servant/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/04/24/well-done-good-and-faithful-servant/</guid>
      <description>To you, commuter on the 6.15am bus
who study on spinning wheels for an hour before a long day of work:
Well done, good and faithful servant.
To you, mother of small children
who have wiped more noses and bottoms and floors than you could count:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enjoying a spot of sewing</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/04/17/enjoying-a-spot-of-sewing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/04/17/enjoying-a-spot-of-sewing/</guid>
      <description>The week before Easter I decided that I’d love for the girls to have new dresses for Easter (which is a bit of an American church tradition, it seems to me), but I really didn’t want to fork out $30 a dress (times three!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April Fool’s Dinner</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/04/03/april-fools-dinner/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/04/03/april-fools-dinner/</guid>
      <description>A few years back, on a whim, I decided to start a fun tradition for April Fool’s Day dinner: dessert for dinner (and no need to have dinner for dessert!). Turns out the kids think this is great, but the adults give a little groan at the thought.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lego Tower version 1</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/03/28/lego-tower-version-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/03/28/lego-tower-version-1/</guid>
      <description>Marica and Esther and I (Ben) have been playing with Lego on Saturdays. Marica’s built up a decent collection of small Lego sets over the past several birthdays and Christmases, and building things with them is one of my favourite inside things to do with the kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black and white trees</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/03/20/black-and-white-trees/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/03/20/black-and-white-trees/</guid>
      <description>I love the way leaf-less trees look so stark in black and white.
These photos were taken in Prospect Park, Brooklyn a couple of years back.
And this one in Lancaster County.
March was heralded in by a snowstorm, and it looked like this in front of our house just a couple of weeks ago:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>She’s 8!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/03/13/beautiful-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/03/13/beautiful-snow/</guid>
      <description>Marica turned 8 in February. It’s been so fun to see her grow up a bit more over the last year! I’ve especially enjoyed seeing her sense of humor develop a bit more (starting to understand and appreciate puns and subtleties), and to see her get a little bit more mature and responsible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Medieval Feast</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/03/06/a-medieval-feast/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/03/06/a-medieval-feast/</guid>
      <description>Back in January, the homeschool co-op we attend put on a Medieval Feast. The organizers did a most spectacular job with the decorations, food and everything else that goes into organizing a big event like this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful snow</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/03/03/beautiful-snow-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/03/03/beautiful-snow-2/</guid>
      <description>Last week we had another bit of snow. (That was the snow before today’s snow, and Sunday’s snow, and then the two snows before that.) It seems every time Boston gets a foot or more of snow, we get about 2 or 3 inches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You can’t see me!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/02/20/you-cant-see-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/02/20/you-cant-see-me/</guid>
      <description>At lunch the other day, Laurelin was playing peek-a-boo with her bib, which was hilariously cute, because she’d stare out the neck hole at us thinking she was invisible!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s been a decade</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/02/13/its-been-a-decade/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/02/13/its-been-a-decade/</guid>
      <description>Like I said last week, it’s been cold here! However, Ben and I did have a blessed little escape from the cold back in January for 3 nights, when we eloped to Jamaica while my parents looked after our kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby, it’s cold outside!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/02/06/baby-its-cold-outside/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/02/06/baby-its-cold-outside/</guid>
      <description>Last night the girls had a lovely surprise of some cards from their cousins (thanks, Ilse, Estelle and Hendrik!). What was funny to us was that they asked how our summer has been, which of course, it very much has not been.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas 2014</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/30/christmas-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/30/christmas-2014/</guid>
      <description>This year was the first year I hosted all of Christmas (meaning both our Christmas Eve and Christmas Day celebrations), and it was fun! We had my parents with us, which was very special, and we also hosted James and Laura Williams and Laura’s friend, Ella.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joyous December</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/23/joyous-december/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/23/joyous-december/</guid>
      <description>December is probably my favourite month of the year. I love the anticipation of Christmas, celebrating Advent, and all that it means: the King of the Universe becoming man to reconcile and restore us to Himself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homemade nutella</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/16/homemade-nutella/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/16/homemade-nutella/</guid>
      <description>I’ve always wanted to try making a version of Nutella at home, so recently I tried it. There are oodles of recipes online, and the one I tried is from here. It calls for coconut sugar, which I think is a bit of a fad food (not to mention its sustainability is questionable), so I used regular sugar and maple syrup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Entrepreneurial Fair</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/09/the-entrepreneurial-fair/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/09/the-entrepreneurial-fair/</guid>
      <description>The Co-op that we attend had an Entrepreneurial Fair early in December, and as much as I would have liked to just be a spectator, my kids were burning to sell stuff (surprise, surprise). So, we made Christmas ornaments, some chocolates and gingerbread men.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autumn baby</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/02/autumn-baby-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/02/autumn-baby-2/</guid>
      <description>For our November Frog Pond class, I went a little click-happy with Laurelin while the older girls were busy. She was in a particularly good mood and I was able to get quite a few happy shots of her outside, enjoying the leaves and dirt.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
