<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogging on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/category/blogging/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogging on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/category/blogging/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Disclaimer</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/10/02/disclaimer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/10/02/disclaimer/</guid>
      <description>I was recently talking with Ben about a blogger whose blog I follow. I really respect her and appreciate her blog immensely, but the frequency with which she puts out quality blog posts about stuff they’ve done or made, and about the amazing things they do in their homeschool was making me feel like she must be some super woman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changing things around</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/05/08/changing-things-around/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/05/08/changing-things-around/</guid>
      <description>You’ll probably have noticed that I’ve been playing around with new blog designs. And you’ll probably also be relieved to know that I’m done now, and that this is what the site will look like for the foreseeable future!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I’m in denial</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/07/06/im-in-denial/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/07/06/im-in-denial/</guid>
      <description>Two days ago, I was sitting on my bed editing some photos in Picasa, having just cleared my camera memory stick of about 500 more photos and video clips. The total number of photos taken on our roadtrip so far were well over a thousand and I was doing well keeping up to date with deleting the bad ones, editing the ones that needed a bit of lightening or the like, even if I haven’t been the greatest at updating the blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I met The Pioneer Woman!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/05/i-met-the-pioneer-woman/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/05/i-met-the-pioneer-woman/</guid>
      <description>I recently had the fun experience of going to a book signing. It was fun, because I got to head out by myself for an evening, and fun because I got to meet someone semi-famous. I say semi-famous because if you don’t frequent food blogs or watch food shows on TV, you’ve probably never heard of The Pioneer Woman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We’re back!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/09/were-back-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/09/were-back-2/</guid>
      <description>The girls and I arrived safely back in New York City on Monday night after three flights over 26 hours. We had a fantastic time back in New Zealand reconnecting with friends and family and enjoying Jeremy and Lillian’s wedding, but we’re very happy to be home with Ben again!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s been 7 years</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/15/its-been-7-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/15/its-been-7-years/</guid>
      <description>Today Ben and I celebrate 7 wonderful years of marriage. I can truly say that it gets better, deeper, and more beautiful to be married to Ben every single year. God has been so faithful and good to us by blessing our marriage, and we are thankful to Him for His enduring love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AliensInTheApple.com</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/30/aliensintheapple-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/30/aliensintheapple-com/</guid>
      <description>It’s kinda subtle, but our blog just moved from aliensintheapple.wordpress.com to our own domain name, aliensintheapple.com. All the old links and addresses will still work (and redirect here), so you don’t need to update anything. Enjoy our dot-com!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guess who’s visiting us?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/10/guess-whos-visiting-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/10/guess-whos-visiting-us/</guid>
      <description>My parents! Right now I’m at home waiting for Ben to bring my parents home from the airport. We’re very excited to have them visit! We’re looking forward to taking a road trip with them while they’re here up to the Adirondacks, Niagara Falls and Pennsylvania.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A little holiday</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/21/a-little-holiday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/21/a-little-holiday/</guid>
      <description>Hey everyone, I’m going on a little computer holiday for the next week or so, so you won’t be getting blog posts, and I most likely won’t be replying to emails. If you need to contact me, I’ll probably be keeping skype on so you can contact me that way, or email Ben, or phone me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When the summer gives you heat…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/10/when-the-summer-gives-you-heat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/10/when-the-summer-gives-you-heat/</guid>
      <description>eat popsicles!
It’s so delicious you have to let your arm and chin taste some too.
It hurts when you bite cold stuff with your teeth!
Look, Mum, a plane! (Depending on the wind direction, we get them coming over every 2 minutes or so to land at JFK.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful encouragement for the mothers among us</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/29/beautiful-encouragement-for-the-mothers-among-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/29/beautiful-encouragement-for-the-mothers-among-us/</guid>
      <description>One of my favourite authors and bloggers (I’ve raved about her before) was invited by Desiring God ministries to write an article for them. I found it very encouraging and helpful, and I hope all the mothers who visit this blog will read this article — you will not be sorry!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scaling down</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/07/scaling-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/07/scaling-down/</guid>
      <description>Some of you have probably seen this coming, but this is just a little announcement to say that I’m going to scale back a bit on blogging. In fact, I’m scaling down whatever time I’m spending on the computer in general.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh yes, I have a blog.</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/02/oh-yes-i-have-a-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/02/oh-yes-i-have-a-blog/</guid>
      <description>That’s how it feels to me sometimes when I realise that all my scheduled posts have run out, and my drafts folder is looking a bit emaciated. We run this blog mainly to stay in contact with family and friends back home in New Zealand to share what we’ve been up to, what we’re thinking about and stuff we like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glitches do happen</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/15/glitches-do-happen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/15/glitches-do-happen/</guid>
      <description>For some reason our previous post about the happy occurrence of our 6th wedding anniversary had a few glitches — not the whole post I had done showed up, missing a kind of special part, and for some inexplicable reason comments were turned off (I’ve fixed that now).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stereotypes, monotony and pain</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/02/stereotypes-monotony-and-pain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/02/stereotypes-monotony-and-pain/</guid>
      <description>It all started on an adventurous Saturday, almost 2 weeks ago. I was excited and a little scared because I was going to be making my biggest driving trip yet — a half an hour drive to our pastor’s house in the south of Brooklyn for a ladies’ Bible study.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking a little break</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/23/taking-a-little-break/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/23/taking-a-little-break/</guid>
      <description>Just thought I’d let everyone know that we’re taking a little blogging holiday over the Thanksgiving break. We’ll be back next week!
I’m also then going to a 3-day a week blogging schedule. I’m finding it a bit difficult to keep up with the demands of a household with 2 small children as well as rolling out a blog post per day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/22/thanksgiving/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/22/thanksgiving/</guid>
      <description>This week on Thursday it is Thanksgiving. I think it must be my favourite American holiday! A life that is full of thanksgiving is a happy one, no matter what the circumstances, and what can be better than once a year celebrating the good things God has given us with a great big feast?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your feedback, please</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/27/your-feedback-please/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/27/your-feedback-please/</guid>
      <description>With this post, I’m going to ask our subscribers and readers to give us some feedback.
We normally post stuff like what we’ve been up to, interesting or funny things we’ve seen, photos of the kids and stuff like that, but I was thinking it would be nice to know some of your suggestions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My October grocery challenge</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/05/my-october-grocery-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/05/my-october-grocery-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes I feel like challenging myself in areas I’m not very good at. Like spending a small amount of money on groceries. Which is why it is a challenge! Here’s what I’m doing:
I’ve decided to try to reach the end of October and spend no more than $100 on groceries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out of action for a week</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/30/out-of-action-for-a-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/30/out-of-action-for-a-week/</guid>
      <description>Tomorrow, Lord willing, we move into our apartment. While this is great, it does however mean that we will be without internet access for a week. Actually, I’ll be without internet access for a week because Ben will still be able to check email and stuff at work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subscribing to this blog</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/26/subscribing-to-this-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/26/subscribing-to-this-blog/</guid>
      <description>I know that a number of you read our blog, and thanks for that! It’s nice to know that people are interested in staying in contact with us.
Though, as you’ve probably noticed by now, we certainly don’t post everyday (our lives aren’t that interesting!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/04/26/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/04/26/welcome/</guid>
      <description>So we’re going overseas in a month and, just to be different like everyone else, we’re starting a blog.
We’re hoping to post updates about how it’s all going, and about life in the Big Apple.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
