<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Roadtrip on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/category/the-roadtrip/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The Roadtrip on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/category/the-roadtrip/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip: Los Angeles</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/11/05/roadtrip-los-angeles/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/11/05/roadtrip-los-angeles/</guid>
      <description>It’s really happened! This is my last post of our roadtrip, only 16 months after the event. Shocking. Oh well, a beautiful baby girl has been added to our family since then and life’s been busy — that’s the way it is sometimes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip: San Francisco</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/10/14/roadtrip-san-francisco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/10/14/roadtrip-san-francisco/</guid>
      <description>We only had one day in San Francisco for sight-seeing, so naturally we didn’t see everything on the list, but we still saw a whole bunch of things!
We saw Alcatraz in the distance:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yosemite!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/08/09/yosemite/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/08/09/yosemite/</guid>
      <description>Yo’s Mite. That’s how I always thought you pronounced Yosemite (having only ever seen it written). Now I know better. Just think Yo’s Cemetery without the ‘r’ and you’re set. :-)
One of the many things I love about the States is how varied the scenery is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip: Mono Lake</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/07/30/roadtrip-mono-lake/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/07/30/roadtrip-mono-lake/</guid>
      <description>I’m determined to finish the posts of our roadtrip, despite it now being almost exactly a year since we’ve been back in New Zealand.
After our stop in Lone Pine, we drove north to Yosemite National Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip: Lone Pine</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/04/09/roadtrip-lone-pine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/04/09/roadtrip-lone-pine/</guid>
      <description>The next stop couldn’t have been more different from Las Vegas. Tranquil, rural, isolated, pretty much nobody around, right in nature, and no electricity! We stayed the night in a little cabin/tent outside a small town called Lone Pine, between the Death Valley and the Sierra Nevada Mountains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip: Las Vegas</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/03/19/roadtrip-las-vegas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/03/19/roadtrip-las-vegas/</guid>
      <description>I know there are people who love Vegas. I find this difficult to understand because we didn’t enjoy it at all! It was like a sleazy version of Times Square, but it had good, cheap accommodation that was en route to our next destination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Continuing the roadtrip posts: A visit to Phoenix</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/03/03/continuing-the-roadtrip-posts-a-visit-to-phoenix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/03/03/continuing-the-roadtrip-posts-a-visit-to-phoenix/</guid>
      <description>I know that I stopped our roadtrip posts rather abruptly last year, and for good reason, but I really do want to finish the posts before the baby arrives. That equates to six more posts over the next 3 months — surely I could do that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Grand Canyon</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/11/22/the-grand-canyon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/11/22/the-grand-canyon/</guid>
      <description>No tourist’s visit to the west of the U.S. is complete without a stop at the Grand Canyon, and we were no exception. We stayed in a little village (consisting mostly of the motel and gift shop) called Cameron for a couple of nights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Driving through Monument Valley</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/11/07/driving-through-monument-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/11/07/driving-through-monument-valley/</guid>
      <description>After our time in Moab and Arches National Park, we traveled south to the Grand Canyon. What we didn’t realise was that our road would take us right through Monument Valley, a beautiful and dramatic piece of creation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A visit to Moab and Arches National Park</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/10/25/a-visit-to-moab-and-arches-national-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/10/25/a-visit-to-moab-and-arches-national-park/</guid>
      <description>One of the scenic highlights of our roadtrip was the state of Utah, where we went to Arches National Park, and drove through Monument Valley on our way to the Grand Canyon. We both loved the Grand Canyon (post still coming!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garden of the Gods at sunrise</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/10/09/garden-of-the-gods-at-sunrise/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/10/09/garden-of-the-gods-at-sunrise/</guid>
      <description>When we were visiting the Boonzaaijers’ in Colorado Springs, I decided to get up early one morning to go and take some photos of the Garden of the Gods. I had heard that it was particularly beautiful at sunrise, so I got up at 5am and headed on down there, just as the sky was changing colour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to the Boonzaaijers’</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/09/19/visit-to-the-boonzaaijers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/09/19/visit-to-the-boonzaaijers/</guid>
      <description>So, getting around to posting these last roadtrip posts have crawled to a terribly slow pace, but I’m determined to finish them up. When I get to that point, I’ll evaluate whether or not I keep AliensInTheApple going, or change its name, or just say “So long, and thanks for all the fish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manitou Cliff Dwellings</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/09/11/manitou-cliff-dwellings/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/09/11/manitou-cliff-dwellings/</guid>
      <description>After the Tschetter reunion we stopped at the Manitou cliff dwellings museum on our way to visit Ben’s cousin Erica and her family in Colorado Springs.
Call me thick, but I only just realised after reading wikipedia that the cliff dwellings are not original, but instead have been relocated to their current location.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Return to the Roadtrip: On to the Tschetter Reunion</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/08/27/return-to-the-roadtrip-on-to-the-tschetter-reunion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/08/27/return-to-the-roadtrip-on-to-the-tschetter-reunion/</guid>
      <description>Some of you might recall that it was at the Tschetter reunion (Ben’s mum’s side of the family) that my laptop hard drive died, so I lost photos of the first half of that stop as well, which is a real shame because Ben’s mum’s Uncle Herb and Aunt Susan came to visit one evening and I got some really nice shots of them, but hey, so’s life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photoless reporting is not quite my style</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/07/21/photoless-reporting-is-not-quite-my-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/07/21/photoless-reporting-is-not-quite-my-style/</guid>
      <description>I’m finding it hard to keep up the blogging while we’re on the road, as you’ve no doubt realised! Not that it’s going to stop me trying. I’ll start by giving a quick run down of what happened after the Hoyt reunion up to the point where I’ve got photos again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip stop 5: Hoyt Reunion in Georgia</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/07/13/roadtrip-stop-5-hoyt-reunion-in-georgia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/07/13/roadtrip-stop-5-hoyt-reunion-in-georgia/</guid>
      <description>In mid-June, we spent a fantastic week in Georgia with some fantastic people at our Hoyt family reunion. Uncle Stan and Aunt Nora hosted us very well. There were great activities, delicious food, lots of fun times joking around, playing games, catching up and having a blast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I’m in denial</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/07/06/im-in-denial/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/07/06/im-in-denial/</guid>
      <description>Two days ago, I was sitting on my bed editing some photos in Picasa, having just cleared my camera memory stick of about 500 more photos and video clips. The total number of photos taken on our roadtrip so far were well over a thousand and I was doing well keeping up to date with deleting the bad ones, editing the ones that needed a bit of lightening or the like, even if I haven’t been the greatest at updating the blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip, stop 4: Atlanta</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/30/roadtrip-stop-4-atlanta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/30/roadtrip-stop-4-atlanta/</guid>
      <description>After visiting the Holders in Knoxville, TN, we travelled down to Atlanta. For some reason our GPS took us on the scenic route instead of the Interstate, which was a nice change of pace and a very beautiful drive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Knoxville and the Smoky Mountains</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/28/more-knoxville-and-the-smoky-mountains/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/28/more-knoxville-and-the-smoky-mountains/</guid>
      <description>We spent 10 nights in Knoxville with Ben’s Uncle Ron and Aunt Marti, and his cousins Hannah and Eva.
This happened already well over two weeks ago, and I’m only now getting around to telling y’all about it (can you tell I’m in the south?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whimsical</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/27/whimsical/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/27/whimsical/</guid>
      <description>I love this photo — I took it when we were in the Smoky Mountains with the Holders.
Consider this a teaser until I get a post up with the rest of our photos from our time in Knoxville.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Roadtrip, stop 2</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/10/the-roadtrip-stop-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/10/the-roadtrip-stop-2/</guid>
      <description>After our first stop in Connecticut with the Snoeks, we headed down to Philadelphia where we stayed with Lillian and Jeremy and visited with several friends over the course of the weekend.
On the way to Lillian and Jeremy we stopped and Sam and Emily Perez’s home, friends from our church in New York.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The start of The Roadtrip</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/06/the-start-of-the-roadtrip/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/06/the-start-of-the-roadtrip/</guid>
      <description>We had a rather stressful start to our roadtrip. I was overly optimistic (or foolish?) and hoped that everything might just fit into 6 suitcases plus a bunch of little bits and pieces. My reasoning for this was that I couldn’t see us parting with much more — I only kept the things I really wanted to and had gotten rid of more than felt comfortable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We’ve hit the road!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/04/weve-hit-the-road/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/04/weve-hit-the-road/</guid>
      <description>The last week has been a crazy whirlwind of activity. We got rid of a lot of stuff, selling some things on Craigslist, selling a bunch of things at our stoop sale and giving loads of stuff away.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
