<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Christchurch on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/category/christchurch/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Christchurch on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/category/christchurch/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Going, going, (almost) gone!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/02/19/going-going-almost-gone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/02/19/going-going-almost-gone/</guid>
      <description>We’re on our way to the States: our house is under offer, we’ve traveled to Auckland and have had our Green Cards approved, and tomorrow, Lord willing, we fly out to New York.
The last few weeks have been a super busy time, and a bit of an emotional roller coaster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gearing up to go</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/02/10/gearing-up-to-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/02/10/gearing-up-to-go/</guid>
      <description>The last few weeks have gotten exponentially busier as we’re getting ready for our move back to the States. It is strange how something can feel so unreal even in the midst of the busyness. I have days where it’s almost a surprise to me when people ask when we’re leaving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On being home</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/08/15/on-being-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/08/15/on-being-home/</guid>
      <description>So yes, as Ben informed you about 2 weeks ago, we’re back in Christchurch! I can hardly believe it’s been two weeks, because it’s been so busy with unpacking and getting right into things here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We’re back</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/08/04/were-back-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/08/04/were-back-3/</guid>
      <description>We’ve arrived safely back in Christchurch, thanks to God. And our home really feels like home already, so thanks everyone for your welcome and your help!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A few post-earthquake photos</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/22/a-few-post-earthquake-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/22/a-few-post-earthquake-photos/</guid>
      <description>This is my last post about my trip to Christchurch in January. It’s about time, I think! This post is largely for our US readers who have expressed interest in the earthquake side of things back home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marica turned 5</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/12/marica-turned-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/12/marica-turned-5/</guid>
      <description>How is it that they go from this…
to this…
so unbelievably fast?
Too fast, that’s what. I’m sure someone’s been speeding up the time.
Marica turned 5 in February, but when we were in New Zealand, my mum (Ouma to the kids) threw a birthday party for Marica.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reconnecting with friends and family</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/08/reconnecting-with-friends-and-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/08/reconnecting-with-friends-and-family/</guid>
      <description>When the girls and I were in New Zealand, we had quite the social time visiting friends and family. The kids got so used to going out and visiting people that if we had the odd morning where we weren’t going out they’d ask, “aren’t we going to visit someone today?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lovely lavender, and a bee to boot</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/23/lovely-lavender-and-a-bee-to-boot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/23/lovely-lavender-and-a-bee-to-boot/</guid>
      <description>I’ve got so many photos I’d like to share from my time in New Zealand, but time is eluding me. The photos in the post today were taken in Christchurch, in the new Cashel Mall where they have a mall made out of shipping containers that have been refurbished, and looks way better than it sounds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More wedding pictures</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/16/more-wedding-pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/16/more-wedding-pictures/</guid>
      <description>Well, I said I’d share some more wedding pictures when I got some time to get them on here. I didn’t get the time, but I made the time, so here they are.
The first lot of photos were taken outside in the harsh sunlight (always a bad move), so unfortunately everyone has sunglass shadows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeremy and Lillian’s wedding day</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/14/jeremy-and-lillians-wedding-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/14/jeremy-and-lillians-wedding-day/</guid>
      <description>On January the 21st Jeremy and Lillian tied the knot, and it was a beautiful day in all respects. It was lovely and sunny (even it if was a bit windy), everything went smoothly and it was just such a joyous day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just do the next thing</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/24/just-do-the-next-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/24/just-do-the-next-thing/</guid>
      <description>There are times in life when we get overwhelmed. Sometimes we have too much work to do, sometimes we’re ill, sometimes we’re just dog tired, sometimes earthquakes strike. The world keeps spinning, life carries on and we have to somehow deal with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another big earthquake in Christchurch</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/22/another-big-earthquake-in-christchurch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/22/another-big-earthquake-in-christchurch/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday a 6.3 magnitude earthquake struck our hometown of Christchurch. You might recall that Christchurch was hit by a 7.1 in September. The city has since felt thousands of aftershocks, of which yesterday’s 6.3 was one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big earthquake in Christchurch</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/04/big-earthquake-in-christchurch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/04/big-earthquake-in-christchurch/</guid>
      <description>Early on Saturday morning, our hometown of Christchurch was hit by a 7.1 magnitude earthquake. There has been a lot of damage, and about 20% of houses are uninhabitable. Sewage pipes and water pipes have burst in some areas and this has caused some flooding.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
