<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2010s on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2010s on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Our first New York Christmas</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/30/our-first-new-york-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/30/our-first-new-york-christmas/</guid>
      <description>This year was the first year our little family did not celebrate Christmas with grandparents. I was going to say that we didn’t celebrate with any extended family, but we do have Lillian here, so we’re not entirely family-less!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Feet of snow!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/27/2-feet-of-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/27/2-feet-of-snow/</guid>
      <description>We have had a great big snow storm that started yesterday and continued through the night. We’re loving it big time! We have a snow drift that goes almost to the top of our fence in the back yard, and this morning when I went outside on the side walk I had snow up to my mid thighs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy self-crusting pie recipe</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/27/easy-self-crusting-pie-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/27/easy-self-crusting-pie-recipe/</guid>
      <description>I have another easy and yummy recipe to share with you. This is kind of like a quiche, and kind of like a pie… and it is so fast it almost feels like cheating! It’s a Jo Seagar recipe, one that I acquired at the same time as the fudge recipe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let it snow, let it snow, let it snow!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/27/let-it-snow-let-it-snow-let-it-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/27/let-it-snow-let-it-snow-let-it-snow/</guid>
      <description>It started snowing on Sunday morning and continued snowing through the night. This morning we woke up to almost 2 feet of snow and a totally transformed neighborhood.
This is what it looked like trying to get out of our metal gate:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/24/merry-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/24/merry-christmas/</guid>
      <description>Today we celebrate the birth of The Biggest Present ever given. A Saviour to free us from sin, to take away the wrath we deserve and puts it on Himself, a death-conquering King who calls us His brothers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New York Christmas</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/23/a-new-york-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/23/a-new-york-christmas/</guid>
      <description>I thought I might share a few New York-ish Christmas moments with you. The city gets decorated quite a lot and there are lights and Christmas trees all over the place. Ben and Lillian and Marica went and had a look at some of the famous Christmas light displays down 5th Avenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating Advent</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/21/celebrating-advent/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/21/celebrating-advent/</guid>
      <description>It’s December… This is my favourite time of the year! I love the anticipation of Christmas, the Christmas music (I’ve been listening to a lot of old school Christmas songs on Pandora and we’ve been through The Messiah quite a number of times now too!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cloisters</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/13/the-cloisters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/13/the-cloisters/</guid>
      <description>Some of you have no doubt heard of The Metropolitan Museum of Art, or “The Met”, here in New York City. It’s a massive museum of art and culture, along Museum Mile on the east side of Central Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time is like mercury</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/11/time-is-like-mercury/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/11/time-is-like-mercury/</guid>
      <description>Time is like mercury. You can’t hold on to it and it keeps slipping away, especially at this time of the year. End of year functions, social events, Christmas shopping, Christmas baking, the usual daily tasks…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A few lovely photos</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/07/a-few-lovely-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/07/a-few-lovely-photos/</guid>
      <description>I thought I’d share a few photos of our time with the Braunings. We were so blessed by their hospitality, company, conversation and great food. Thanks again for inviting us, Mr &amp;amp; Mrs Brauning, and putting up with our changed plans and an invalid!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stereotypes, monotony and pain</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/02/stereotypes-monotony-and-pain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/02/stereotypes-monotony-and-pain/</guid>
      <description>It all started on an adventurous Saturday, almost 2 weeks ago. I was excited and a little scared because I was going to be making my biggest driving trip yet — a half an hour drive to our pastor’s house in the south of Brooklyn for a ladies’ Bible study.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another update</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/29/another-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/29/another-update/</guid>
      <description>I’m just now home from a second trip to the hospital and feeling much better than last week! After getting home last week I couldn’t keep food down and felt dizzy all the time. We made a kind of last-minute decision to go to the Braunings after all and spent Friday night with them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Appendix-less Franci, an update</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/23/appendix-less-franci-an-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/23/appendix-less-franci-an-update/</guid>
      <description>Just letting any readers know that the surgeon was able to remove Franci’s inflamed appendix successfully. Apparently it was pretty close to bursting when they operated. She’s sore and tired, but seems to be recovering well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking a little break</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/23/taking-a-little-break/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/23/taking-a-little-break/</guid>
      <description>Just thought I’d let everyone know that we’re taking a little blogging holiday over the Thanksgiving break. We’ll be back next week!
I’m also then going to a 3-day a week blogging schedule. I’m finding it a bit difficult to keep up with the demands of a household with 2 small children as well as rolling out a blog post per day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Appendix: Franci won’t have one for much longer</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/22/appendix/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/22/appendix/</guid>
      <description>We got the tummy bug over the weekend — fun for the whole family! But Franci’s “bug” hung around, and then got more and more painful. Turns out she has acute appendicitis. They’re going to cut her open tonight (might as well not “mince” words) and remove her appendix.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/22/thanksgiving/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/22/thanksgiving/</guid>
      <description>This week on Thursday it is Thanksgiving. I think it must be my favourite American holiday! A life that is full of thanksgiving is a happy one, no matter what the circumstances, and what can be better than once a year celebrating the good things God has given us with a great big feast?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keep sweeping</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/19/keep-sweeping/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/19/keep-sweeping/</guid>
      <description>My kitchen/dining room floor gets swept at least once a day. Usually more, but at least once. I never cease to be amazed at how much junk can land on the floor in just a day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More cereal box fun</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/18/more-cereal-box-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/18/more-cereal-box-fun/</guid>
      <description>When we looked for ideas for what kinds of crafts one can make with cereal boxes, back when we made Glitter Girl, we also came across a cute idea of making sandals. I promised Marica we’d do that, and here’s the result.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Through Marica’s eyes</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/17/through-maricas-eyes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/17/through-maricas-eyes/</guid>
      <description>Marica absolutely loves being allowed to use the camera to take photos. And I always have a chuckle when I download them and see just what caught her eye. Let’s just say that she has a realistic view and she takes pictures of it — she won’t avoid the messy room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snug as a bug…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/16/snug-as-a-bug/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/16/snug-as-a-bug/</guid>
      <description>in a front-pack on Pappa. Now if those silly teeth will just stop bothering me…
This cutie has cut a molar, even though she hasn’t even cut all her front teeth yet! She also seems to have found her voice, especially when her sister is giving her a hard time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enjoying Fall</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/15/enjoying-fall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/15/enjoying-fall/</guid>
      <description>Two weekends ago we visited friends from church for lunch who recently got married, Franco and Neli. Franco grew up in NYC and Neli is from Peru. They’re a really lovely couple!
Franco and Neli live in a tall apartment building a block away from Central Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Silly Billy Elliot</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/12/silly-billy-elliot/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/12/silly-billy-elliot/</guid>
      <description>Last Friday, Franci and I went to a Broadway show for the first time: Billy Elliot the Musical at the Imperial Theatre. Here’s a photo we took just before we went in:
It was quite the experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Well there you go!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/11/well-there-you-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/11/well-there-you-go/</guid>
      <description>We saw this billboard with graffiti on on our way home from the Bronx Zoo and I just had to take a picture. What a great commentary on how our society thinks — “it’s all about you”, never mind others, just go ahead and bless yourself!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>High class mac ‘n cheese recipe (done)</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/10/high-class-mac--n-cheese-recipe-done/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/10/high-class-mac--n-cheese-recipe-done/</guid>
      <description>We recently had an Italian-themed pot-luck lunch at church (we have pot-lucks once a month on the Sunday we have Lord’s Supper) and I wanted to find a recipe that was not just another lasagne. In my online search I came across this recipe, which I thought tasted very yummy indeed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Broadway and a birthday</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/09/broadway-and-a-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/09/broadway-and-a-birthday/</guid>
      <description>This past weekend was a full, but very enjoyable one.
On Friday night, our friend Rick babysat the kids while we went to see Billy Elliot on Broadway. We enjoyed our first Broadway experience. The “show” aspect at least — Ben will have more to say about the story later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If you’re ever feeling a bit glum…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/08/if-you-re-ever-feeling-a-bit-glum--done/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/08/if-you-re-ever-feeling-a-bit-glum--done/</guid>
      <description>and need a reason to put a smile on your face, then here are 2:
Now, let’s go pull radish together! Just watch out for thorny hedgehog! I love Chinglish!
(Special thanks to my friend Anna for taking these pictures for me!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A little summary</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/05/a-little-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/05/a-little-summary/</guid>
      <description>We’ve been in New York City for just a little over 5 months now. I can hardly believe it’s been that long, and on the other hand it feels much longer! I thought I’d use this post to update you in a bit more detail about how we’re doing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doing homework</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/04/doing-homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/04/doing-homework/</guid>
      <description>Marica reckons that one of the best things about preschool is that she gets to do homework!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sugar snap pea salad</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/03/sugar-snap-pea-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/03/sugar-snap-pea-salad/</guid>
      <description>When we visited aunt Sharon and uncle Sherwood Hoyt, aunt Sharon made a really nice salad for dinner one evening. I thought it was absolutely delicious and so I’m going to share it here. The recipe can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playing tourist again: Bronx Zoo</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/02/playing-tourist-again-bronx-zoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/02/playing-tourist-again-bronx-zoo/</guid>
      <description>A couple of Saturdays ago we bundled up and visited the Bronx Zoo. It is the biggest metropolitan zoo in the world, and we certainly didn’t see all of it in the day we were there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grocery challenge: week 4. I’m done!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/01/week-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/01/week-4/</guid>
      <description>Let’s just say I’m glad to have life returning to normal! It was a good little exercise in sticking to a budget (or close to, anyway), but I don’t think I’ll be doing that again any time soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not so many smiles at the moment</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/29/not-so-many-smiles-at-the-moment/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/29/not-so-many-smiles-at-the-moment/</guid>
      <description>As some of you know, Esther has been sick for over 5 weeks now, plagued by colds, teething and then this week some virus that has been giving her pretty high fevers. We’re pretty sure that it’s Roseola because as soon as she got a rash late yesterday afternoon her fever broke.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does it get any cuter than this?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/28/cuter-than-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/28/cuter-than-this/</guid>
      <description>A face full of dinner and eager to get in the water!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your feedback, please</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/27/your-feedback-please/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/27/your-feedback-please/</guid>
      <description>With this post, I’m going to ask our subscribers and readers to give us some feedback.
We normally post stuff like what we’ve been up to, interesting or funny things we’ve seen, photos of the kids and stuff like that, but I was thinking it would be nice to know some of your suggestions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This is the way we wash our clothes…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/26/this-is-the-way-we-wash-our-clothes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/26/this-is-the-way-we-wash-our-clothes/</guid>
      <description>wash our clothes, wash our clothes. This is the way we wash our clothes, living in New York City!
At our apartment, we don’t have facilities to do washing other than by hand. In fact, our rental contract specifies that we are not allowed to have a washing machine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grocery Challenge: week 3</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/25/grocery-challenge-week-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/25/grocery-challenge-week-3/</guid>
      <description>This past week seems to have been shorter than the others. Strange how that happens sometimes. Maybe it was because I didn’t have to cook very often! The flu was still having a field day, uh, week at our house and even Ben stayed home for 2 days from work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Esther’s new favourite toy</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/22/esthers-new-favourite-toy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/22/esthers-new-favourite-toy/</guid>
      <description>Esther loves water. She has also recently started pulling herself up on things. I guess it is to be expected that she would have found the toilet very entertaining!
Esther and the toilet seem to have a magnetic attraction to each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hoyt Street, Brooklyn</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/21/hoyt-street-brooklyn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/21/hoyt-street-brooklyn/</guid>
      <description>Hoyt is a fairly well-established name here in New York. Brooklyn even has a Hoyt Street, and there are two subway stations along it. It’s kinda fun to see our name popping up here and there!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playing tourist again: Little Italy</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/20/playing-tourist-again-little-italy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/20/playing-tourist-again-little-italy/</guid>
      <description>Stepping into Little Italy is like being overseas for a little while. The streets (Mulberry Street in particular) is decorated in Italian colours — red, green and white.
The place is littered with restaurants, and pizza shops and places selling “Italian Specialties” like meats, breads and desserts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugs</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/19/hugs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/19/hugs/</guid>
      <description>Marica giving Esther a cuddle at uncle Sherwood and aunt Sharon Hoyt’s place in Pennsylvania. Marica loves cuddling Esther, but Esther isn’t always so sure about it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grocery Challenge: week 2</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/18/grocery-challenge-week-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/18/grocery-challenge-week-2/</guid>
      <description>In some ways, week 2 was a lot easier than week 1. I only bought what I needed, but it seemed that I needed more than $25 worth of stuff a week. You’re probably all thinking “I knew she couldn’t do it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happiness in a box</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/15/happiness-in-a-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/15/happiness-in-a-box/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday afternoon was pretty grey, but then the rainy gloom was seriously cheered up by a special package from Oupa and Ouma Voges. It was filled with special goodies for all of us. Just check this out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stronger than Circumstances: Contentment and joy</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/14/stronger-than-circumstances/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/14/stronger-than-circumstances/</guid>
      <description>Just a little heads-up to our readers that this post is dealing with the topic of Christian contentment and is therefore explicitly religious. :-)
Today I’m delving into something totally different. This post won’t have many photos, and it won’t be about what we’ve been up to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cereal box fun</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/13/cereal-box-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/13/cereal-box-fun/</guid>
      <description>Last week we were all a bit under the weather, but of course when kids are sick they are still full of ideas and energy. So one morning after finishing off a box of cereal, I remembered doing crafts with cereal boxes as a kid and looked online for something to do with the cereal box.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calculus for three-year-olds</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/12/calculus-for-three-year-olds/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/12/calculus-for-three-year-olds/</guid>
      <description>The other day Franci and I were talking about subjects we studied in high school, and Marica asked what “calculus” was. Franci said it was a type of maths (Marica’s been learning her written numbers). Marica of course replied that “she could do that”, but Franci said she was probably a bit young for calculus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October grocery challenge: week 1</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/11/grocery-challenge-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/11/grocery-challenge-1/</guid>
      <description>I had a very interesting moment on the first day of the challenge. I had hopped over to Tim Challies’ blog and read an article about The Heart of Frugality. I almost immediately wanted to forget about this challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We’ve been a bit blah</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/08/weve-been-a-bit-blah/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/08/weve-been-a-bit-blah/</guid>
      <description>The weather has turned colder, there has been a lot of (cold) rain, I’ve unpacked the winter clothes, the heaters have had their first few runs and we’ve all gotten sick. Ben has only had a couple of days where he didn’t feel too great, and Marica’s only had a bit of a runny nose, but Esther’s gotten hit the hardest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend in Pottstown</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/07/weekend-in-pottstown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/07/weekend-in-pottstown/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend we visited Ben’s uncle Sherwood and aunt Sharon in Pottstown, near Philadelphia. It was a very nice restful weekend, just visiting and getting to know them a bit better. Their daughter, Esther, is away at college, but Jonathan was there and the kids loved playing with him — he’s really good with children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mmmm, white chocolate and Macadamia cookies</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/06/mmmm-white-chocolate-and-macadamia-cookies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/06/mmmm-white-chocolate-and-macadamia-cookies/</guid>
      <description>Macadamia nuts are my absolutely no-doubt-about-it favourite nut! They also seem to be about the most expensive, though. However, I recently discovered that we have an organic grocer nearby and they have bulk bins (unlike the supermarket) and their nuts and pretty much everything else are very well priced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My October grocery challenge</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/05/my-october-grocery-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/05/my-october-grocery-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes I feel like challenging myself in areas I’m not very good at. Like spending a small amount of money on groceries. Which is why it is a challenge! Here’s what I’m doing:
I’ve decided to try to reach the end of October and spend no more than $100 on groceries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Esther’s new shoes</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/04/esthers-new-shoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/04/esthers-new-shoes/</guid>
      <description>Esther recently got her first pair of shoes. She’s been a barefoot baby for all the 10 months of her life (not counting socks, of course!) and is taking a little while getting used to them!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playing tourist again: Chinatown</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/01/playing-tourist-again-chinatown/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/01/playing-tourist-again-chinatown/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weekends ago we visited Chinatown and Little Italy. I took so many photos that day that I cannot possibly fit them all into one post, so this one will be about Chinatown. Little Italy will follow eventually.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Firefly</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/30/little-firefly/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/30/little-firefly/</guid>
      <description>A (cheesy) little poem I wrote one very hot night sitting outside in my Brooklyn backyard.
—————————————————————————————————————————————-
Little firefly,
What are you doing here?
Don’t you belong
in open fields
by sliding streams
under uninterrupted skies?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What we’re doing and reading</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/28/what-were-doing-and-reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/28/what-were-doing-and-reading/</guid>
      <description>Last night I had an audition for the Brooklyn Conservatory Chorale. I’ve been thinking for a while that I’d like to do some music again, but because we don’t have a piano and I decided not to bring my violin, it has to be singing which I thankfully enjoy doing very much!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sisterly love</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/27/sisterly-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/27/sisterly-love/</guid>
      <description>I love moments like this!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rubber ducky</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/24/rubber-ducky/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/24/rubber-ducky/</guid>
      <description>Something we saw plastered on a wall near Little Italy. If your sense of humour is anything like mine, you’ll find this pretty funny.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Really good fudge</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/23/really-good-fudge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/23/really-good-fudge/</guid>
      <description>I haven’t made fudge many times before, but whenever I’ve tried, it’s turned out terribly. Either too soft and runny, or hard and crystallised. Until the day I made this recipe that I obtained in a dubious way…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet our church in New York</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/22/meet-our-church-in-new-york/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/22/meet-our-church-in-new-york/</guid>
      <description>Here in New York we attend a URCNA (United Reformed Church of North America) congregation that meets in lower Manhattan near Ground Zero, called Messiah’s Reformed Fellowship (MeRF for short).
MeRF started as a response to the September 11 terrorist attacks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Today I did a really crazy thing…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/21/crazy-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/21/crazy-thing/</guid>
      <description>I think I made some angels work overtime today. I’ve just returned from a shoe shopping experience in a great big shoe store my mother-in-law recommended. The shopping experience was quite fun, but that wasn’t the crazy part.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HannahHolder.com, fine art from a fine artist</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/20/hannah-holder-fine-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/20/hannah-holder-fine-art/</guid>
      <description>My cousin Hannah Holder has a lovely website detailing some of the fine art she has done (and can do). She now has her very own domain name, so browse on over to HannahHolder.com and see it for yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lady Liberty</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/20/lady-liberty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/20/lady-liberty/</guid>
      <description>The other night I was busy in the kitchen setting the table and suddenly wondered why Marica was so quiet. I looked up and saw this.
Totally unprompted, and she got the pose and everything right!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tornado in Brooklyn</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/18/tornado-in-brooklyn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/18/tornado-in-brooklyn/</guid>
      <description>While Christchurch is still having earthquakes, here in Brooklyn we had our very own tornado (or super-severe storm — the weather service isn’t sure which). The winds and rain whipped up all of a sudden, picked up huge branches and even trees and threw them across the streets, and then twenty minutes later it was dead calm again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grilled chicken open sandwich</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/17/grilled-chicken-open-sandwich/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/17/grilled-chicken-open-sandwich/</guid>
      <description>The other night I didn’t feel much like cooking, but didn’t want to spend money on take-aways either. I also had some chicken in the fridge that had thawed that needed to be used. What I thought would end up as a slap-together quick dinner, ended up being really yummy, so I decided to share it with you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oops</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/16/oops/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/16/oops/</guid>
      <description>Couldn’t help smiling yet at the same time feeling sorry for whoever this belongs to:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who said there’s no such thing as a free lunch?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/15/free-lunch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/15/free-lunch/</guid>
      <description>Autumn (or “fall” as it is called here) has come and school has started up again after a good hot summer. It’s been a full summer for us and we’re glad for things to start settling a bit, not to mention glad for a hint of some cooler weather.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two nights &#43; 14 people &#43; 1 (small) New York apartment = Lots of fun!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/14/two-nights/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/14/two-nights/</guid>
      <description>It’s really hard to believe that it’s almost been two weeks since the van Wichens descended on our place. For those who don’t know, Laurel is Ben’s oldest sister and their family is touring the States for 10 weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your comments, preschool and a jewelery hanger</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/12/your-comments-preschool-and-a-jewelery-hanger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/12/your-comments-preschool-and-a-jewelery-hanger/</guid>
      <description>Some people have told us that they enjoy our blog. Thanks, that’s cool! :-) However, I would encourage you to add your comments — having a blog is a bit like us having a conversation with everyone who reads it, and your comments help this conversation feel a little less one-sided.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marica’s sayings on Twitter</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/10/maricas-sayings-on-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/10/maricas-sayings-on-twitter/</guid>
      <description>I don’t understand the appeal of Twitter. Just as you’re three quarters of the way through your controversial opening statement, you have t…
But anyway, Franci and I did find a good use for it. You know all those weird and wonderful things three-year-olds say but you always forget to write down?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A brief history of Hoyt</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/08/a-brief-history-of-hoyt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/08/a-brief-history-of-hoyt/</guid>
      <description>As far as I know, not many Hoyts in my extended family are into family history. I’m not exactly either, but it is interesting when you run across a bit of good old ancestry (actually, an old friend from Masterton put me onto most of this stuff).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Day</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/07/first-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/07/first-day/</guid>
      <description>Today is a pretty big day here in the Hoyt household. It’s Marica’s first day at an American preschool!
She was really excited and keen, all smiles walking there and meeting the teachers and putting her bag away and finding her name on the table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big earthquake in Christchurch</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/04/big-earthquake-in-christchurch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/04/big-earthquake-in-christchurch/</guid>
      <description>Early on Saturday morning, our hometown of Christchurch was hit by a 7.1 magnitude earthquake. There has been a lot of damage, and about 20% of houses are uninhabitable. Sewage pipes and water pipes have burst in some areas and this has caused some flooding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tasty Recipe and more</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/01/tasty-recipe-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/01/tasty-recipe-and-more/</guid>
      <description>Last night we had some company (a work colleague of Ben’s) and I made a new recipe. I have a very bad habit of trying new recipes when we have people over, but this time it was definitely a winner!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saturday at Coney Island</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/30/saturday-at-coney-island/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/30/saturday-at-coney-island/</guid>
      <description>On Saturday we went to Coney Island for the day. We tried to pack in as much as possible and first went to the Aquarium, then for a swim at the beach and then off to the best part: some rides at the amusement parks!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rainy day fun</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/27/rainy-day-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/27/rainy-day-fun/</guid>
      <description>When I realised that we have rain forecast for most of this past week, I wondered how on earth I was going to entertain two busy little people indoors? But then I just googled ‘rainy day activities with preschoolers’ and it comes up with a list of stuff to do that will keep you occupied almost all winter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is smoking a sin?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/24/is-smoking-a-sin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/24/is-smoking-a-sin/</guid>
      <description>Quite probably for you, it is. :-)
I just read this short address by Doug Wilson to a bunch of Christian college students and found it a refreshing argument against smoking rather than the usual ‘it ruins your body’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And then there was Texas</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/22/and-then-there-was-texas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/22/and-then-there-was-texas/</guid>
      <description>After the Tschetter family reunion in Colorado, I caught a ride with Ben’s parents to Smolan, Kansas, where Grandma and Grandpa Tschetter live. (Ben had to head back to NYC for work.) It was really special to spend 2 nights in their home, see Grandma’s cool kitchen wallpaper and eat out of her pretty china.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little bits of update</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/18/little-bits-of-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/18/little-bits-of-update/</guid>
      <description>I’m slowly settling into the groove of life here in NYC again and today we ventured out to the Prospect Park Zoo. I’m sure you with dial-up will be delighted to know that I forgot my camera at home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to Colorado</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/16/visit-to-colorado/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/16/visit-to-colorado/</guid>
      <description>The last week of July we headed off to Colorado for a Tschetter family reunion (Ben’s mum’s side of the family) to specially celebrate Ben’s grandparents’ 70th wedding anniversary. We flew to Denver and then Mum and Dad Hoyt picked us up from the airport and we drove into the mountains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We’re back!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/12/were-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/12/were-back/</guid>
      <description>I’ve you’re an avid follower of our blog, you will have noticed that our posts have been rather sparse the last 2 and a half weeks. We’ve had a great time away traipsing over the country visiting family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My new book</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/07/my-new-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/07/my-new-book/</guid>
      <description>My lovely husband has recently bought me Julia Child’s Mastering the Art of French Cooking. I have read the preface and all the introductory remarks. Now I need to start cooking from it. It’s just been so hot that cooking anything that isn’t a hamburger patty is not very appealing, even if it is French.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working at Oyster.com</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/02/working-at-oyster-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/02/working-at-oyster-com/</guid>
      <description>As most of you know, I’m now working for Oyster.com in New York City. Oyster is a small (15 staff) startup company that runs a website which lets you review and book hotels. Apart from offering good rates, one of the main things that sets Oyster apart is its thorough reviews and top-quality photos, allowing customers to really see what they’re getting before they book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From old to new</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/22/from-old-to-new/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/22/from-old-to-new/</guid>
      <description>Last week I had fun being a bit creative using stuff that was left here from the previous tenant and sprucing them up a bit. The whole Reduce, Recycle and Reuse slogan comes to mind, but also making things pretty for cheap really appeals to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I love my kids</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/18/i-love-my-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/18/i-love-my-kids/</guid>
      <description>I love my kids. They certainly are hard work, and their sinful natures are so raw and need so much refining and shaping and I sometimes feel so hopelessly unqualified to be their mother, but then Marica would run up to me and say “I love you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our very first dinner guests, and the second lot too</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/18/our-very-first-dinner-guests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/18/our-very-first-dinner-guests/</guid>
      <description>Meeting Rick and Susanna was one of those amazing cases of providence. Both our families happened to be visiting Park Slope Presbyterian Church on the same Sunday, we got talking, we clicked, and a friendship was formed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 4th of July</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/15/the-4th-of-july/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/15/the-4th-of-july/</guid>
      <description>Earlier this month, on the 4th of July, the United States of America celebrated Independence Day. It’s been 234 years since America declared independence from Great Britain, and for the average American England is now just some far away place where people talk funny.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to the New York Aquarium</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/13/visit-to-the-new-york-aquarium/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/13/visit-to-the-new-york-aquarium/</guid>
      <description>We visited the New York Aquarium in Coney Island recently. From where we were at our old place in Brooklyn, it’s about an hour on the subway to get there.
There’s a great board walk with lots of shops selling food and trinkets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our new place (with photo tour)</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/10/our-new-place/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/10/our-new-place/</guid>
      <description>On Thursday the first of July we moved into our new rental place. Now, 10 days later we are starting to feel a bit more settled. Thursday was a very busy day. But perhaps I should tell you about Wednesday first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Saga of the Air Conditioning</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/08/the-saga-of-the-air-conditioning/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/08/the-saga-of-the-air-conditioning/</guid>
      <description>I was going to do a post with pictures about our new place, but alas, I haven’t gotten around to taking pictures, so I’ll try to do that in the next day or two.
So we moved into our new place last Thursday, and let me tell you, it has been a full week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out of action for a week</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/30/out-of-action-for-a-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/30/out-of-action-for-a-week/</guid>
      <description>Tomorrow, Lord willing, we move into our apartment. While this is great, it does however mean that we will be without internet access for a week. Actually, I’ll be without internet access for a week because Ben will still be able to check email and stuff at work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Streets of Power</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/30/streets-of-power/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/30/streets-of-power/</guid>
      <description>On Saturday, after our little jaunt to Staten Island, we had a little meander around Wall Street. When dad Hoyt talks about Canyon City, then this is it. I don’t get that feeling in Brooklyn, but boy, down there the streets are quite narrow and the buildings go up so high that if you wanted to take a photo of them you’d have to plaster 2 or 3 together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend touristy fun</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/30/weekend-touristy-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/30/weekend-touristy-fun/</guid>
      <description>Ben has already told you that we went to Staten (pronounced Statten, not State-in) Island on Saturday. I have some cool photos to share of our trip there and back, and later in the week I’ll tell and show you all about the stuff we saw in the Financial District.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Statue of Liberty</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/28/the-statue-of-liberty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/28/the-statue-of-liberty/</guid>
      <description>Today we took the Staten Island Ferry from the southern tip of Manhattan to the north-most point on Staten Island (and back, of course). For a long time the ferry cost only 25 cents for a return trip, then it went up to 50 cents in 1990.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We have an apartment!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/28/we-have-an-apartment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/28/we-have-an-apartment/</guid>
      <description>Yes, yesterday we signed the contract to rent a “Garden Apartment”. It’s the bottom floor in the brown building on the right in this photo (thanks to Google Maps), under the stairs where the little “A” is:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subscribing to this blog</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/26/subscribing-to-this-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/26/subscribing-to-this-blog/</guid>
      <description>I know that a number of you read our blog, and thanks for that! It’s nice to know that people are interested in staying in contact with us.
Though, as you’ve probably noticed by now, we certainly don’t post everyday (our lives aren’t that interesting!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend trip to New Jersey</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/24/weekend-trip-to-new-jersey/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/24/weekend-trip-to-new-jersey/</guid>
      <description>I promised that I’d share about our time with the Stoltes in New Jersey this past weekend. I can’t believe it’s already Wednesday — and I’m only getting around to this now.
Public transport around here is really good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ye olde green cards</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/23/ye-olde-green-cards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/23/ye-olde-green-cards/</guid>
      <description>I am happy to report that Marica, Esther and I are now the proud owners of U.S. green cards. (Not just the temporary paperwork, but the Real Thing.) The cards arrived in the mail yesterday, so we are now officially Permanent Residents of the United States of America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dear Roseola, thanks for not being Chickenpox (or worse, Measles)</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/19/dear-roseola-thanks-for-not-being-chickenpox-or-worse-measles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/19/dear-roseola-thanks-for-not-being-chickenpox-or-worse-measles/</guid>
      <description>This week has been a bit trying as Marica has been quite unwell. Monday and Tuesday she had a high fever and was listless and irritable. The listlessness and irritability has continued all week and on Thursday she broke out with a rash which we initially thought was a very bad case of chickenpox.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kids!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/16/kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/16/kids/</guid>
      <description>This post is about the cool new things our kids can do. :-)
Marica has learned to recognise the numbers 1-6 and is quickly learning 7-10 as well. I think this has a lot to do with the fact that we let her push the buttons in the elevator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All Natural!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/13/all-natural/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/13/all-natural/</guid>
      <description>Ben and I have had lots of chuckles over some product labelling here in the U.S. lately. The term “all natural” seems to be plastered on everything. With such a label, you would assume “healthy”, but is anything edible not natural (in the sense that it has been derived from nature?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Like a little child</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/10/like-a-little-child/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/10/like-a-little-child/</guid>
      <description>Last night as I was putting Esther to bed, Marica peeked into the door and said out of the blue and quite matter of factly with her little double-jointed forefinger pointing upwards that “Wanneer ek doodgaan, ek gaan hemel toe by Jesus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quirky New York</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/10/quirky-new-york/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/10/quirky-new-york/</guid>
      <description>So far we’ve noticed a few quirky things here in New York.
For instance, the light switches are the other way around than in NZ - up is on and down is off. I still get confused.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Showing you around (a photo post)</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/07/showing-you-around/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/07/showing-you-around/</guid>
      <description>First off, if you have dail-up, I apologise. This post is going to be laden with photos!
The other day, Ben caught Marica on camera looking out the window of our 5th floor apartment:
The nice building across the road is the HSBC bank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apartment hunting</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/05/apartment-hunting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/05/apartment-hunting/</guid>
      <description>There is not a whole lot to tell you about yet, but finding an apartment in NYC is hard work. Especially without the ease of a car! On Wednesday I packed up the kids and we set of to look at some apartments in Prospect Heights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The city that never sleeps</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/05/31/the-city-that-never-sleeps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/05/31/the-city-that-never-sleeps/</guid>
      <description>I can’t believe we’ve only been in NYC for 4 nights — it feels much longer. I’m sure that this is because we haven’t exactly slept very well. Jet lag aside, we’ve had some interesting night-time sound experiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balm for anxious thoughts</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/05/28/balm-for-anxious-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/05/28/balm-for-anxious-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>This morning, as I sit here alone with an apartment full of beautiful sleeping people, my mind is full of anxious thoughts. Things like, where will we end up living? Will I even like it here?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye Christchurch, Hello New York</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/05/28/goodbye-christchurch-hello-new-york/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/05/28/goodbye-christchurch-hello-new-york/</guid>
      <description>It’s been a hectic last few days! The days leading up to our departure were filled with last-minute packing and cleaning (thanks to everyone who helped!) and lots of goodbyes. I hate goodbyes, but as far as they go, the ones we had were good byes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Big Apple</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/05/24/the-big-apple/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/05/24/the-big-apple/</guid>
      <description>Why is New York City called The Big Apple?
It’s actually one of those old terms that has a sketchy history. Wikipedia tells me it was first used as a term for New York in 1921 by John J Fitz Gerald in a horce-racing context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Packing and stacking</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/05/13/packing-and-stacking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/05/13/packing-and-stacking/</guid>
      <description>When Ben came home 2 weeks ago and told me that we were leaving for NYC in 4 1/2 weeks instead of the original 12 weeks, I went into a mini panic, so to speak. We made a list of all the things he needed to do and what I needed to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What you notice when you’re going to NYC</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/05/04/what-you-notice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/05/04/what-you-notice/</guid>
      <description>It’s amazing what you notice about a place you’ve lived in for ages when you’re planning a trip overseas. For one thing, Christchurch has a lot of center-city apartments — never noticed ‘em before, but now they’re everywhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why and wherefore</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/04/27/why-and-wherefore/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/04/27/why-and-wherefore/</guid>
      <description>Several people have asked us why we’re heading away, so here’s a brief run-down. We’ve been thinking about a U.S. holiday for a few years now, but then we thought it might make more sense to save up for a U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/04/26/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/04/26/welcome/</guid>
      <description>So we’re going overseas in a month and, just to be different like everyone else, we’re starting a blog.
We’re hoping to post updates about how it’s all going, and about life in the Big Apple.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
