<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2016s on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2016s on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/12/25/merry-christmas-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/12/25/merry-christmas-4/</guid>
      <description>Merry Christmas to all of you, from all of us!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful autumn</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/12/23/beautiful-autumn-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/12/23/beautiful-autumn-2/</guid>
      <description>Autumn this year was beautiful and mild and felt like a sort of nicer continuation of summer. We were, of course, back at doing school, but we tried to enjoy the nice weather as much as we could.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The rest of the summer</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/12/09/the-rest-of-the-summer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/12/09/the-rest-of-the-summer/</guid>
      <description>(This post is pretty heavy on photos. Just a reminder that if you want to see larger versions of them, to click on a photo and you’ll then be able to view the slideshow of that particular group of photos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Veggie Garden</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/11/18/our-veggie-garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/11/18/our-veggie-garden/</guid>
      <description>(Though perhaps a better title would have been My Veggie Garden, but I’m generously including Ben because he heaved heavy compost bags and helped with digging and building a frame for my beans.)
I decided that this year I’d like to have a veggie garden again after not having one for three summers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Greatest Gift</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/11/14/the-greatest-gift/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/11/14/the-greatest-gift/</guid>
      <description>A couple of years ago, I really enjoyed reading through The Greatest Gift by Ann Voskamp for Advent. This year I’m trying to be organized enough to remind you that if this is something you’d like to buy, now’s a good time, with Advent being just two weeks away and all!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banana Cake with chocolate cream cheese icing</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/11/11/banana-cake-with-chocolate-cream-cheese-icing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/11/11/banana-cake-with-chocolate-cream-cheese-icing/</guid>
      <description>I built a cake earlier this week. I’m doing really well at blogging about it while the cake is still in existence on the kitchen counter! I’m still playing catch-up with blogging about news from the summer, but I wanted to share this before it died in my drafts folder like so many other recipes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip ’16: Six Flags</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/11/04/roadtrip-16-six-flags/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/11/04/roadtrip-16-six-flags/</guid>
      <description>For the last leg of our roadtrip home, we made a stop at Six Flags in the south of New Jersey. They have a program called Read To Succeed where the kids have to read a total of 600 hours in the year to get free tickets to Six Flags.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip ’16: Chincoteague</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/10/21/roadtrip-16-chincoteague/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/10/21/roadtrip-16-chincoteague/</guid>
      <description>After our stint in Charleston, we had a long but beautiful drive up to Chincoteague, VA. Our reason for visiting was because we had recently listened to Misty of Chincoteague on audio and loved the story, and seeing that it was sort of on our way home, thought it would be cool to stop and see the area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip ’16: Charleston, SC</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/10/07/roadtrip-16-charleston-sc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/10/07/roadtrip-16-charleston-sc/</guid>
      <description>It was with heavy hearts that we said our goodbyes after the Hoyt reunion, but it was time to start making our way home. Because Ben was in between jobs at that point, he could take off some extra time and we decided to take the trip back up a little more slowly to stop at a few places we were interested in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip ’16: Hoyt Reunion</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/09/30/roadtrip-16-hoyt-reunion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/09/30/roadtrip-16-hoyt-reunion/</guid>
      <description>After our great camping experience, we drove down to Columbia, SC, to spend the night and visit Ben’s parents’ old church where we got to meet people who knew them 40 years ago, which was pretty neat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip ’16: Camping in TN</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/09/23/roadtrip-16-camping-in-tn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/09/23/roadtrip-16-camping-in-tn/</guid>
      <description>After our visit to Monticello we started the drive down to Cherokee National Forest in east Tennessee where we planned on camping for a couple of nights. We started off in the rain and the rain just got heavier and heavier, and there were predictions for a huge storm to pass over where we were going to camp that night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip ’16: Monticello</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/09/09/roadtrip-16-monticello/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/09/09/roadtrip-16-monticello/</guid>
      <description>This year was the happy year where a US Hoyt reunion took place. This time was again in Georgia, so back in June we took a two and a half week long roadtrip down south. It worked out well that Ben happened to be between jobs at that point so he took 3 weeks off, which was so great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MeRF Getaway</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/09/02/merf-getaway/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/09/02/merf-getaway/</guid>
      <description>Back in June, some folks in our church (MeRF = Messiah’s Reformed Fellowship) headed out to Pennsylvania for a getaway at Kirby House, a beautiful old house that was once used by the Kirby family as their summer home in the mountains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurelin’s 3rd birthday</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/08/26/laurelins-3rd-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/08/26/laurelins-3rd-birthday/</guid>
      <description>In all the bustle of the end of the school year and then summer vacation, I’ve neglected to post photos of Laurelin’s 3rd birthday.
Laurelin is now a full-blown 3-year-old and no push-over, in every sense of the word.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finishing up the school year</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/08/19/finishing-up-the-school-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/08/19/finishing-up-the-school-year/</guid>
      <description>It’s taken us a while to get used to this business of school finishing right in the middle of the calendar year and the starting again in August/September when we are so used to the school year following the calendar year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The job front</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/08/12/the-job-front/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/08/12/the-job-front/</guid>
      <description>In the last couple of months I’ve had a bit of a change job-wise (Franci said it was about time for me to write). I had been a software engineer for Oyster.com — now part of TripAdvisor — for just over six years, and decided it was time for a change and some new work experience while we’re here in the States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A morning in the big city</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/08/05/a-morning-in-the-big-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/08/05/a-morning-in-the-big-city/</guid>
      <description>I’m playing catch-up here on the blog after my long silence. We start back at school in 3 weeks or so, but it feels as though we’ve hardly started vacation. Summer for us here in the US seems to be filled with more activity than during the school year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random thoughts</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/06/10/random-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/06/10/random-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>The last couple of months have looked a little different to our usual routines. I’ve had a relapse of the Epstein-Barr virus which wiped me out but I seem to be feeling a fair bit better the last week or so; Ben’s been looking at different job options and has had multiple interviews with several different companies (no decision yet, though).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Co-op class pizza night</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/05/20/co-op-class-pizza-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/05/20/co-op-class-pizza-night/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp;
I teach a Narnia literature class at our homeschool co-op, which has been really fun. For me, anyway. Not quite sure what the kids think, seeing that it’s a discussion class and I make them talk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Spring Tea Party</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/05/13/a-spring-tea-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/05/13/a-spring-tea-party/</guid>
      <description>In our living room stands a beautiful wooden display cabinet that has been in my family for 3 generations. It displays a selection of pretty tea cups, teapots, milk pitchers and sugar pots I have been given from my grandma, my mum, and Ben’s grandma Tschetter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easter 2016</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/05/06/easter-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/05/06/easter-2016/</guid>
      <description>This year’s Easter was a busy but lovely one. We kept up the tradition of making hot cross buns and egg dying, which the kids always love,
&amp;nbsp;
and on Easter Sunday we hosted a large crowd of church folk for a yummy dinner, followed by some rousing hymn singing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April Fool’s Day</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/04/29/april-fools-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/04/29/april-fools-day/</guid>
      <description>Our family, especially the kids, have taken a real liking to April 1st. The kids plan pranks for weeks in advance, which they then gleefully execute on the day. We also have a little tradition of having waffles for dinner on that night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some fishy characters</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/04/22/some-fishy-characters/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/04/22/some-fishy-characters/</guid>
      <description>For the first few years of our marriage Ben and I had a little dog, Blitzie. When we came to the States in 2010, we gave her away and she’s been living happily every after on a pig farm since.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holy bubbles</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/04/15/its-too-serious-to-be-funny/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/04/15/its-too-serious-to-be-funny/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been searching for a preschool for Laurelin for a couple of mornings a week. I think it’ll be good for her, and it will help the two older girls and me get a bit more done in school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick, sticky snow</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/04/08/quick-sticky-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/04/08/quick-sticky-snow/</guid>
      <description>It’s been quiet on here for a while. When that happens, it usually means things around here have been a little extra busy, which it indeed has. Some of the highlights of the busyness will be following in the next few weeks, but before the warm weather completely overtakes us I wanted to share some last winter snow pictures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The new GiftyWeddings.com</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/04/06/the-new-giftyweddings-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/04/06/the-new-giftyweddings-com/</guid>
      <description>Most of you know that I (this is Ben posting for a change) run a little wedding gift registry website called GiftyWeddings.com. It’s been going for almost eight years now, helping several couples every month create nice simple gift registries that aren’t tied to a particular store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marica’s 9th birthday</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/03/11/maricas-9th-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/03/11/maricas-9th-birthday/</guid>
      <description>My oldest turned 9 last month. Where did the time go? I know all mothers always say that, but my oh my, they grow up fast. Gone is the little girl who liked her hair braided all pretty, and who would wear whatever her mother put out for her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This winter’s first snow</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/03/04/this-winters-first-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/03/04/this-winters-first-snow/</guid>
      <description>I feel like I’m always putting up stuff on here that’s a month or more old. It just seems to be the rate at which I can keep up with things! A few days after we got back from New Zealand mid-January, we had the first big (and the only big, really) snow storm of the winter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to New Zealand, part 4</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/02/19/visit-to-new-zealand-part-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/02/19/visit-to-new-zealand-part-4/</guid>
      <description>A couple of days after Christmas Ben returned to the US, and the girls and I stayed in NZ for another 3 (full, but great) weeks. We met up with lots of family and friends and had such a great time that for the most part I forgot to take my camera along.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A tad on the cool side</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/02/15/a-tad-on-the-cool-side/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/02/15/a-tad-on-the-cool-side/</guid>
      <description>This past weekend was a little nippy. I’d say it was the coldest weather we’ve ever experienced! Most of last week the high during the day didn’t get above 0°C, and by Sunday morning we woke up to this (my phone shows temperature in Celsius):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to New Zealand, part 3</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/02/12/visit-to-new-zealand-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/02/12/visit-to-new-zealand-part-3/</guid>
      <description>I know this isn’t technically part of our trip to New Zealand, but I didn’t really want to make a whole separate post for these photos I took before we left. December was unseasonably warm, so one evening while Ben worked late, I took the kids on a post-dinner walk around the neighborhood to enjoy the lights on people’s houses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to New Zealand, part 2</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/02/05/visit-to-new-zealand-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/02/05/visit-to-new-zealand-part-2/</guid>
      <description>A couple of days after we arrived, we headed out of town to Mt Hutt in the Southern Alps for a Hoyt reunion. I think it had been the first time in almost 6 years that everyone were together again — Mum &amp;amp; Dad, all 8 siblings, plus spouses and kids — and it was fantastic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to New Zealand, part 1</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/01/29/visit-to-new-zealand-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/01/29/visit-to-new-zealand-part-1/</guid>
      <description>How do you describe a place? I can tell you about beautiful green rolling hills, changeable weather, children walking barefoot down the road without anyone scowling at them. I can tell you about the lilt of an accent, of driving on the left side of the road, of great coffee — both instant and barista made.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pie Day</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/01/01/pie-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/01/01/pie-day/</guid>
      <description>Back in mid-November I had a few girls from church over at our house for a pie making day. We worked hard, had lots of fun and got to enjoy some pretty yummy pies.
For those of you who might be interested, here are the recipes of what we made.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
