<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Being creative on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/category/being-creative/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Being creative on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/category/being-creative/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Banana Cake with chocolate cream cheese icing</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/11/11/banana-cake-with-chocolate-cream-cheese-icing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/11/11/banana-cake-with-chocolate-cream-cheese-icing/</guid>
      <description>I built a cake earlier this week. I’m doing really well at blogging about it while the cake is still in existence on the kitchen counter! I’m still playing catch-up with blogging about news from the summer, but I wanted to share this before it died in my drafts folder like so many other recipes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enjoying a spot of sewing</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/04/17/enjoying-a-spot-of-sewing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/04/17/enjoying-a-spot-of-sewing/</guid>
      <description>The week before Easter I decided that I’d love for the girls to have new dresses for Easter (which is a bit of an American church tradition, it seems to me), but I really didn’t want to fork out $30 a dress (times three!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lego Tower version 1</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/03/28/lego-tower-version-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/03/28/lego-tower-version-1/</guid>
      <description>Marica and Esther and I (Ben) have been playing with Lego on Saturdays. Marica’s built up a decent collection of small Lego sets over the past several birthdays and Christmases, and building things with them is one of my favourite inside things to do with the kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Entrepreneurial Fair</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/09/the-entrepreneurial-fair/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/09/the-entrepreneurial-fair/</guid>
      <description>The Co-op that we attend had an Entrepreneurial Fair early in December, and as much as I would have liked to just be a spectator, my kids were burning to sell stuff (surprise, surprise). So, we made Christmas ornaments, some chocolates and gingerbread men.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some nice things</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/31/some-nice-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/31/some-nice-things/</guid>
      <description>I like autumn. It’s not so hot, there are pretty colors everywhere, and the change of season brings all sorts of nice things like warm slippers and hot drinks, nice decorations and good smelling candles, and fun kids’ crafts…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marica the entrepreneur</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/13/marica-the-entrepreneur/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/13/marica-the-entrepreneur/</guid>
      <description>When Marica was 4, I got a fancy new camera as a very generous gift. Marica then got our old camera, which was a little point and shoot that was on its way out but still in good condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A prize-winning photo!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/09/05/a-prize-winning-photo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/09/05/a-prize-winning-photo/</guid>
      <description>With such a sensationalist title, you’d think this is something really special, right? Well, not quite! TripAdvisor (where Ben works) had this internal competition over the summer where you could send in a photo with a TripAdvisor fridge magnet on your vehicle, and every week they picked a winner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love poem to New York</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/31/love-poem-to-new-york/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/31/love-poem-to-new-york/</guid>
      <description>New York…
Your name invoked images, awe, presumptions
of ghetto, gangster, glamour, glitz.
Yet many will be surprised to know
I found in you much goodness and grace
just as ingrained
as the grit and grime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gingerbread House fun</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/22/gingerbread-house-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/22/gingerbread-house-fun/</guid>
      <description>Our much loved pastor’s wife, Julie, invited a few moms over to her house last Friday to make gingerbread houses. What a total blast! We made the houses out of graham crackers instead of baked sheets of gingerbread, which was much easier and less time consuming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Christmas craft afternoon</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/20/a-christmas-craft-afternoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/20/a-christmas-craft-afternoon/</guid>
      <description>On an unseasonably warm Saturday late in November, a few women from our church gathered at our friend Jen’s house to make some Christmas crafts. It was bliss… lots of good chatting and food while being enjoyably creative and productive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting excited about Christmas</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/12/getting-excited-about-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/12/getting-excited-about-christmas/</guid>
      <description>I love the month of December here in New York — I think it’s even my favourite time of the year, even better than beautiful spring-time April. It’s cold, but everyone seems to be in good spirits (as opposed to grumpy January!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent is here!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/10/advent-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/10/advent-is-here/</guid>
      <description>I started the blog post draft a few weeks back, and now the season of Advent is about halfway through. Last year we decided to start celebrating Advent in a more deliberate way, building the excitement until Christmas, and enjoying the anticipation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some nature shots from the Adirondacks</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/07/some-nature-shots-from-the-adirondacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/07/some-nature-shots-from-the-adirondacks/</guid>
      <description>During our time in the Adirondacks it rained most of the time, except for our first afternoon there. There were some breaks in the rain, though, and I took my chances to go outside and take some ‘nature shots’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accidental coolness</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/13/accidental-coolness/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/13/accidental-coolness/</guid>
      <description>When I was driving through Philly with Margaret, I was just happily snapping pictures of stuff out of the car while we were driving. I happened to take this picture of a city centre sculpture and when I went through the photos afterwards I saw how perfectly (total fluke) the moon was aligned with this thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green and glorious</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/09/green-and-glorious/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/09/green-and-glorious/</guid>
      <description>Hooray for pesto! What a beautiful thing pesto is. Easy to make, and it gives a wonderful flavour to sandwiches, pastas, risotto, pizza, baked potatoes, salads, chocolate cake, wait, what? Just trust me, it’s good stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A garden grows in Brooklyn</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/06/a-garden-grows-in-brooklyn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/06/a-garden-grows-in-brooklyn/</guid>
      <description>We are among the few privileged New Yorkers who have our own private backyard. Private as in access (no one else uses our backyard), not private in the sense that nobody can see us, because we certainly have plenty of window eyes all around!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo fun</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/02/photo-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/02/photo-fun/</guid>
      <description>The outside of our house at the back is painted in a vivid blue. I’ve planted some zinnias in pots, and the colour contrast is great. I had some fun taking photos of a couple of flowers the other day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glimpses into the last couple of weeks</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/27/glimpses-into-the-last-couple-of-weeks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/27/glimpses-into-the-last-couple-of-weeks/</guid>
      <description>I don’t know why the weeks go by so fast. I have a bunch of photos to share with you from when Ben’s cousin Sharon visited us a month ago, our trip to Connecticut 2 weeks ago and our trip to visit Jeremy in Philadelphia last weekend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When you don’t have a sandwich press…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/26/when-you-dont-have-a-sandwich-press/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/26/when-you-dont-have-a-sandwich-press/</guid>
      <description>… make your own with whatever you have on hand!
See, it works pretty well!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beauty is in the eye of the beholder</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/02/beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/02/beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder/</guid>
      <description>Marica said I looked beautiful after she was finished making me beautiful. Ben came home and called me hideous. I’ll let you decide for yourself!
It was cold and rainy a fair bit back in March, so one day when Marica asked if she could make me pretty, I consented.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating Easter</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/18/celebrating-easter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/18/celebrating-easter/</guid>
      <description>Let me just start by saying that I loooove living in the northern hemisphere! The seasons and church calendar finally make sense! Christmas with snow, Easter with blossoms, summer holiday that doesn’t mix with Christmas. Celebrating Christmas here was great in that sense, and Easter is looking promising too.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
