<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Parks on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/category/parks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Parks on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/category/parks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Time travel into the past: July 2017</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2018/03/14/time-travel-into-the-past-july-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2018/03/14/time-travel-into-the-past-july-2017/</guid>
      <description>Life’s been happening by the spade full around here, and blogging has been severely neglected, sorry. Here’s an attempt at rectifying that!
Back in July last year… hmmm, let’s see if the photos can remind me that far back!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip ’16: Six Flags</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/11/04/roadtrip-16-six-flags/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/11/04/roadtrip-16-six-flags/</guid>
      <description>For the last leg of our roadtrip home, we made a stop at Six Flags in the south of New Jersey. They have a program called Read To Succeed where the kids have to read a total of 600 hours in the year to get free tickets to Six Flags.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homeschool field trip</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/07/10/homeschool-field-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/07/10/homeschool-field-trip/</guid>
      <description>One weekend in May we took the girls in to the Ancient Egyptian section of the Metropolitan Museum of Art, because in our history program we’d been studying Ancient Egypt. It was great to see many of the things we (including myself!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camping in the wilds of New Jersey</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/03/camping-in-the-wilds-of-new-jersey/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/03/camping-in-the-wilds-of-new-jersey/</guid>
      <description>The first weekend in September we went camping with Lillian and Jeremy and Shanna at High Point State Park. We didn’t really know what to expect, seeing that we had never been there before, but we were up for trying it — our very first camping trip in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A visit to Moab and Arches National Park</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/10/25/a-visit-to-moab-and-arches-national-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/10/25/a-visit-to-moab-and-arches-national-park/</guid>
      <description>One of the scenic highlights of our roadtrip was the state of Utah, where we went to Arches National Park, and drove through Monument Valley on our way to the Grand Canyon. We both loved the Grand Canyon (post still coming!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helping to push</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/18/helping-to-push/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/18/helping-to-push/</guid>
      <description>We were having a picnic in Prospect Park when Lizel was here and there was this man doing his stretches against a tree.
We joked with the kids that the man was trying to push over the tree, and do they want to go and help him?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring is here! (and some going away thoughts)</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/27/spring-is-here-and-some-going-away-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/27/spring-is-here-and-some-going-away-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>It seems that spring came a month early this year, after a winter that seemed like it never quite happened. Last year we had so much snow, this year, nothing to speak of. So much for the nice sturdy new toboggan I bought last autumn!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adventures with hippos</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/12/adventures-with-hippos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/12/adventures-with-hippos/</guid>
      <description>In Central Park there is this cool playground that has a herd of hippos made out of fibre glass (?? I guess). The kids always think it’s fun to pretend to ride the hippos.
So do some of the adults.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking kids on a photo shoot can be interesting</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/03/taking-kids-on-a-photo-shoot-can-be-interesting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/03/taking-kids-on-a-photo-shoot-can-be-interesting/</guid>
      <description>And also pretty fun.
Perhaps “photo shoot” is too formal a title for what we did with Jeremy and Lillian, but I still tried to get a heap of photos while at the same time trying to keep an eye on two speedy escape artists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now for the black and white engagement pics</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/01/now-for-the-black-and-white-engagement-pics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/01/now-for-the-black-and-white-engagement-pics/</guid>
      <description>As I said earlier, my previous post kept freezing up because I had too many photos in there, so I instead made the first post the colour post and this one the black&amp;amp;white post. I personally often prefer black and white, so this was fun for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The last one bites the dust</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/01/the-last-one-bites-the-dust/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/01/the-last-one-bites-the-dust/</guid>
      <description>But that makes it sound like it’s a bad thing when it is indeed a very happy thing — the last of 8 children getting married. Yes, that’s right, Ben’s little sister, Lillian, is engaged to be married to a certain Mr Jeremy Fisher, uh, I mean Mr Jeremy L Eshelman!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer is here!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/16/summer-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/16/summer-is-here/</guid>
      <description>And we’ve well and truly been out and about enjoying it. We’ve only had two very hot days and for the rest of the time it has been pretty much perfect weather (25 - 30 C).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful Brooklyn Botanic Garden</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/21/beautiful-brooklyn-botanic-garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/21/beautiful-brooklyn-botanic-garden/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weeks ago, we went to the Brooklyn Botanic Garden with our friends Julie and Abby Murphy and Damaris and her 2 cute kids, Elijah and Sophia.
The gardens were amazingly beautiful and dressed in their Spring finest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marica the soccer player</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/19/marica-the-soccer-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/19/marica-the-soccer-player/</guid>
      <description>Friends of ours recently invited Marica to join a little informal ‘soccer’ team that will practice just until the start of the summer. Marica has loved her Saturday morning soccer practices and all the games the coach lets them play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musings on New York, the weather, and teeth.</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/26/musings-on-new-york-the-weather-and-teeth/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/26/musings-on-new-york-the-weather-and-teeth/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been sharing a lot of photos and telling you about stuff we’ve seen and experienced lately (and there’s a lot more to come!), but I thought I’d just give you a little update on how we’re all doing, as well as some related thoughts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring is knocking on Winter’s door!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/22/spring-is-knocking-on-winters-door/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/22/spring-is-knocking-on-winters-door/</guid>
      <description>The crocuses are out! And some mini irises too. I hope to see some daffodils soon!
We spotted these cuties in Central Park last Saturday.
Aren’t these just so gorgeous? These flowers we saw in Fort Tryon Park near The Cloisters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let it snow, let it snow, let it snow!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/27/let-it-snow-let-it-snow-let-it-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/27/let-it-snow-let-it-snow-let-it-snow/</guid>
      <description>It started snowing on Sunday morning and continued snowing through the night. This morning we woke up to almost 2 feet of snow and a totally transformed neighborhood.
This is what it looked like trying to get out of our metal gate:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enjoying Fall</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/15/enjoying-fall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/15/enjoying-fall/</guid>
      <description>Two weekends ago we visited friends from church for lunch who recently got married, Franco and Neli. Franco grew up in NYC and Neli is from Peru. They’re a really lovely couple!
Franco and Neli live in a tall apartment building a block away from Central Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playing tourist again: Bronx Zoo</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/02/playing-tourist-again-bronx-zoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/02/playing-tourist-again-bronx-zoo/</guid>
      <description>A couple of Saturdays ago we bundled up and visited the Bronx Zoo. It is the biggest metropolitan zoo in the world, and we certainly didn’t see all of it in the day we were there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who said there’s no such thing as a free lunch?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/15/free-lunch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/15/free-lunch/</guid>
      <description>Autumn (or “fall” as it is called here) has come and school has started up again after a good hot summer. It’s been a full summer for us and we’re glad for things to start settling a bit, not to mention glad for a hint of some cooler weather.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quirky New York</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/10/quirky-new-york/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/10/quirky-new-york/</guid>
      <description>So far we’ve noticed a few quirky things here in New York.
For instance, the light switches are the other way around than in NZ - up is on and down is off. I still get confused.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The city that never sleeps</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/05/31/the-city-that-never-sleeps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/05/31/the-city-that-never-sleeps/</guid>
      <description>I can’t believe we’ve only been in NYC for 4 nights — it feels much longer. I’m sure that this is because we haven’t exactly slept very well. Jet lag aside, we’ve had some interesting night-time sound experiences.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
