<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nature on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/category/nature/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nature on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/category/nature/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful autumn</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/12/23/beautiful-autumn-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/12/23/beautiful-autumn-2/</guid>
      <description>Autumn this year was beautiful and mild and felt like a sort of nicer continuation of summer. We were, of course, back at doing school, but we tried to enjoy the nice weather as much as we could.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip ’16: Camping in TN</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/09/23/roadtrip-16-camping-in-tn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/09/23/roadtrip-16-camping-in-tn/</guid>
      <description>After our visit to Monticello we started the drive down to Cherokee National Forest in east Tennessee where we planned on camping for a couple of nights. We started off in the rain and the rain just got heavier and heavier, and there were predictions for a huge storm to pass over where we were going to camp that night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to New Zealand, part 2</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/02/05/visit-to-new-zealand-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/02/05/visit-to-new-zealand-part-2/</guid>
      <description>A couple of days after we arrived, we headed out of town to Mt Hutt in the Southern Alps for a Hoyt reunion. I think it had been the first time in almost 6 years that everyone were together again — Mum &amp;amp; Dad, all 8 siblings, plus spouses and kids — and it was fantastic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple picking day</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/12/04/apple-picking-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/12/04/apple-picking-day/</guid>
      <description>On a lovely warm day back in October, the girls and I took a field trip to a farm about an hour’s drive from where we live to go apple and pumpkin picking. The weather was fantastic — it was nice and sunny and not too hot or cold, a real Goldilocks kind of day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful autumn</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/11/20/beautiful-autumn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/11/20/beautiful-autumn/</guid>
      <description>I have a love-hate relationship with autumn. I love all the beautiful colors, the cooler weather and the fun things the season brings like apples, cinnamon, pumpkin pie and hot chocolate. But… autumn is the start of a long cold spell that only keeps getting worse for about 5 months before it starts getting better!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A summary of summer, part 3</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/09/19/a-summary-of-summer-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/09/19/a-summary-of-summer-part-3/</guid>
      <description>August was filled to the brim with activity. We said goodbye to our Chinese exchange students, and celebrated Ben’s birthday.
We swam a few times in our friend’s nearby pool, but also did a fun day trip out to go swim at a water hole our friend Sarah knows about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black and white trees</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/03/20/black-and-white-trees/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/03/20/black-and-white-trees/</guid>
      <description>I love the way leaf-less trees look so stark in black and white.
These photos were taken in Prospect Park, Brooklyn a couple of years back.
And this one in Lancaster County.
March was heralded in by a snowstorm, and it looked like this in front of our house just a couple of weeks ago:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autumn baby</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/02/autumn-baby-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/02/autumn-baby-2/</guid>
      <description>For our November Frog Pond class, I went a little click-happy with Laurelin while the older girls were busy. She was in a particularly good mood and I was able to get quite a few happy shots of her outside, enjoying the leaves and dirt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October Fest</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/11/21/october-fest/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/11/21/october-fest/</guid>
      <description>One weekend in October we went to an October Fest (not the beer-drinking kind) hosted by the Essex County Environmental Center, the same place where the girls go for their Frog Pond Science Club. It was a lovely community event where all the things on offer were free — crafts, a petting zoo, a snake man, music, and even some snacks!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camping in the wilds of New Jersey</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/03/camping-in-the-wilds-of-new-jersey/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/03/camping-in-the-wilds-of-new-jersey/</guid>
      <description>The first weekend in September we went camping with Lillian and Jeremy and Shanna at High Point State Park. We didn’t really know what to expect, seeing that we had never been there before, but we were up for trying it — our very first camping trip in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pretty little gift</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/07/04/pretty-little-gift/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/07/04/pretty-little-gift/</guid>
      <description>Where we live now, we have no garden, which is a bit of a shame. The other day, though, we were outside and the girls were riding their bikes on the sidewalk when Esther brought these little flowers to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yosemite!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/08/09/yosemite/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/08/09/yosemite/</guid>
      <description>Yo’s Mite. That’s how I always thought you pronounced Yosemite (having only ever seen it written). Now I know better. Just think Yo’s Cemetery without the ‘r’ and you’re set. :-)
One of the many things I love about the States is how varied the scenery is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip: Mono Lake</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/07/30/roadtrip-mono-lake/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/07/30/roadtrip-mono-lake/</guid>
      <description>I’m determined to finish the posts of our roadtrip, despite it now being almost exactly a year since we’ve been back in New Zealand.
After our stop in Lone Pine, we drove north to Yosemite National Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Grand Canyon</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/11/22/the-grand-canyon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/11/22/the-grand-canyon/</guid>
      <description>No tourist’s visit to the west of the U.S. is complete without a stop at the Grand Canyon, and we were no exception. We stayed in a little village (consisting mostly of the motel and gift shop) called Cameron for a couple of nights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A visit to Moab and Arches National Park</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/10/25/a-visit-to-moab-and-arches-national-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/10/25/a-visit-to-moab-and-arches-national-park/</guid>
      <description>One of the scenic highlights of our roadtrip was the state of Utah, where we went to Arches National Park, and drove through Monument Valley on our way to the Grand Canyon. We both loved the Grand Canyon (post still coming!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garden of the Gods at sunrise</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/10/09/garden-of-the-gods-at-sunrise/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/10/09/garden-of-the-gods-at-sunrise/</guid>
      <description>When we were visiting the Boonzaaijers’ in Colorado Springs, I decided to get up early one morning to go and take some photos of the Garden of the Gods. I had heard that it was particularly beautiful at sunrise, so I got up at 5am and headed on down there, just as the sky was changing colour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to the Boonzaaijers’</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/09/19/visit-to-the-boonzaaijers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/09/19/visit-to-the-boonzaaijers/</guid>
      <description>So, getting around to posting these last roadtrip posts have crawled to a terribly slow pace, but I’m determined to finish them up. When I get to that point, I’ll evaluate whether or not I keep AliensInTheApple going, or change its name, or just say “So long, and thanks for all the fish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Knoxville and the Smoky Mountains</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/28/more-knoxville-and-the-smoky-mountains/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/28/more-knoxville-and-the-smoky-mountains/</guid>
      <description>We spent 10 nights in Knoxville with Ben’s Uncle Ron and Aunt Marti, and his cousins Hannah and Eva.
This happened already well over two weeks ago, and I’m only now getting around to telling y’all about it (can you tell I’m in the south?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wildflowers</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/21/wildflowers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/21/wildflowers/</guid>
      <description>I snapped these little beauties on the Davys’ farm near Darfield. Anyone know what they’re called?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cool wood grain</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/15/cool-wood-grain/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/15/cool-wood-grain/</guid>
      <description>I saw this beam at the farm we stayed at when we took Lizel to Lancaster County, and really liked the way the wood grain showed up on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring is here! (and some going away thoughts)</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/27/spring-is-here-and-some-going-away-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/27/spring-is-here-and-some-going-away-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>It seems that spring came a month early this year, after a winter that seemed like it never quite happened. Last year we had so much snow, this year, nothing to speak of. So much for the nice sturdy new toboggan I bought last autumn!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Special time with Pappa</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/24/special-time-with-pappa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/24/special-time-with-pappa/</guid>
      <description>I think the Pennsylvanian countryside is just so beautiful. It seems very peaceful to me, perhaps because I’m usually on holiday when I’m there.
When we took Lizel there when she visited, Marica stayed with dear friends who took her to a ballet concert, so Esther got to be the only child for a weekend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If llamas could get braces…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/20/if-llamas-could-get-braces/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/20/if-llamas-could-get-braces/</guid>
      <description>…then this guy would set off a metal detector a mile away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Droplets</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/27/droplets/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/27/droplets/</guid>
      <description>I visited Margaret and her family on a drizzly Sunday afternoon in January, and just had to take a photo of this plant in her garden. The water droplets seemed to just stick to it in such a pretty way!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lovely lavender, and a bee to boot</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/23/lovely-lavender-and-a-bee-to-boot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/23/lovely-lavender-and-a-bee-to-boot/</guid>
      <description>I’ve got so many photos I’d like to share from my time in New Zealand, but time is eluding me. The photos in the post today were taken in Christchurch, in the new Cashel Mall where they have a mall made out of shipping containers that have been refurbished, and looks way better than it sounds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yellow Orchid</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/13/yellow-orchid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/13/yellow-orchid/</guid>
      <description>I took this photo at the Eshelmans’ place over Christmas time. What a cheery little yellow fellow!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black and white, day 15</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/30/black-and-white-day-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/30/black-and-white-day-15/</guid>
      <description>A pier on a lake in the Adirondacks. October 2011.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black and white, day 14</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/29/black-and-white-day-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/29/black-and-white-day-14/</guid>
      <description>Niagara Falls. October 2011.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stop 3 on the trip</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/14/stop-3-on-the-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/14/stop-3-on-the-trip/</guid>
      <description>Just a little note: I’m not blogging real-time. I think I might have blogged about something on the same day it happened about twice in the whole time I’ve had this blog. I just don’t have the luxury of lots of time to be able to do that!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magnificent Niagara Falls</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/10/magnificent-niagara-falls/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/10/magnificent-niagara-falls/</guid>
      <description>After our 3 nights in the Adirondack mountains, we drove to Niagara Falls. The scenery on the way was beautiful!
Crossing the border into Canada.
We arrived on a cold, windy, overcast afternoon, but didn’t know whether the weather would clear up over the weekend, so decided to brave it and go look at the falls regardless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some nature shots from the Adirondacks</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/07/some-nature-shots-from-the-adirondacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/07/some-nature-shots-from-the-adirondacks/</guid>
      <description>During our time in the Adirondacks it rained most of the time, except for our first afternoon there. There were some breaks in the rain, though, and I took my chances to go outside and take some ‘nature shots’.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
