<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Uncategorized on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/category/uncategorized/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Uncategorized on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/category/uncategorized/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A cool video Marica made</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2018/02/12/a-cool-video-marica-made/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2018/02/12/a-cool-video-marica-made/</guid>
      <description>Marica has been taking photos of everyday beauty (mostly during our time in NZ), editing them, and has turned them into a nice little video, which I’d like to share with you below. Proud Mama moment!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1920’s Day at co-op</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/03/27/1920s-day-at-co-op/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/03/27/1920s-day-at-co-op/</guid>
      <description>In February we had a 1920’s festival at our homeschool co-op where we learned about some things that happened in the 1920’s in general, and in our area (Thomas Edison, who lived nearby, was actively inventing cool things; the Holland Tunnel between NJ and Manhattan was being built); we got to dress up in fun costumes, someone came in to teach us how to dance the Charleston, and we had a 1920’s themed feast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/12/25/merry-christmas-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/12/25/merry-christmas-4/</guid>
      <description>Merry Christmas to all of you, from all of us!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Veggie Garden</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/11/18/our-veggie-garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/11/18/our-veggie-garden/</guid>
      <description>(Though perhaps a better title would have been My Veggie Garden, but I’m generously including Ben because he heaved heavy compost bags and helped with digging and building a frame for my beans.)
I decided that this year I’d like to have a veggie garden again after not having one for three summers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip ’16: Chincoteague</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/10/21/roadtrip-16-chincoteague/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/10/21/roadtrip-16-chincoteague/</guid>
      <description>After our stint in Charleston, we had a long but beautiful drive up to Chincoteague, VA. Our reason for visiting was because we had recently listened to Misty of Chincoteague on audio and loved the story, and seeing that it was sort of on our way home, thought it would be cool to stop and see the area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip ’16: Charleston, SC</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/10/07/roadtrip-16-charleston-sc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/10/07/roadtrip-16-charleston-sc/</guid>
      <description>It was with heavy hearts that we said our goodbyes after the Hoyt reunion, but it was time to start making our way home. Because Ben was in between jobs at that point, he could take off some extra time and we decided to take the trip back up a little more slowly to stop at a few places we were interested in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A morning in the big city</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/08/05/a-morning-in-the-big-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/08/05/a-morning-in-the-big-city/</guid>
      <description>I’m playing catch-up here on the blog after my long silence. We start back at school in 3 weeks or so, but it feels as though we’ve hardly started vacation. Summer for us here in the US seems to be filled with more activity than during the school year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holy bubbles</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/04/15/its-too-serious-to-be-funny/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/04/15/its-too-serious-to-be-funny/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been searching for a preschool for Laurelin for a couple of mornings a week. I think it’ll be good for her, and it will help the two older girls and me get a bit more done in school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to New Zealand, part 1</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/01/29/visit-to-new-zealand-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/01/29/visit-to-new-zealand-part-1/</guid>
      <description>How do you describe a place? I can tell you about beautiful green rolling hills, changeable weather, children walking barefoot down the road without anyone scowling at them. I can tell you about the lilt of an accent, of driving on the left side of the road, of great coffee — both instant and barista made.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/12/25/merry-christmas-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/12/25/merry-christmas-3/</guid>
      <description>To all the lovely readers of our blog, we wish you a very Merry Christmas! May you be blessed today and in the year to come.
God rest ye merry, gentlemen,
Let nothing you dismay</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We’re still here…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/07/31/were-still-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/07/31/were-still-here/</guid>
      <description>I’m just taking a break from blogging to enjoy the summer, and spend time with visitors, the kids and to do all those fun activities that only happen in the summer. I hope to resume a regular blogging schedule again in late August.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A peek at spring</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/07/03/a-peek-at-spring/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/07/03/a-peek-at-spring/</guid>
      <description>April seems like a long time ago… spring seems like a bit of a blur filled with the house buying process and then packing and getting ready to move. But it wasn’t all crazy — we made some time to go enjoy the nice weather outside too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Win a copy of Side by Side!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/05/04/win-a-copy-of-side-by-side/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/05/04/win-a-copy-of-side-by-side/</guid>
      <description>If you are interested in winning a copy of Side by Side, you can click on this link to enter.
I had planned on including the link in my previous post, but completely forgot. You still have some time!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joyous December</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/23/joyous-december/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/23/joyous-december/</guid>
      <description>December is probably my favourite month of the year. I love the anticipation of Christmas, celebrating Advent, and all that it means: the King of the Universe becoming man to reconcile and restore us to Himself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frog Pond Science Club</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/11/14/frog-pond-science-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/11/14/frog-pond-science-club/</guid>
      <description>I signed Marica and Esther up for a “Frog Pond Science Club” class at the Essex County Environmental Center, which is about a half hour drive from our house heading into the mountains. Once you get past Newark, it’s a beautiful drive, especially this time of the year with all the autumn colours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The solution</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/01/30/the-solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/01/30/the-solution/</guid>
      <description>Oops… that must have been the longest 48 hours in the history of the world. And I know you’re all just bursting to know the answer to the riddle. (Not!)
What can see light but has never seen the sun;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/12/23/merry-christmas-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/12/23/merry-christmas-2/</guid>
      <description>May this Christmas be blessed as you celebrate the birth of Jesus, Saviour of the world!
&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip: San Francisco</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/10/14/roadtrip-san-francisco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/10/14/roadtrip-san-francisco/</guid>
      <description>We only had one day in San Francisco for sight-seeing, so naturally we didn’t see everything on the list, but we still saw a whole bunch of things!
We saw Alcatraz in the distance:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On our way home</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/07/30/on-our-way-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/07/30/on-our-way-home/</guid>
      <description>Though the term “home” is a strange one — maybe I should say we’re on our way to one of our homes? Poor Esther is so confused, having never known a different home than New York.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Today, two years ago…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/25/today-two-years-ago/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/25/today-two-years-ago/</guid>
      <description>Was our first day in New York City. Where did these two years go? This morning I told Marica the story of how she went missing in our first tiny apartment, shortly after I wrote the post linked to above.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
