<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2012s on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2012s on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why the blog has been rather neglected</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/11/26/why-the-blog-has-been-rather-neglected/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/11/26/why-the-blog-has-been-rather-neglected/</guid>
      <description>Those of you who have been following the blog for any time over the last 2.5 years or so will have noticed that there has been a marked drop in the frequency of posts here. The reason for that has partly been that coming back to New Zealand has made life busier in many ways and that the time to blog has diminished.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Grand Canyon</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/11/22/the-grand-canyon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/11/22/the-grand-canyon/</guid>
      <description>No tourist’s visit to the west of the U.S. is complete without a stop at the Grand Canyon, and we were no exception. We stayed in a little village (consisting mostly of the motel and gift shop) called Cameron for a couple of nights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Driving through Monument Valley</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/11/07/driving-through-monument-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/11/07/driving-through-monument-valley/</guid>
      <description>After our time in Moab and Arches National Park, we traveled south to the Grand Canyon. What we didn’t realise was that our road would take us right through Monument Valley, a beautiful and dramatic piece of creation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A visit to Moab and Arches National Park</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/10/25/a-visit-to-moab-and-arches-national-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/10/25/a-visit-to-moab-and-arches-national-park/</guid>
      <description>One of the scenic highlights of our roadtrip was the state of Utah, where we went to Arches National Park, and drove through Monument Valley on our way to the Grand Canyon. We both loved the Grand Canyon (post still coming!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garden of the Gods at sunrise</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/10/09/garden-of-the-gods-at-sunrise/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/10/09/garden-of-the-gods-at-sunrise/</guid>
      <description>When we were visiting the Boonzaaijers’ in Colorado Springs, I decided to get up early one morning to go and take some photos of the Garden of the Gods. I had heard that it was particularly beautiful at sunrise, so I got up at 5am and headed on down there, just as the sky was changing colour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to the Boonzaaijers’</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/09/19/visit-to-the-boonzaaijers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/09/19/visit-to-the-boonzaaijers/</guid>
      <description>So, getting around to posting these last roadtrip posts have crawled to a terribly slow pace, but I’m determined to finish them up. When I get to that point, I’ll evaluate whether or not I keep AliensInTheApple going, or change its name, or just say “So long, and thanks for all the fish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manitou Cliff Dwellings</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/09/11/manitou-cliff-dwellings/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/09/11/manitou-cliff-dwellings/</guid>
      <description>After the Tschetter reunion we stopped at the Manitou cliff dwellings museum on our way to visit Ben’s cousin Erica and her family in Colorado Springs.
Call me thick, but I only just realised after reading wikipedia that the cliff dwellings are not original, but instead have been relocated to their current location.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Return to the Roadtrip: On to the Tschetter Reunion</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/08/27/return-to-the-roadtrip-on-to-the-tschetter-reunion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/08/27/return-to-the-roadtrip-on-to-the-tschetter-reunion/</guid>
      <description>Some of you might recall that it was at the Tschetter reunion (Ben’s mum’s side of the family) that my laptop hard drive died, so I lost photos of the first half of that stop as well, which is a real shame because Ben’s mum’s Uncle Herb and Aunt Susan came to visit one evening and I got some really nice shots of them, but hey, so’s life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On being home</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/08/15/on-being-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/08/15/on-being-home/</guid>
      <description>So yes, as Ben informed you about 2 weeks ago, we’re back in Christchurch! I can hardly believe it’s been two weeks, because it’s been so busy with unpacking and getting right into things here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We’re back</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/08/04/were-back-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/08/04/were-back-3/</guid>
      <description>We’ve arrived safely back in Christchurch, thanks to God. And our home really feels like home already, so thanks everyone for your welcome and your help!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On our way home</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/07/30/on-our-way-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/07/30/on-our-way-home/</guid>
      <description>Though the term “home” is a strange one — maybe I should say we’re on our way to one of our homes? Poor Esther is so confused, having never known a different home than New York.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photoless reporting is not quite my style</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/07/21/photoless-reporting-is-not-quite-my-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/07/21/photoless-reporting-is-not-quite-my-style/</guid>
      <description>I’m finding it hard to keep up the blogging while we’re on the road, as you’ve no doubt realised! Not that it’s going to stop me trying. I’ll start by giving a quick run down of what happened after the Hoyt reunion up to the point where I’ve got photos again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip stop 5: Hoyt Reunion in Georgia</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/07/13/roadtrip-stop-5-hoyt-reunion-in-georgia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/07/13/roadtrip-stop-5-hoyt-reunion-in-georgia/</guid>
      <description>In mid-June, we spent a fantastic week in Georgia with some fantastic people at our Hoyt family reunion. Uncle Stan and Aunt Nora hosted us very well. There were great activities, delicious food, lots of fun times joking around, playing games, catching up and having a blast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I’m in denial</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/07/06/im-in-denial/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/07/06/im-in-denial/</guid>
      <description>Two days ago, I was sitting on my bed editing some photos in Picasa, having just cleared my camera memory stick of about 500 more photos and video clips. The total number of photos taken on our roadtrip so far were well over a thousand and I was doing well keeping up to date with deleting the bad ones, editing the ones that needed a bit of lightening or the like, even if I haven’t been the greatest at updating the blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip, stop 4: Atlanta</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/30/roadtrip-stop-4-atlanta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/30/roadtrip-stop-4-atlanta/</guid>
      <description>After visiting the Holders in Knoxville, TN, we travelled down to Atlanta. For some reason our GPS took us on the scenic route instead of the Interstate, which was a nice change of pace and a very beautiful drive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Knoxville and the Smoky Mountains</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/28/more-knoxville-and-the-smoky-mountains/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/28/more-knoxville-and-the-smoky-mountains/</guid>
      <description>We spent 10 nights in Knoxville with Ben’s Uncle Ron and Aunt Marti, and his cousins Hannah and Eva.
This happened already well over two weeks ago, and I’m only now getting around to telling y’all about it (can you tell I’m in the south?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whimsical</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/27/whimsical/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/27/whimsical/</guid>
      <description>I love this photo — I took it when we were in the Smoky Mountains with the Holders.
Consider this a teaser until I get a post up with the rest of our photos from our time in Knoxville.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Knoxville Farmers’ Market</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/18/the-knoxville-farmers-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/18/the-knoxville-farmers-market/</guid>
      <description>Today is our second day at the Hoyt reunion in Georgia. Since I’ve last blogged we’ve visited the Holders in Knoxville, and some friends in Atlanta. I hope to blog about that soon, but I need to catch up with sharing some of the things we did in Knoxville first!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Roadtrip, stop 2</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/10/the-roadtrip-stop-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/10/the-roadtrip-stop-2/</guid>
      <description>After our first stop in Connecticut with the Snoeks, we headed down to Philadelphia where we stayed with Lillian and Jeremy and visited with several friends over the course of the weekend.
On the way to Lillian and Jeremy we stopped and Sam and Emily Perez’s home, friends from our church in New York.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The start of The Roadtrip</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/06/the-start-of-the-roadtrip/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/06/the-start-of-the-roadtrip/</guid>
      <description>We had a rather stressful start to our roadtrip. I was overly optimistic (or foolish?) and hoped that everything might just fit into 6 suitcases plus a bunch of little bits and pieces. My reasoning for this was that I couldn’t see us parting with much more — I only kept the things I really wanted to and had gotten rid of more than felt comfortable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We’ve hit the road!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/04/weve-hit-the-road/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/04/weve-hit-the-road/</guid>
      <description>The last week has been a crazy whirlwind of activity. We got rid of a lot of stuff, selling some things on Craigslist, selling a bunch of things at our stoop sale and giving loads of stuff away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love poem to New York</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/31/love-poem-to-new-york/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/31/love-poem-to-new-york/</guid>
      <description>New York…
Your name invoked images, awe, presumptions
of ghetto, gangster, glamour, glitz.
Yet many will be surprised to know
I found in you much goodness and grace
just as ingrained
as the grit and grime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Today, two years ago…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/25/today-two-years-ago/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/25/today-two-years-ago/</guid>
      <description>Was our first day in New York City. Where did these two years go? This morning I told Marica the story of how she went missing in our first tiny apartment, shortly after I wrote the post linked to above.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Packing up, cleaning out, giving away, selling…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/24/packing-up-cleaning-out-giving-away-selling/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/24/packing-up-cleaning-out-giving-away-selling/</guid>
      <description>That’s what I’m doing a lot of at the moment. And I’m seriously worried about this 4 suitcase limit. I’m just praying that our rental car can fit more than that because just our family’s clothing takes up 3 suitcases!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wildflowers</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/21/wildflowers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/21/wildflowers/</guid>
      <description>I snapped these little beauties on the Davys’ farm near Darfield. Anyone know what they’re called?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helping to push</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/18/helping-to-push/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/18/helping-to-push/</guid>
      <description>We were having a picnic in Prospect Park when Lizel was here and there was this man doing his stretches against a tree.
We joked with the kids that the man was trying to push over the tree, and do they want to go and help him?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cool wood grain</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/15/cool-wood-grain/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/15/cool-wood-grain/</guid>
      <description>I saw this beam at the farm we stayed at when we took Lizel to Lancaster County, and really liked the way the wood grain showed up on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 3-step guide for mothers who want to Do It All</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/10/the-3-step-guide-for-mothers-who-want-to-do-it-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/10/the-3-step-guide-for-mothers-who-want-to-do-it-all/</guid>
      <description>Yes, you too can Do It All! Small children? A big workload? Stack of dishes in the sink? Pile of bills to pay? No problem! Just follow my easy 3-step program and soon you too could be one of those special people who can Do It All!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some people just can’t eat cake like normal people</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/30/some-people-just-cant-eat-cake-like-normal-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/30/some-people-just-cant-eat-cake-like-normal-people/</guid>
      <description>Some of you might remember Jeremy and Lillian’s bizarre cake eating rituals at their wedding ceremony in New Zealand. Well, it would seem the strangeness just keeps on going.
Just look at the mess they made of my beautiful lemon cake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring is here! (and some going away thoughts)</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/27/spring-is-here-and-some-going-away-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/27/spring-is-here-and-some-going-away-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>It seems that spring came a month early this year, after a winter that seemed like it never quite happened. Last year we had so much snow, this year, nothing to speak of. So much for the nice sturdy new toboggan I bought last autumn!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Special time with Pappa</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/24/special-time-with-pappa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/24/special-time-with-pappa/</guid>
      <description>I think the Pennsylvanian countryside is just so beautiful. It seems very peaceful to me, perhaps because I’m usually on holiday when I’m there.
When we took Lizel there when she visited, Marica stayed with dear friends who took her to a ballet concert, so Esther got to be the only child for a weekend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If llamas could get braces…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/20/if-llamas-could-get-braces/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/20/if-llamas-could-get-braces/</guid>
      <description>…then this guy would set off a metal detector a mile away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The beauty of a farmers’ market</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/18/the-beauty-of-a-farmers-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/18/the-beauty-of-a-farmers-market/</guid>
      <description>I love markets of any kind, but I especially like farmers’ markets. I can’t explain it — they just make me happy in the same way that flowers make me happy. On Saturdays there is a farmers’ market at Prospect Park, and we’ve been there a couple of times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My daddy is stronger than your daddy</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/16/my-daddy-is-stronger-than-your-daddy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/16/my-daddy-is-stronger-than-your-daddy/</guid>
      <description>I know I’m thoroughly biased, but this photo just melts my heart. Our girls sure are blessed to have such a wonderful daddy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Because your dog is worth it</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/14/because-your-dog-is-worth-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/14/because-your-dog-is-worth-it/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adventures with hippos</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/12/adventures-with-hippos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/12/adventures-with-hippos/</guid>
      <description>In Central Park there is this cool playground that has a herd of hippos made out of fibre glass (?? I guess). The kids always think it’s fun to pretend to ride the hippos.
So do some of the adults.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 years of friendship, and still going strong</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/10/20-years-of-friendship-and-still-going-strong/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/10/20-years-of-friendship-and-still-going-strong/</guid>
      <description>In March, my friend Lizel visited us from South Africa.
Lizel and I have been close friends since we were seven years old, despite living apart for 15 of those. As kids, we would do all sorts of crazy things like pelt the neighbour’s house with mud cookies, or knock on people’s doors and run away, or take whoopie cushions into shops and walk through the aisles making farting noises.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I met The Pioneer Woman!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/05/i-met-the-pioneer-woman/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/05/i-met-the-pioneer-woman/</guid>
      <description>I recently had the fun experience of going to a book signing. It was fun, because I got to head out by myself for an evening, and fun because I got to meet someone semi-famous. I say semi-famous because if you don’t frequent food blogs or watch food shows on TV, you’ve probably never heard of The Pioneer Woman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blessed hands, broken grammar</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/02/blessed-hands-broken-grammar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/02/blessed-hands-broken-grammar/</guid>
      <description>Saw this the other day near where we live and couldn’t help but chuckle a little. You need to read the sign in the window too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Droplets</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/27/droplets/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/27/droplets/</guid>
      <description>I visited Margaret and her family on a drizzly Sunday afternoon in January, and just had to take a photo of this plant in her garden. The water droplets seemed to just stick to it in such a pretty way!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books we’ve read recently</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/24/books-weve-read-recently/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/24/books-weve-read-recently/</guid>
      <description>For your interest, here’s a list of some of the books we’ve read in the last year or so, with a tiny summary of each. Most of them are really good. I’ve put B after the author’s name if only I’ve read it, F if just Franci’s read it, or BF if we’ve both read it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A few post-earthquake photos</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/22/a-few-post-earthquake-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/22/a-few-post-earthquake-photos/</guid>
      <description>This is my last post about my trip to Christchurch in January. It’s about time, I think! This post is largely for our US readers who have expressed interest in the earthquake side of things back home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Enlightenment Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/19/quantum-enlightenment-dynamics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/19/quantum-enlightenment-dynamics/</guid>
      <description>The other day we received an incredible free magazine: NEWLIFE EXPO — America’s Largest Mind, Body, Spirit Expo. Its highly intelligent content, its carefully-placed typos, and its cohesive aesthetic have provided Franci and me with more belly laughs than any comedy magazine ever could.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Because we’re so normal</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/15/because-were-so-normal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/15/because-were-so-normal/</guid>
      <description>We sometimes have dinner wearing cabbage leaf hats.
(Well, only if I’m making coleslaw to go with our pulled pork and need to get rid of some cabbage leaves!)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marica turned 5</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/12/marica-turned-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/12/marica-turned-5/</guid>
      <description>How is it that they go from this…
to this…
so unbelievably fast?
Too fast, that’s what. I’m sure someone’s been speeding up the time.
Marica turned 5 in February, but when we were in New Zealand, my mum (Ouma to the kids) threw a birthday party for Marica.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reconnecting with friends and family</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/08/reconnecting-with-friends-and-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/08/reconnecting-with-friends-and-family/</guid>
      <description>When the girls and I were in New Zealand, we had quite the social time visiting friends and family. The kids got so used to going out and visiting people that if we had the odd morning where we weren’t going out they’d ask, “aren’t we going to visit someone today?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lovely lavender, and a bee to boot</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/23/lovely-lavender-and-a-bee-to-boot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/23/lovely-lavender-and-a-bee-to-boot/</guid>
      <description>I’ve got so many photos I’d like to share from my time in New Zealand, but time is eluding me. The photos in the post today were taken in Christchurch, in the new Cashel Mall where they have a mall made out of shipping containers that have been refurbished, and looks way better than it sounds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Malboro Man sandwich</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/20/a-malboro-man-sandwich/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/20/a-malboro-man-sandwich/</guid>
      <description>I’m subsribed to The Pioneer Woman Cooks blog, and with every recipe that comes from there I’m almost drooling. I’ve never had one of her recipes fail, and they’re always a hit. The Malboro Man Sandwich was especially a hit with Ben, and I loved it too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More wedding pictures</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/16/more-wedding-pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/16/more-wedding-pictures/</guid>
      <description>Well, I said I’d share some more wedding pictures when I got some time to get them on here. I didn’t get the time, but I made the time, so here they are.
The first lot of photos were taken outside in the harsh sunlight (always a bad move), so unfortunately everyone has sunglass shadows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeremy and Lillian’s wedding day</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/14/jeremy-and-lillians-wedding-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/14/jeremy-and-lillians-wedding-day/</guid>
      <description>On January the 21st Jeremy and Lillian tied the knot, and it was a beautiful day in all respects. It was lovely and sunny (even it if was a bit windy), everything went smoothly and it was just such a joyous day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yellow Orchid</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/13/yellow-orchid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/13/yellow-orchid/</guid>
      <description>I took this photo at the Eshelmans’ place over Christmas time. What a cheery little yellow fellow!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Fat Bacon Sliders</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/11/big-fat-bacon-sliders/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/11/big-fat-bacon-sliders/</guid>
      <description>Bacon is a beautiful thing. Whoever invented it needs a medal. Bacon and eggs, bacon on pizza, bacon in pasta, bacon with pretty much anything is just wonderful. (I’ve even seen bacon chocolate here in New York!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We’re back!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/09/were-back-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/09/were-back-2/</guid>
      <description>The girls and I arrived safely back in New York City on Monday night after three flights over 26 hours. We had a fantastic time back in New Zealand reconnecting with friends and family and enjoying Jeremy and Lillian’s wedding, but we’re very happy to be home with Ben again!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black and white, day 16</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/31/black-and-white-day-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/31/black-and-white-day-16/</guid>
      <description>Today is the last day of the black and white series. Thanks for bearing with me. I hope you’re not all now sick and tired of black and white photographs — I love them!
Today’s photos are from when Ben and Marica attended the Nutcracker ballet, December 2011.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black and white, day 15</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/30/black-and-white-day-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/30/black-and-white-day-15/</guid>
      <description>A pier on a lake in the Adirondacks. October 2011.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black and white, day 14</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/29/black-and-white-day-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/29/black-and-white-day-14/</guid>
      <description>Niagara Falls. October 2011.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black and white, day 13</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/28/black-and-white-day-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/28/black-and-white-day-13/</guid>
      <description>Brooklyn Bridge. October 2011.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black and white, day 12</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/27/black-and-white-day-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/27/black-and-white-day-12/</guid>
      <description>Cheese shop in Philadelphia. October 2011.
I love this one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black and white, day 11</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/26/black-and-white-day-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/26/black-and-white-day-11/</guid>
      <description>Opposite hair day. October 2011.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black and white, day 10</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/25/black-and-white-day-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/25/black-and-white-day-10/</guid>
      <description>Sculpture by Aristide Maillol at the Metropolitan Museum of Art. September 2011.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black and white, day 9</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/24/black-and-white-day-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/24/black-and-white-day-9/</guid>
      <description>Coney Island Wonder Wheel. August 2011.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black and white, day 8</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/23/black-and-white-day-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/23/black-and-white-day-8/</guid>
      <description>The Statue of Liberty. March 2011.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black and white, day 7</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/22/black-and-white-day-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/22/black-and-white-day-7/</guid>
      <description>The girls and I in a hammock in enjoying each other’s company. June 2011.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black and white, day 6</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/21/black-and-white-day-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/21/black-and-white-day-6/</guid>
      <description>A statue of The Signer in Philadelphia.
This photo is significant, because today a man from Philadelphia is signing a very special contract with a very special lady in Christchurch. Yes, today Jeremy and Lillian are getting married!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black and white, day 5</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/20/black-and-white-day-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/20/black-and-white-day-5/</guid>
      <description>Trust.
Esther with Ben in Philadelphia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black and white, day 4</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/19/black-and-white-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/19/black-and-white-day-4/</guid>
      <description>Esther at the Brooklyn Botanic Garden, spring 2011.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black and white, day 3</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/18/black-and-white-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/18/black-and-white-day-3/</guid>
      <description>Marica on a bench in a subway station waiting for our train home after church. April 2011</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black and white, day 2</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/17/black-and-white-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/17/black-and-white-day-2/</guid>
      <description>A very interesting tree by Central Park, just opposite the Museum of Natural History.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bygone days; black and white day 1</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/16/bygone-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/16/bygone-days/</guid>
      <description>To start off the black and white series while I’m away, I thought I’d introduce you to Planter. He lives in the Eshelmans’ neighbors’ yard who had the lovely little thing refurbished all nice and new, parked it beside the house and haven’t touched it for about 15 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s been 7 years</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/15/its-been-7-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/15/its-been-7-years/</guid>
      <description>Today Ben and I celebrate 7 wonderful years of marriage. I can truly say that it gets better, deeper, and more beautiful to be married to Ben every single year. God has been so faithful and good to us by blessing our marriage, and we are thankful to Him for His enduring love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pics from Jeremy’s bachelor party</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/14/pics-from-jeremys-bachelor-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/14/pics-from-jeremys-bachelor-party/</guid>
      <description>Last Saturday afternoon and evening, a few of Jeremy’s Philadelphia friends organized a bachelor party for him. They captured him, got in a little bit of trouble with the Philly police, and drove him blind-folded all the way to New York, where I joined them for dinner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Christmas goodie report, with recipes</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/06/a-christmas-goodie-report-with-recipes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/06/a-christmas-goodie-report-with-recipes/</guid>
      <description>I love baking. I love sharing baking. I love receiving baking. I love eating baking. Who doesn’t?!
Christmas is always a time of the year that I excitedly go totally overboard in the baking department, making way too many goodies and loving every minute of it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another wonderful Christmas</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/04/another-wonderful-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/04/another-wonderful-christmas/</guid>
      <description>Christmas feels like such a long time ago… but I really want to share these photos with you from our time with Jeremy’s folks.
We took the bus to Philadelphia from where Jeremy picked us up and drove us out to his parents’ place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This little piggy</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/03/this-little-piggy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/03/this-little-piggy/</guid>
      <description>A black and white shot of Esther’s little feet, shortly before her 2nd birthday.
Happy New Year, everyone! We hope that the new year will be a blessed one.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
