<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Education on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/category/education/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Education on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/category/education/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Finishing up the school year</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/08/19/finishing-up-the-school-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/08/19/finishing-up-the-school-year/</guid>
      <description>It’s taken us a while to get used to this business of school finishing right in the middle of the calendar year and the starting again in August/September when we are so used to the school year following the calendar year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random thoughts</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/06/10/random-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/06/10/random-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>The last couple of months have looked a little different to our usual routines. I’ve had a relapse of the Epstein-Barr virus which wiped me out but I seem to be feeling a fair bit better the last week or so; Ben’s been looking at different job options and has had multiple interviews with several different companies (no decision yet, though).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Co-op class pizza night</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/05/20/co-op-class-pizza-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/05/20/co-op-class-pizza-night/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp;
I teach a Narnia literature class at our homeschool co-op, which has been really fun. For me, anyway. Not quite sure what the kids think, seeing that it’s a discussion class and I make them talk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What we’re doing in homeschooling this year</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/11/13/what-were-doing-in-homeschooling-this-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/11/13/what-were-doing-in-homeschooling-this-year/</guid>
      <description>We’ve been back in the full swing of the regular school year for a few months now, and I must admit that I find it hard to make the time to blog. It’s great to have the routines of school, but it does leave very little time for extra things, like blogging and other fun stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Medieval Feast</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/03/06/a-medieval-feast/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/03/06/a-medieval-feast/</guid>
      <description>Back in January, the homeschool co-op we attend put on a Medieval Feast. The organizers did a most spectacular job with the decorations, food and everything else that goes into organizing a big event like this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Entrepreneurial Fair</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/09/the-entrepreneurial-fair/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/09/the-entrepreneurial-fair/</guid>
      <description>The Co-op that we attend had an Entrepreneurial Fair early in December, and as much as I would have liked to just be a spectator, my kids were burning to sell stuff (surprise, surprise). So, we made Christmas ornaments, some chocolates and gingerbread men.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr Rubik’s back</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/05/08/mr-rubiks-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/05/08/mr-rubiks-back/</guid>
      <description>Marica and I went to the Liberty Science Center in Jersey City last Saturday to see their new Rubik’s Cube exhibition, which was being opened by Ernő Rubik, the inventor of the cube. I own a cube, but still have no idea how to solve it…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life in limbo</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/03/10/life-in-limbo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/03/10/life-in-limbo/</guid>
      <description>Since the last time I posted, we’ve moved into our temporary apartment for the month of March, settled into a daily routine with homeschooling in the mornings, and all of us have gotten sick. New climate, new bugs — it was to be expected!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting into the homeschooling groove</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/05/getting-into-the-homeschooling-groove/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/05/getting-into-the-homeschooling-groove/</guid>
      <description>Since Marica started preschool two days a week last year, I have been doing some casual schoolwork with her at home. When the school year finished and we decided to school her at home rather than send her to yet another school, we started making ‘school work’ more of a part of our daily routine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preschool poetry</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/05/preschool-poetry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/05/preschool-poetry/</guid>
      <description>Last Friday, Marica’s preschool put on a poetry recital that parents were invited to. The kids had all worked hard at memorising the poems — they recited 3 poems and then sung Mary had a little lamb, and they did really well!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How not to praise your kids</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/14/how-not-to-praise-your-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/14/how-not-to-praise-your-kids/</guid>
      <description>I just finished reading an online article by New York Magazine, How not to talk to your kids. It talked about a lot of research that has been done over the last few years about the effects of praise on children’s performance — how not to praise your kids’ intelligence, but their efforts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calculus for three-year-olds</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/12/calculus-for-three-year-olds/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/12/calculus-for-three-year-olds/</guid>
      <description>The other day Franci and I were talking about subjects we studied in high school, and Marica asked what “calculus” was. Franci said it was a type of maths (Marica’s been learning her written numbers). Marica of course replied that “she could do that”, but Franci said she was probably a bit young for calculus.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
