<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2011s on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2011s on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tips for new New Yorkers</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/29/tips-for-new-new-yorkers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/29/tips-for-new-new-yorkers/</guid>
      <description>It takes a lot of adjusting to live in the greatest city in the world, and there are some protocols that you should follow if you want to survive in this city. You might be a kind, generous and gentle person in the privacy of your own home, but follow these tips for how to act in public, and within a couple of weeks you will not only feel like a real New Yorker, but look like it to anyone watching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas in New York</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/27/christmas-in-new-york/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/27/christmas-in-new-york/</guid>
      <description>On Wednesday evening the kids and I met Ben at work and had a special treat of eating out (there’s a decent diner near his work) and then going to look at some of the Christmas light displays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Merry Christmas to you</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/24/a-merry-christmas-to-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/24/a-merry-christmas-to-you/</guid>
      <description>We want to take this opportunity to wish you all a very Merry Christmas as you celebrate with your loved ones. May you abound in joy as you remember the humble birth of the God-man, the King of Kings, our Prince of Peace, our Saviour Jesus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Autobiography of Benjamin Franklin</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/23/the-autobiography-of-benjamin-franklin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/23/the-autobiography-of-benjamin-franklin/</guid>
      <description>Some time ago Franci picked up a little, falling-apart paperback version of The Autobiography of Benjamin Franklin. As well as having a pretty respectable first name, Franklin was a fascinating character in many respects. Was he a printer, a writer, a politician, or an inventor?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gingerbread House fun</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/22/gingerbread-house-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/22/gingerbread-house-fun/</guid>
      <description>Our much loved pastor’s wife, Julie, invited a few moms over to her house last Friday to make gingerbread houses. What a total blast! We made the houses out of graham crackers instead of baked sheets of gingerbread, which was much easier and less time consuming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Christmas craft afternoon</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/20/a-christmas-craft-afternoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/20/a-christmas-craft-afternoon/</guid>
      <description>On an unseasonably warm Saturday late in November, a few women from our church gathered at our friend Jen’s house to make some Christmas crafts. It was bliss… lots of good chatting and food while being enjoyably creative and productive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nanaimo Bars</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/19/nanaimo-bars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/19/nanaimo-bars/</guid>
      <description>Let me introduce you to a lovely piece of goodness. This little bite of joy is apparently a Canadian treat, and when I saw a recipe for it online some months back, I knew it would be something Ben would enjoy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lovely hair</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/17/lovely-hair/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/17/lovely-hair/</guid>
      <description>A while back we girls had a fun afternoon of doing each other’s hair. I made Marica’s hair into a triple braid.
She was studiously doing her schoolwork while I took photos of her hair!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A visit to the New York City Ballet</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/15/a-visit-to-the-new-york-city-ballet-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/15/a-visit-to-the-new-york-city-ballet-2/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend our friend Megan, who dances in the New York City Ballet, gave us two tickets to attend The Nutcracker ballet at the Lincoln Centre, and Ben took Marica to go watch her dance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting excited about Christmas</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/12/getting-excited-about-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/12/getting-excited-about-christmas/</guid>
      <description>I love the month of December here in New York — I think it’s even my favourite time of the year, even better than beautiful spring-time April. It’s cold, but everyone seems to be in good spirits (as opposed to grumpy January!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent is here!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/10/advent-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/10/advent-is-here/</guid>
      <description>I started the blog post draft a few weeks back, and now the season of Advent is about halfway through. Last year we decided to start celebrating Advent in a more deliberate way, building the excitement until Christmas, and enjoying the anticipation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pizza!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/08/pizza/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/08/pizza/</guid>
      <description>I guess most of you know that there’s nothing much to homemade pizza, except that it can be time consuming. You can put pretty much anything on it, and cover it with cheese and you can call it pizza.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting into the homeschooling groove</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/05/getting-into-the-homeschooling-groove/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/05/getting-into-the-homeschooling-groove/</guid>
      <description>Since Marica started preschool two days a week last year, I have been doing some casual schoolwork with her at home. When the school year finished and we decided to school her at home rather than send her to yet another school, we started making ‘school work’ more of a part of our daily routine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caring for Creation</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/02/caring-for-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/02/caring-for-creation/</guid>
      <description>My friend Matthew Bartlett recently started his own publishing company, and his first book is The Biblical Mandate for Caring for Creation by retired New Zealand minister Dick Tripp. The 158-page book, which can be yours for a mere $24.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Esther’s turned two!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/01/esthers-turned-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/01/esthers-turned-two/</guid>
      <description>I was going to start by saying that Esther turned two just last week. But then I realised that it would almost be more accurate to say she turned two just last month. Sometimes I feel disoriented with how fast time goes — my head is still two weeks ago and my body, by default, is here and now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AliensInTheApple.com</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/30/aliensintheapple-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/30/aliensintheapple-com/</guid>
      <description>It’s kinda subtle, but our blog just moved from aliensintheapple.wordpress.com to our own domain name, aliensintheapple.com. All the old links and addresses will still work (and redirect here), so you don’t need to update anything. Enjoy our dot-com!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving yumminess</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/28/thanksgiving-yumminess/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/28/thanksgiving-yumminess/</guid>
      <description>Well, Thanksgiving came and went, and we had a lovely day. It was great to have a bonus day where Ben had the day off, and we enjoyed getting to know a friend from church a bit better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The beauty of gratitude</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/23/the-beauty-of-gratitude/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/23/the-beauty-of-gratitude/</guid>
      <description>What a great gift to have a whole feast day dedicated to giving thanks! I’m relishing the opportunity to celebrate Thanksgiving while we’re here in the States. It might even be a tradition we take home to New Zealand with us!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Christianity sexist?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/19/is-christianity-sexist/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/19/is-christianity-sexist/</guid>
      <description>Perhaps the most-prayed Christian prayer is the Lord’s Prayer: “Our Father who art in heaven…” But why Father and not person or parent? Is Christianity sexist?
Our home church denomination recently held a national Synod meeting, and one of the things they discussed was the updated 2011 translation of the NIV Bible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More good times</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/17/more-good-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/17/more-good-times/</guid>
      <description>Our last overnight stop on our roadtrip with my parents was at Mr &amp;amp; Mrs Brauning’s place. Mr Brauning is a pastor who came and filled our pulpit for a few months while our home congregation was vacant and the Braunings are loved by many back home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If looks could kill…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/14/if-looks-could-kill/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/14/if-looks-could-kill/</guid>
      <description>then this cheeky face kills me with laughter almost every time I see it.
Figuratively, of course.
She was putting on her pretend grouchy face, only to dissolve into giggles herself!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stop 3 on the trip</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/14/stop-3-on-the-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/14/stop-3-on-the-trip/</guid>
      <description>Just a little note: I’m not blogging real-time. I think I might have blogged about something on the same day it happened about twice in the whole time I’ve had this blog. I just don’t have the luxury of lots of time to be able to do that!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magnificent Niagara Falls</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/10/magnificent-niagara-falls/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/10/magnificent-niagara-falls/</guid>
      <description>After our 3 nights in the Adirondack mountains, we drove to Niagara Falls. The scenery on the way was beautiful!
Crossing the border into Canada.
We arrived on a cold, windy, overcast afternoon, but didn’t know whether the weather would clear up over the weekend, so decided to brave it and go look at the falls regardless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some nature shots from the Adirondacks</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/07/some-nature-shots-from-the-adirondacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/07/some-nature-shots-from-the-adirondacks/</guid>
      <description>During our time in the Adirondacks it rained most of the time, except for our first afternoon there. There were some breaks in the rain, though, and I took my chances to go outside and take some ‘nature shots’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October, a wonderful month with family</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/03/october-a-wonderful-month-with-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/03/october-a-wonderful-month-with-family/</guid>
      <description>For most of the month of October we had my parents visiting with us, and we had a very good time together.
The highlight of their time here was probably our road trip that we took to the Adirondack mountains, Niagara Falls, Toronto and Pennsylvania to visit our friends the Tysons and the Braunings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A hairy theme at the Met</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/31/a-hairy-theme-at-the-met/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/31/a-hairy-theme-at-the-met/</guid>
      <description>Every time I go to the Metropolitan Museum of Art I see something I haven’t seen before, and I certainly go back to old favourites. Recently I took some photos with a hairy theme. Some of them are so ridiculous, you’d have to be an old stodge not to even get a slight smile at the lips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some cool photos of the Guggenheim</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/27/some-cool-photos-of-the-guggenheim/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/27/some-cool-photos-of-the-guggenheim/</guid>
      <description>I don’t really care for modern art much, so I’ve never felt a deep desire to go look at what’s inside the Guggenheim museum (I can get my fill at the Met by glimpsing at the modern art section when I walk past there to get to the European sculptures).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Night</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/24/night/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/24/night/</guid>
      <description>“Why are you downcast, O my soul? Why so disturbed within me?” Ps 43:5
That’s what this sculpture by Aristide Maillol brought to mind when I saw it at the Metropolitan Museum of Art.
The artist did an amazing job — it was as if everything about her just felt so sad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where there’s a will, there’s a way</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/20/where-theres-a-will-theres-a-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/20/where-theres-a-will-theres-a-way/</guid>
      <description>As shown by this very stubborn plant determined to grow on a church steeple in Baltimore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t mess with this guy</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/17/dont-mess-with-this-guy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/17/dont-mess-with-this-guy/</guid>
      <description>I took his photo one day while walking the Brooklyn Bridge. I wonder if he’s ticked off at the cyclists that come hooning down at breakneck speeds, or if he’s just having a bad day?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accidental coolness</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/13/accidental-coolness/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/13/accidental-coolness/</guid>
      <description>When I was driving through Philly with Margaret, I was just happily snapping pictures of stuff out of the car while we were driving. I happened to take this picture of a city centre sculpture and when I went through the photos afterwards I saw how perfectly (total fluke) the moon was aligned with this thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guess who’s visiting us?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/10/guess-whos-visiting-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/10/guess-whos-visiting-us/</guid>
      <description>My parents! Right now I’m at home waiting for Ben to bring my parents home from the airport. We’re very excited to have them visit! We’re looking forward to taking a road trip with them while they’re here up to the Adirondacks, Niagara Falls and Pennsylvania.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The night I met Daniel</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/10/the-night-i-met-daniel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/10/the-night-i-met-daniel/</guid>
      <description>I don’t usually share particularly personal experiences here on the blog, but this is a bit of an exception as I thought some of you might find it strangely encouraging too.
In the last few weeks, I have had a profound sense of the weight and enormity of my sin and selfishness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road trip report, Days 5 and 6</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/06/road-trip-report-days-5-and-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/06/road-trip-report-days-5-and-6/</guid>
      <description>We left Washington D.C. on a Friday afternoon and drove up to Baltimore. I’m not sure if we saw the wrong side of Baltimore or what, but neither of us were particularly impressed. I guess that wasn’t helped by a fire drill going on at the Art Museum as soon as we walked in, and nobody knowing what was going on, including the staff, which meant we just walked straight back out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Baltimore hotel window view</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/04/a-baltimore-hotel-window-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/04/a-baltimore-hotel-window-view/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been just a little bit busy lately, preparing for another roadtrip (yay!), this time with my parents (double yay!) who should have arrived in San Francisco by now. I hope. I realised I never gave my parents my contact details here in the States before they left.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road trip report, Day 4</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/30/road-trip-report-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/30/road-trip-report-day-4/</guid>
      <description>So you’re all dying to hear how we became chummy with the President, right? Well, it happened like this: we were walking outside the fence of his big fancy house, admiring the well kept garden and lawns, all lonesome and deserted when suddenly he jumped out of the bushes and shouted “BOO!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road trip report, Day 3</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/26/road-trip-report-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/26/road-trip-report-day-3/</guid>
      <description>Just a little note: I’ve switched to uploading smaller photos on here, to make things faster for me while editing blog posts, and hopefully also for you as subscribers having to download the posts. As far as I can tell the quality is still pretty good, but let me know what you think.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road trip report, Day 1 and 2</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/24/road-trip-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/24/road-trip-report/</guid>
      <description>So like I said, Margaret took me and the girls on a week-long road trip (thanks, Gary!) and boy did we have fun! There was a good amount of banter and hilarity and also some really good conversations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What a great 2 weeks it has been!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/20/what-a-great-2-weeks-it-has-been/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/20/what-a-great-2-weeks-it-has-been/</guid>
      <description>As I mentioned a while back, I was anticipating a visit from a good old friend from Christchurch, Margaret Haverland. Today she is getting ready to leave, after almost 2 weeks here. What a blast it has been!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Person’s Prayer</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/17/the-persons-prayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/17/the-persons-prayer/</guid>
      <description>Our Caregiver in the spiritual realm,
Transparent be your name.
Your democracy be voted in,
Your social policy be implemented,
In reality as it is in the spiritual realm.
Give us every day our organic tofu,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travelling fruit</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/12/travelling-fruit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/12/travelling-fruit/</guid>
      <description>This little guy has come a long way!
And he tasted pretty good too. A taste of home, you could say. :-)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ten years on</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/11/ten-years-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/11/ten-years-on/</guid>
      <description>This week, and especially today, New Yorkers remember the day on which Muslim terrorists hijacked planes and flew into the World Trade Center towers, killing almost 3000 civilians. I’m not going to delve into the politics and debates surrounding it, but rather give you my perspective on what it’s like living here at a time like this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green and glorious</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/09/green-and-glorious/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/09/green-and-glorious/</guid>
      <description>Hooray for pesto! What a beautiful thing pesto is. Easy to make, and it gives a wonderful flavour to sandwiches, pastas, risotto, pizza, baked potatoes, salads, chocolate cake, wait, what? Just trust me, it’s good stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A pre-engagement visit</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/07/a-pre-engagement-visit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/07/a-pre-engagement-visit/</guid>
      <description>Now that you all know that Lillian and Jeremy are engaged, we can all happily say “Hooray!”. Lillian was here for a very short visit (just under 2 weeks) and flew into JFK, so we got the privilege of hosting the two of them for a few nights before they went off to Philadelphia to go get engaged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your office is where?!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/05/your-office-is-where/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/05/your-office-is-where/</guid>
      <description>I often see this sign on the wall of a house on my walk to the hospital (and I’ve done that walk a few times recently) and it cracks me up every single time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking kids on a photo shoot can be interesting</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/03/taking-kids-on-a-photo-shoot-can-be-interesting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/03/taking-kids-on-a-photo-shoot-can-be-interesting/</guid>
      <description>And also pretty fun.
Perhaps “photo shoot” is too formal a title for what we did with Jeremy and Lillian, but I still tried to get a heap of photos while at the same time trying to keep an eye on two speedy escape artists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now for the black and white engagement pics</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/01/now-for-the-black-and-white-engagement-pics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/01/now-for-the-black-and-white-engagement-pics/</guid>
      <description>As I said earlier, my previous post kept freezing up because I had too many photos in there, so I instead made the first post the colour post and this one the black&amp;amp;white post. I personally often prefer black and white, so this was fun for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The last one bites the dust</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/01/the-last-one-bites-the-dust/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/01/the-last-one-bites-the-dust/</guid>
      <description>But that makes it sound like it’s a bad thing when it is indeed a very happy thing — the last of 8 children getting married. Yes, that’s right, Ben’s little sister, Lillian, is engaged to be married to a certain Mr Jeremy Fisher, uh, I mean Mr Jeremy L Eshelman!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luth3r hacks iChurch, makes Bible open source</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/30/luth3r-hacks-ichurch-makes-bible-open-source/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/30/luth3r-hacks-ichurch-makes-bible-open-source/</guid>
      <description>GENEVA TRIBUNE, August 1517.
New things are afoot in the world of Scripture freedom. Two days ago a hacker, who goes under the pseudonym Mart1n Luth3r, released a set of 95 bullet points outlining how to hack iChurch’s core systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We survived Irene</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/28/we-survived-irene/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/28/we-survived-irene/</guid>
      <description>We’re posting this from a rescue boat (with free wireless internet) that lifted us from the roof of our flooded apartment early this morning. We’re sipping complimentary cocktails as we traverse the streets by boat, witnessing how New York has turned into a lake full of broken branches and leaves, a veritable Venice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Irene</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/27/hurricane-irene/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/27/hurricane-irene/</guid>
      <description>Most of you are probably aware that Hurricane Irene is currently moving up the East Coast of the States, and will most likely pass through, or very close to New York City. For those of you who are interested, we are not in an area likely to flood, and we don’t foresee needing to evacuate at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A little holiday</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/21/a-little-holiday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/21/a-little-holiday/</guid>
      <description>Hey everyone, I’m going on a little computer holiday for the next week or so, so you won’t be getting blog posts, and I most likely won’t be replying to emails. If you need to contact me, I’ll probably be keeping skype on so you can contact me that way, or email Ben, or phone me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby loves babies</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/21/baby-loves-babies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/21/baby-loves-babies/</guid>
      <description>Ever since Esther has been able to cuddle dolls, she has been a little ‘mother’ to her dolls (when she isn’t destroying them by writing all over them!). It’s rather cute to see her personality come out in this way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perspective</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/19/perspective/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/19/perspective/</guid>
      <description>I like how the composition of this photo turned out: pretty clover in focus and a couple in the background. Some of the clover leaves look like love hearts… It’s kind of sweet. :-)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three peas in  a pod</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/17/three-peas-in-a-pod/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/17/three-peas-in-a-pod/</guid>
      <description>We recently had our friends Rick and Susanna here for dinner while their two oldest kids were visiting grandparents and when bathtime rolled around we stuck our 3 little blondies in the bath. I just had to share the cuteness!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When the summer gives you heat…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/10/when-the-summer-gives-you-heat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/10/when-the-summer-gives-you-heat/</guid>
      <description>eat popsicles!
It’s so delicious you have to let your arm and chin taste some too.
It hurts when you bite cold stuff with your teeth!
Look, Mum, a plane! (Depending on the wind direction, we get them coming over every 2 minutes or so to land at JFK.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turning 30</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/08/turning-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/08/turning-30/</guid>
      <description>Last Thursday I (Ben) turned 30, and an otherwise ordinary workday was turned into Something Special by my lovely wife. She’d been being secretive about something for a few weeks, so I guessed something was going to happen, but I had no idea what.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A quiet Saturday morning</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/06/a-quiet-saturday-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/06/a-quiet-saturday-morning/</guid>
      <description>It’s quiet because I’m home alone, which is a rare event indeed! Ben took the girls to Prospect Park this morning and I have some time to myself here at home. Guess what I’ve chosen to spend my time doing?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy hammocking</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/01/happy-hammocking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/01/happy-hammocking/</guid>
      <description>Hammocking is a verb, didn’t you know? It does not involve mocking ham. Ham is too good to mock.
Enjoying some mum-and-daughter time in the hammock a while back when we were at Jeremy’s place in Philadelphia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A matter of the heart</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/29/a-matter-of-the-heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/29/a-matter-of-the-heart/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been thinking about all sorts of matters relating to the heart — it’s interesting that we describe both things emotional and spiritual with the metaphor of the heart. “His heart is not in the right place”, “she’s lost heart”, “guard your heart”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How high do your kids rank?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/27/how-high-do-your-kids-rank/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/27/how-high-do-your-kids-rank/</guid>
      <description>Another excellent article from Rachel Jankovic. A good look at how society views children, where your children rank in your priorities, and the calling of motherhood. I encourage you to go read it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another beautiful zinnia</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/25/another-beautiful-zinnia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/25/another-beautiful-zinnia/</guid>
      <description>It boggles my mind that God would put such intricate beauty into a simple flower… layer upon layer, curly baby petals… in a pot I too often forget to water.
But then again, it really shouldn’t surprise me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Okay, so it’s just a teensy bit hot here</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/23/okay-so-its-just-a-teensy-bit-hot-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/23/okay-so-its-just-a-teensy-bit-hot-here/</guid>
      <description>You’ve probably heard about the heat wave that has hit us here in the States. It’s a steaming sauna — free! We seem to be spending time here when all the records strike. Record snow, record heat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I stopped reading a classic</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/22/why-i-stopped-reading-a-classic/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/22/why-i-stopped-reading-a-classic/</guid>
      <description>The Brothers Karamazov by Fyodor Dostoyevsky is a classic, or so I’ve heard. It’s one of those books so great and so worth reading that no one you talk to has actually read it.
A 700-page novel is something of a commitment, but I approached this one with an open mind and a daily subway commute.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lorraine, the not-so Divine</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/20/lorraine-the-not-so-divine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/20/lorraine-the-not-so-divine/</guid>
      <description>Saw this old building on our way to Jeremy’s place in Philadelphia, and couldn’t help noticing the irony.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Jeremy eats a mushroom</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/18/how-jeremy-eats-a-mushroom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/18/how-jeremy-eats-a-mushroom/</guid>
      <description>When we were visiting Jeremy in Philly, I made some grilled mushrooms on the barbecue with fresh parmesan, salt, pepper, butter and fresh mozzarella cheese, garnished with a fresh basil leaf. Are your mouths watering yet?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to Mr. J</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/15/visit-to-mr-j/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/15/visit-to-mr-j/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weekends ago, we visited our good friend, Jeremy, in Philadelphia.
What a blast — we did some sight-seeing, but also my favourite pastime: having good discussions over good food.
There was of course also an appropriate amount of teasing which Jeremy thrived upon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Childlike trust</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/13/childlike-trust/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/13/childlike-trust/</guid>
      <description>Trust is knowing that we are small and God is big and that He will not let us go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blueberry pancakes worth eating</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/11/blueberry-pancakes-worth-eating/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/11/blueberry-pancakes-worth-eating/</guid>
      <description>Blueberries are in season now here in the States and they’re plentiful and cheap. They’re also ridiculously good for you, but that’s really beside the point — what matters is that they taste so good! It’s hard to believe that they can taste better in any way other than plain from the punnet, but these pancakes bring out the blueberry flavour very well and they melt in your mouth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 4th of July!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/08/the-4th-of-july-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/08/the-4th-of-july-2/</guid>
      <description>This year the 4th of July fell on a Monday so we were very happy that Ben got the day off. We spent a relaxing morning at home and in the afternoon went to Manhattan to view the Macy’s 4th of July fireworks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>White Collar in Clinton Hill!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/07/white-collar-in-clinton-hill/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/07/white-collar-in-clinton-hill/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday and today we’ve had film crews on our street and surrounding neighborhood shooting for the TV series WhiteCollar. It’s been really cool to see a little glimpse of what goes into a production like this — SO many trucks and people doing all sorts of things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A garden grows in Brooklyn</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/06/a-garden-grows-in-brooklyn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/06/a-garden-grows-in-brooklyn/</guid>
      <description>We are among the few privileged New Yorkers who have our own private backyard. Private as in access (no one else uses our backyard), not private in the sense that nobody can see us, because we certainly have plenty of window eyes all around!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to Connecticut</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/04/visit-to-connecticut/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/04/visit-to-connecticut/</guid>
      <description>A few weekends ago we drove up to Connecticut to visit fellow Kiwis, Ron and Judy Snoek and their son Troy. They very kindly hosted us for a night with some good ol’ home-like hospitality. It was so nice to spend time with them and get to know them a bit better (I (Franci) hadn’t even met them before this!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo fun</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/02/photo-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/02/photo-fun/</guid>
      <description>The outside of our house at the back is painted in a vivid blue. I’ve planted some zinnias in pots, and the colour contrast is great. I had some fun taking photos of a couple of flowers the other day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shenanigans with Sharon</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/01/shenanigans-with-sharon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/01/shenanigans-with-sharon/</guid>
      <description>Ben’s cousin Sharon visited us over Memorial Weekend, and we had a lot of fun packing in as much sight-seeing as was practical! Here is some photographic evidence.
We walked the Brooklyn Bridge,
sat on cool seats on the way to the Ferry terminal,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful encouragement for the mothers among us</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/29/beautiful-encouragement-for-the-mothers-among-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/29/beautiful-encouragement-for-the-mothers-among-us/</guid>
      <description>One of my favourite authors and bloggers (I’ve raved about her before) was invited by Desiring God ministries to write an article for them. I found it very encouraging and helpful, and I hope all the mothers who visit this blog will read this article — you will not be sorry!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glimpses into the last couple of weeks</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/27/glimpses-into-the-last-couple-of-weeks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/27/glimpses-into-the-last-couple-of-weeks/</guid>
      <description>I don’t know why the weeks go by so fast. I have a bunch of photos to share with you from when Ben’s cousin Sharon visited us a month ago, our trip to Connecticut 2 weeks ago and our trip to visit Jeremy in Philadelphia last weekend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proof that we are Americanizing</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/20/proof-that-we-are-americanizing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/20/proof-that-we-are-americanizing/</guid>
      <description>I have Uncrustables in my freezer. Yes, ma’am, I tell no lie. Uncrustables in your freezer means that you have attained to the great feat of crossing over to The Other Side. For any of you ignorant folk who do not know about the beauty of Uncrustables, let me introduce you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer is here!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/16/summer-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/16/summer-is-here/</guid>
      <description>And we’ve well and truly been out and about enjoying it. We’ve only had two very hot days and for the rest of the time it has been pretty much perfect weather (25 - 30 C).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fish Parcels</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/11/fish-parcels/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/11/fish-parcels/</guid>
      <description>I have a quick and easy recipe to share with you. We’re not big fans of fish around here. Yes, I know we should be, it’s healthy and all that… omega 3’s and a bunch of other healthy bits and bobs, but fish just doesn’t really feature on our favourites list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Ground Zero looks like these days</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/07/what-ground-zero-looks-like-these-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/07/what-ground-zero-looks-like-these-days/</guid>
      <description>I don’t think there would be anyone who doesn’t remember the shock they felt at the news of the September 11 attacks. Since then, almost ten years have passed, and much has changed. Ground Zero is now a bustling construction site instead of a heap of rubble.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did I tell you that Esther is now walking?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/03/did-i-tell-you-that-esther-is-now-walking/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/03/did-i-tell-you-that-esther-is-now-walking/</guid>
      <description>Well, she certainly is. And she’s fast too. She’s loving the new independence and so am I. Playgrounds are much more fun, despite the scratched knees she inevitably gets!
Walking down Fulton Street. That big tower in the background under construction is the new One World Trade Center.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheeky grin</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/31/cheeky-grin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/31/cheeky-grin/</guid>
      <description>This girly has some awesome facial expressions. This is one of them. :-)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who sped up time?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/28/who-sped-up-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/28/who-sped-up-time/</guid>
      <description>How is it possible that we have been in New York City for a year already? Yes, everyone, it’s been a YEAR! When we arrived a year ago, I must admit that I viewed our ‘adventure’ with some trepidation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When you don’t have a sandwich press…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/26/when-you-dont-have-a-sandwich-press/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/26/when-you-dont-have-a-sandwich-press/</guid>
      <description>… make your own with whatever you have on hand!
See, it works pretty well!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful Brooklyn Botanic Garden</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/21/beautiful-brooklyn-botanic-garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/21/beautiful-brooklyn-botanic-garden/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weeks ago, we went to the Brooklyn Botanic Garden with our friends Julie and Abby Murphy and Damaris and her 2 cute kids, Elijah and Sophia.
The gardens were amazingly beautiful and dressed in their Spring finest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marica the soccer player</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/19/marica-the-soccer-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/19/marica-the-soccer-player/</guid>
      <description>Friends of ours recently invited Marica to join a little informal ‘soccer’ team that will practice just until the start of the summer. Marica has loved her Saturday morning soccer practices and all the games the coach lets them play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Long-distance running inside our apartment</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/16/long-distance-running-inside-our-apartment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/16/long-distance-running-inside-our-apartment/</guid>
      <description>The other day Marica decided to start running laps between our bed and the couch in the lounge, a distance of about six or seven metres. After a few laps she started counting, “1, 2, 3, 4 …” Soon I took over the counting, “14, 15, 16, see if you can get up to 20 …”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brooklyn Bridge!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/14/brooklyn-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/14/brooklyn-bridge/</guid>
      <description>When Ben’s dad was here back in April we got a fair bit of sight-seeing done, which even included some things I hadn’t seen or done before, which was pretty exciting. One of those things was walking the Brooklyn Bridge, which is just one of those things you have to do in New York City.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Up to no good</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/12/up-to-no-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/12/up-to-no-good/</guid>
      <description>Esther’s fine motor skills are very well developed, at least when it comes to opening things. Somehow she managed to open the coffee packet the other day and spill grounds all over the floor. But then you see that expression and how can’t you laugh?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About servants and serving</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/07/about-servants/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/07/about-servants/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been thinking about my job (as a mother) a fair bit recently. After Monday’s blog post, I felt that I might have given the wrong impression of what life around here looks like. I have a policy (with myself) not to complain or whine on this blog — not about big city life and not about my family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where to find me</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/07/where-to-find-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/07/where-to-find-me/</guid>
      <description>… in a subway station.
Or my initials, at least. :-)
The real place you’ll find me in a subway station is as far away from the tracks as possible, holding onto my kids pretty well!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preschool poetry</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/05/preschool-poetry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/05/preschool-poetry/</guid>
      <description>Last Friday, Marica’s preschool put on a poetry recital that parents were invited to. The kids had all worked hard at memorising the poems — they recited 3 poems and then sung Mary had a little lamb, and they did really well!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some other New York sights (and eats) with Hannah and Eva</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/05/some-other-new-york-sights-and-eats-with-hannah-and-eva/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/05/some-other-new-york-sights-and-eats-with-hannah-and-eva/</guid>
      <description>As you can tell, I’m waaay behind on sight-seeing posts! When Hannah and Eva were here way back in March, we did quite a few fun things I haven’t shared here yet, so here’s a photo post of some of the things we did and ate!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beauty is in the eye of the beholder</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/02/beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/02/beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder/</guid>
      <description>Marica said I looked beautiful after she was finished making me beautiful. Ben came home and called me hideous. I’ll let you decide for yourself!
It was cold and rainy a fair bit back in March, so one day when Marica asked if she could make me pretty, I consented.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easter</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/29/easter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/29/easter/</guid>
      <description>Easter this year was probably the most different for us as a family than what we’ve had before. Ben didn’t get Good Friday off, so it was really strange not to be able to go to church together as a family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musings on New York, the weather, and teeth.</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/26/musings-on-new-york-the-weather-and-teeth/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/26/musings-on-new-york-the-weather-and-teeth/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been sharing a lot of photos and telling you about stuff we’ve seen and experienced lately (and there’s a lot more to come!), but I thought I’d just give you a little update on how we’re all doing, as well as some related thoughts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The importance of a decimal point</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/21/the-importance-of-a-decimal-point/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/21/the-importance-of-a-decimal-point/</guid>
      <description>You might not think it, but it can make quite a big difference!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating Easter</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/18/celebrating-easter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/18/celebrating-easter/</guid>
      <description>Let me just start by saying that I loooove living in the northern hemisphere! The seasons and church calendar finally make sense! Christmas with snow, Easter with blossoms, summer holiday that doesn’t mix with Christmas. Celebrating Christmas here was great in that sense, and Easter is looking promising too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Up close and personal with Lady Liberty</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/16/up-close-and-personal-with-lady-liberty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/16/up-close-and-personal-with-lady-liberty/</guid>
      <description>The New Colossus By Emma Lazarus, 1883
Not like the brazen giant of Greek fame,
With conquering limbs astride from land to land;
Here at our sea-washed, sunset gates shall stand
A mighty woman with a torch, whose flame</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How not to praise your kids</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/14/how-not-to-praise-your-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/14/how-not-to-praise-your-kids/</guid>
      <description>I just finished reading an online article by New York Magazine, How not to talk to your kids. It talked about a lot of research that has been done over the last few years about the effects of praise on children’s performance — how not to praise your kids’ intelligence, but their efforts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t be late for class!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/13/dont-be-late-for-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/13/dont-be-late-for-class/</guid>
      <description>Or else…
We saw this on the subway to church the other day and I couldn’t help it — I just had to take a picture! Sometimes graffiti is hilarious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yummy muesli</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/07/yummy-muesli/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/07/yummy-muesli/</guid>
      <description>Guess what I’m making today? Muesli! If you’ve never tried your hand at making your own, may I gently prod you in that direction? You will be done with it and with cleaning your kitchen within half an hour, and you’ll be thanking yourself for doing it every breakfast for the next few weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A too-short visit to The Met</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/06/a-too-short-visit-to-the-met/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/06/a-too-short-visit-to-the-met/</guid>
      <description>When Hannah and Eva were here, we went to the Met the same day we went to the Cloisters. The Met really deserves a day or two to itself, and I definitely plan to go back — the two or so hours we had there were only enough to see a few musical instruments and about 3/4 of the European Painters section.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Would you?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/05/would-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/05/would-you/</guid>
      <description>Would you feel confident using a dry cleaner with a name like this? It cracks me up every time I see it!
I took the photo at night, so excuse the poor lighting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An uncultured laugh (specially for April Fool’s day)</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/01/an-uncultured-laugh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/01/an-uncultured-laugh/</guid>
      <description>When I went to The Cloisters with Hannah and Eva, there were a few sculptures/carvings that I took pictures of purely to post on here with funny comments, because they sure made us crack up. My apologies go to the artists who did not create their masterpieces for us to laugh at, and to those of you who find Roman Catholic artefacts more meaningful than un-cultured moi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting The Cloisters</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/30/revisiting-the-cloisters/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/30/revisiting-the-cloisters/</guid>
      <description>When Ben’s cousins, Hannah and Eva, were here visiting with us, the three of us took a trip up into Manhattan to see The Cloisters and The Met (The Met will be in another post!).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheesecake and getting old</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/28/cheesecake-and-getting-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/28/cheesecake-and-getting-old/</guid>
      <description>Last Sunday (a week and a half ago, almost), I got another year older. It’s funny how birthday excitement has the tendency to wane as you get older! Though perhaps that’s not a good way for me to look at it — it would be better to think about being blessed with another year instead of having a hum-ho attitude of ‘oh, just another year’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Barbie is a big deal</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/24/why-barbie-is-a-big-deal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/24/why-barbie-is-a-big-deal/</guid>
      <description>Today’s post goes out on a limb a bit. It’s probably going to be controversial and many of you won’t agree with me, but these are some thoughts that have been swirling around in my mind for many months, and that some of you might find beneficial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring is knocking on Winter’s door!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/22/spring-is-knocking-on-winters-door/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/22/spring-is-knocking-on-winters-door/</guid>
      <description>The crocuses are out! And some mini irises too. I hope to see some daffodils soon!
We spotted these cuties in Central Park last Saturday.
Aren’t these just so gorgeous? These flowers we saw in Fort Tryon Park near The Cloisters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marica’s self-photography</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/16/maricas-self-photography/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/16/maricas-self-photography/</guid>
      <description>Just a little something that I hope you find as funny as I did!
A post explaining the make-up on the eyes is coming soon…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Salmon and Couscous Salad</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/14/spring-salmon-and-couscous-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/14/spring-salmon-and-couscous-salad/</guid>
      <description>I know that I’ve had a lot of recipes on here recently. Maybe that can partly be attributed to the weather — the more time we have inside, the more time I have to do fun stuff in the kitchen, plus it’s not so insanely hot when the oven goes on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Should churches care about branding?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/11/should-churches-care-about-branding/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/11/should-churches-care-about-branding/</guid>
      <description>Centuries ago (in internet time) graphic designer David Airey wrote a blog post asking folks whether they’d seen any good church logos. My brother Bryan responded with a thought-provoking comment asking whether churches should even be concerned about “branding”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Franci the judge</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/10/franci-the-judge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/10/franci-the-judge/</guid>
      <description>Now that’s a catchy title if I ever saw one! :-)
This past Saturday I took the train up to a little town called Irvington on the bank of the Hudson river where there was a huge homeschoolers debating tournament going on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scaling down</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/07/scaling-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/07/scaling-down/</guid>
      <description>Some of you have probably seen this coming, but this is just a little announcement to say that I’m going to scale back a bit on blogging. In fact, I’m scaling down whatever time I’m spending on the computer in general.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuscan Pork with beans</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/04/tuscan-pork-with-beans/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/04/tuscan-pork-with-beans/</guid>
      <description>Can I just draw your attention to something rather delicious?
Slow-cooked Tuscan Pork is the thing! I got the recipe on Femina, so you’d better hop over there if you want it. Let me just tell you that this is worth making.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh yes, I have a blog.</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/02/oh-yes-i-have-a-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/02/oh-yes-i-have-a-blog/</guid>
      <description>That’s how it feels to me sometimes when I realise that all my scheduled posts have run out, and my drafts folder is looking a bit emaciated. We run this blog mainly to stay in contact with family and friends back home in New Zealand to share what we’ve been up to, what we’re thinking about and stuff we like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cute kids’ photos</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/28/cute-kids-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/28/cute-kids-photos/</guid>
      <description>While Ben and I were having a blast in the Caribbean, our kids were having a blast at the Murphys’ place. Julie was kind enough to send me some pictures, so I’ll share them here for you to enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just do the next thing</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/24/just-do-the-next-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/24/just-do-the-next-thing/</guid>
      <description>There are times in life when we get overwhelmed. Sometimes we have too much work to do, sometimes we’re ill, sometimes we’re just dog tired, sometimes earthquakes strike. The world keeps spinning, life carries on and we have to somehow deal with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another big earthquake in Christchurch</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/22/another-big-earthquake-in-christchurch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/22/another-big-earthquake-in-christchurch/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday a 6.3 magnitude earthquake struck our hometown of Christchurch. You might recall that Christchurch was hit by a 7.1 in September. The city has since felt thousands of aftershocks, of which yesterday’s 6.3 was one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The beauty of bread</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/21/the-beauty-of-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/21/the-beauty-of-bread/</guid>
      <description>Here in the States, I’ve taken to baking most of our bread from scratch by hand, because I can’t stand the taste of the bread here. Specialty breads here taste great, but I do still have a grocery budget to stick to!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is it vague, or is it lazy?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/18/is-it-vague-or-is-it-lazy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/18/is-it-vague-or-is-it-lazy/</guid>
      <description>This article is best read out loud for maximum effect.
I like read this interesting article the other day, and, you know, I thought it was pretty interesting, so I thought I’d like link to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marica is 4!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/16/marica-is-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/16/marica-is-4/</guid>
      <description>On Saturday, Marica turned 4 years old. I find that hard to believe that it’s already been 4 years since she was born. And at the same time it feels as if she’s been my big girl forever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The One True BDFL</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/14/the-one-true-bdfl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/14/the-one-true-bdfl/</guid>
      <description>Note: This blog is mostly read by family and friends, but I wrote this more for my fellow programmers. Knowing me, it’ll be taken the wrong way by both groups of people. :-) By the way, see the first comment for a book give-away!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A joyful glimpse</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/11/a-joyful-glimpse/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/11/a-joyful-glimpse/</guid>
      <description>I just wanted to share a little moment in our life here, because it’s moments like these that make me so happy and thankful for the gift of being able to be a mother at home with my kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Punta Cana!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/11/punta-cana/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/11/punta-cana/</guid>
      <description>Ben and I have always dreamed of going on a romantic tropical island holiday. This has partly been inspired by the total un-tropical-ness of our honeymoon destination (Stewart Island! I don’t know why we ever thought it would be tropical.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back to reality</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/09/back-to-reality/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/09/back-to-reality/</guid>
      <description>This past weekend Ben and I flew off into the Tropical sunset and had a total blast. We came back on Monday night and since then we’ve been right back into things here. I wasn’t organised enough to have self-publishing posts past Monday’s post on here, and things have been busy since we’ve been back, so you’ll all have to wait a little while till Friday to hear all about our trip and see a whole bunch of photos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loving the Little Years</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/07/loving-the-little-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/07/loving-the-little-years/</guid>
      <description>I have recently been reading through Loving the Little Years by Rachel Jankovic. It is GOOD. Every single chapter encourages me and exhorts me and redirects my focus off myself and onto Christ. Off what other people think and onto Christ.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who left the toilet open this time?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/04/who-left-the-toilet-open-this-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/04/who-left-the-toilet-open-this-time/</guid>
      <description>I recently discovered Esther in the act of playing with her favourite toy again. She was in her element, and had even put a washcloth and some bath toys in there too. She even washed herself with the washcloth, as you can see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting creative with snow</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/02/getting-creative-with-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/02/getting-creative-with-snow/</guid>
      <description>We’ve had a lot of snow here this winter, and today we’ve got snow and ice rain again! Well, life carries on about as normally as it can and we try to get out when we can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowsational</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/31/snowsational/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/31/snowsational/</guid>
      <description>Snow is beautiful. And fun. It does get messy, and it keeps you indoors more than you’d like, but those are trifles compared to the six foot high piles of white-or-grey frozen stuff all over the streets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sally Henny Penny</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/28/sally-henny-penny/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/28/sally-henny-penny/</guid>
      <description>Those of you familiar with Beatrix Potter’s stories would appreciate this picture of our very own Sally Henny Penny wearing her yellow stockings. Very soon she will be going barefoot barefoot barefoot!
And no, we hadn’t brushed her hair yet!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cherry Delight on the menu tonight</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/26/cherry-delight-on-the-menu-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/26/cherry-delight-on-the-menu-tonight/</guid>
      <description>Cherry Delight was introduced to us by Lillian, who made it for one of our Advent dinner desserts. She, in turn, got it from her Grandma Tschetter. It is very delicious, and therefore I feel compelled to share the goodness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Have we mentioned it’s been cold?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/24/have-we-mentioned-its-been-cold/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/24/have-we-mentioned-its-been-cold/</guid>
      <description>Our first blizzard in New York was a very exciting event. Everything was beautiful and white and we were on holiday. The second one was not so exciting, apart from the fact that it kept Lillian with us for a day longer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A visit to Wonderland</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/21/a-visit-to-wonderland/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/21/a-visit-to-wonderland/</guid>
      <description>Last Friday, a few friends from church met up at Alice’s Tea Cup with their daughters for a fun, girly time of drinking tea, eating good food and some good conversation.
Alice’s Tea Cup is definitely a girly tea room, decorated in pretty colours with cool chandeliers and fairy wings on the walls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Having a bad day parenting? Sue McDonald’s!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/19/having-a-bad-day-parenting-sue-mcdonalds/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/19/having-a-bad-day-parenting-sue-mcdonalds/</guid>
      <description>Warning: This article may contain traces of sarcasm.
Maybe she was just having a bad day as a parent. Or who knows, maybe she is getting paid by an advocacy group. But one Mizz Parham from California seems to have a thing against Happy Meals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Clutter</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/17/time-clutter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/17/time-clutter/</guid>
      <description>I often feel slightly frustrated at the seeming lack of time I have for doing things like reading, crafting or doing special fun things with the kids. Part of my lack of time is certainly due to the demands of daily life as a wife and a stay-at-home mother of two busy little people, but some of it is most certainly due to me wasting time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glitches do happen</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/15/glitches-do-happen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/15/glitches-do-happen/</guid>
      <description>For some reason our previous post about the happy occurrence of our 6th wedding anniversary had a few glitches — not the whole post I had done showed up, missing a kind of special part, and for some inexplicable reason comments were turned off (I’ve fixed that now).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Six blessed and beautiful years</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/15/six-blessed-and-beautiful-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/15/six-blessed-and-beautiful-years/</guid>
      <description>Today, 6 years ago, I married my best friend.
Life with Ben has been like a beautiful dance, a dance he leads to help us move forward as one. There has been the odd difficult patch because we are living life in a fallen world, after all, but on the whole it has been six years that God has packed with blessing upon blessing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Chocolate Monkster</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/13/the-chocolate-monkster/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/13/the-chocolate-monkster/</guid>
      <description>Since turning one, Esther has been introduced to the wonders of chocolate. She loves that stuff with a passion!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The penny queen</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/11/the-penny-queen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/11/the-penny-queen/</guid>
      <description>Marica must have either Dutch or Jewish blood in her. She’s always scouting to find coins on the ground, and the number she has picked up is astounding. Here’s one day’s laundromat loot: a quarter and a penny.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food is so beautiful</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/07/food-is-so-beautiful-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/07/food-is-so-beautiful-2/</guid>
      <description>In preparing our Christmas dessert I twice had to stop and take pictures because the food was so beautiful.
First up, just admire the beauty of butter, sugar and eggs creamed together:
And when you cook up a syrup of sugar, butter and water, you get pretty swirls!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our first snowman</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/05/our-first-snowman/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/05/our-first-snowman/</guid>
      <description>It got seriously warm today (almost 10 degrees C), so we went into our snow-covered backyard and colonized it, turning the beautiful fresh snow into a snowman.
Our back “yard” before we started:
Laying the foundation (Marica supervising):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sight-seeing with Lillian</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/03/sight-seeing-with-lillian/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/03/sight-seeing-with-lillian/</guid>
      <description>In the few weeks that Lillian has been here we’ve done all sorts of things like Christmas baking, movie watching, eating good food and talking, but we’ve also done some sight-seeing. You can’t leave that out when you’re in New York, even if the weather is freezing!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
