<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Just life on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/category/just-life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Just life on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/category/just-life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Time travel into the past: July 2017</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2018/03/14/time-travel-into-the-past-july-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2018/03/14/time-travel-into-the-past-july-2017/</guid>
      <description>Life’s been happening by the spade full around here, and blogging has been severely neglected, sorry. Here’s an attempt at rectifying that!
Back in July last year… hmmm, let’s see if the photos can remind me that far back!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General update</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/07/28/general-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/07/28/general-update/</guid>
      <description>An update written by Ben for a change. After all, Franci has written almost all of the posts on this blog. As it happens, the last one Ben wrote was almost a year ago.
Ben is busy with various things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The rest of the summer</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/12/09/the-rest-of-the-summer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/12/09/the-rest-of-the-summer/</guid>
      <description>(This post is pretty heavy on photos. Just a reminder that if you want to see larger versions of them, to click on a photo and you’ll then be able to view the slideshow of that particular group of photos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random thoughts</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/06/10/random-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/06/10/random-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>The last couple of months have looked a little different to our usual routines. I’ve had a relapse of the Epstein-Barr virus which wiped me out but I seem to be feeling a fair bit better the last week or so; Ben’s been looking at different job options and has had multiple interviews with several different companies (no decision yet, though).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful autumn</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/11/20/beautiful-autumn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/11/20/beautiful-autumn/</guid>
      <description>I have a love-hate relationship with autumn. I love all the beautiful colors, the cooler weather and the fun things the season brings like apples, cinnamon, pumpkin pie and hot chocolate. But… autumn is the start of a long cold spell that only keeps getting worse for about 5 months before it starts getting better!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our new place</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/06/26/our-new-place-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/06/26/our-new-place-2/</guid>
      <description>I thought it’s about time I showed you a photo of our new place. We moved in Memorial Day (with the help of some amazing and hard-working friends), and have managed to unpack all the boxes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some nice things</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/31/some-nice-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/31/some-nice-things/</guid>
      <description>I like autumn. It’s not so hot, there are pretty colors everywhere, and the change of season brings all sorts of nice things like warm slippers and hot drinks, nice decorations and good smelling candles, and fun kids’ crafts…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If your daughter asks you for french toast…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/24/if-your-daughter-asks-you-for-french-toast/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/24/if-your-daughter-asks-you-for-french-toast/</guid>
      <description>If your daughter asks you for French toast, then you’ll be tempted to just say ‘no’. It’s a weekday, after all. But then you’ll remember that you want to be more of a ‘yes’ parent than a ‘no’ parent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I quit Facebook (for now)</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/10/why-i-quit-facebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/10/why-i-quit-facebook/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: this is simply my reasoning for giving up Facebook for the foreseeable future. I’m not saying any of this to make you feel like you should quit Facebook too.
&amp;nbsp;
I thought I’d give a bit of an explanation to those who might be interested on why I deactivated my Facebook account 3 months ago (since a few people have asked).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflecting on a year</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/06/20/reflecting-on-a-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/06/20/reflecting-on-a-year/</guid>
      <description>Laurelin Grace, our youngest, turned one recently. The first year of her life has been an eventful one for our family. She was born 3 weeks early, induced in a bit of a rush. For the first 5 weeks of her life, she nursed every 2 hours or less and developed strong lungs from all her colic-induced crying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A general update. About time too</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/06/06/a-general-update-about-time-too/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/06/06/a-general-update-about-time-too/</guid>
      <description>Three weeks ago, Laurelin turned one. I started writing a post the week before her birthday and got about two paragraphs in. Life is a bit like that at the moment — some people have hinted or asked directly if we will post regularly again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Settling in. Or at least trying to</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/04/24/settling-in-or-at-least-trying-to/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/04/24/settling-in-or-at-least-trying-to/</guid>
      <description>Our container with all our stuff arrived last Wednesday from New Zealand. It’s great to have our things again, but also very odd. It all seems so out of place. The furniture looks about as comfortable in our apartment as a fat girl in a skinny girl’s clothes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things I forgot</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/04/16/things-i-forgot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/04/16/things-i-forgot/</guid>
      <description>When you live somewhere and move away, it’s easy to forget the things that were strange, funny or hard, especially if they’re just small details of life. There are a few things that have struck me again, this time around, in no particular order:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We’ve moved in!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/04/05/weve-moved-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/04/05/weve-moved-in/</guid>
      <description>Just a quick note to let you all know that we’ve moved into our new apartment where we hope to be for the next year (or more) in Jersey City Heights. We moved in on Monday and it’s been a bit of a shambles around here that is slowly turning into order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2013: A year in photos</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/12/31/2013-a-year-in-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/12/31/2013-a-year-in-photos/</guid>
      <description>In an attempt to get up to date on here, I’m doing a ‘year in photos’, with a few glimpses into some of the highlights of the past year.
It’s one of those years I’m very thankful to see the end of.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
