<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Summer on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/category/summer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Summer on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/category/summer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The rest of the summer</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/12/09/the-rest-of-the-summer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/12/09/the-rest-of-the-summer/</guid>
      <description>(This post is pretty heavy on photos. Just a reminder that if you want to see larger versions of them, to click on a photo and you’ll then be able to view the slideshow of that particular group of photos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip ’16: Six Flags</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/11/04/roadtrip-16-six-flags/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/11/04/roadtrip-16-six-flags/</guid>
      <description>For the last leg of our roadtrip home, we made a stop at Six Flags in the south of New Jersey. They have a program called Read To Succeed where the kids have to read a total of 600 hours in the year to get free tickets to Six Flags.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip ’16: Hoyt Reunion</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/09/30/roadtrip-16-hoyt-reunion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/09/30/roadtrip-16-hoyt-reunion/</guid>
      <description>After our great camping experience, we drove down to Columbia, SC, to spend the night and visit Ben’s parents’ old church where we got to meet people who knew them 40 years ago, which was pretty neat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip ’16: Camping in TN</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/09/23/roadtrip-16-camping-in-tn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/09/23/roadtrip-16-camping-in-tn/</guid>
      <description>After our visit to Monticello we started the drive down to Cherokee National Forest in east Tennessee where we planned on camping for a couple of nights. We started off in the rain and the rain just got heavier and heavier, and there were predictions for a huge storm to pass over where we were going to camp that night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random thoughts</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/06/10/random-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/06/10/random-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>The last couple of months have looked a little different to our usual routines. I’ve had a relapse of the Epstein-Barr virus which wiped me out but I seem to be feeling a fair bit better the last week or so; Ben’s been looking at different job options and has had multiple interviews with several different companies (no decision yet, though).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to New Zealand, part 3</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/02/12/visit-to-new-zealand-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/02/12/visit-to-new-zealand-part-3/</guid>
      <description>I know this isn’t technically part of our trip to New Zealand, but I didn’t really want to make a whole separate post for these photos I took before we left. December was unseasonably warm, so one evening while Ben worked late, I took the kids on a post-dinner walk around the neighborhood to enjoy the lights on people’s houses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to New Zealand, part 2</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/02/05/visit-to-new-zealand-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/02/05/visit-to-new-zealand-part-2/</guid>
      <description>A couple of days after we arrived, we headed out of town to Mt Hutt in the Southern Alps for a Hoyt reunion. I think it had been the first time in almost 6 years that everyone were together again — Mum &amp;amp; Dad, all 8 siblings, plus spouses and kids — and it was fantastic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A summary of summer, part 3</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/09/19/a-summary-of-summer-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/09/19/a-summary-of-summer-part-3/</guid>
      <description>August was filled to the brim with activity. We said goodbye to our Chinese exchange students, and celebrated Ben’s birthday.
We swam a few times in our friend’s nearby pool, but also did a fun day trip out to go swim at a water hole our friend Sarah knows about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A summary of summer, part 2</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/09/11/a-summary-of-summer-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/09/11/a-summary-of-summer-part-2/</guid>
      <description>A summary of summer, continued.
In July, we hosted the Holtslags, our pastor from NZ and his family, as well as James and Laura (James is Phillipa’s son, Laura is the Holtslags’ daughter). This time we sent them off to do sight-seeing by themselves, but we still got to have some good conversations over the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A summary of summer, part 1</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/09/04/a-summary-of-summer-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/09/04/a-summary-of-summer-part-1/</guid>
      <description>I know our blog posts have been a bit sporadic recently, but we’ve been up to all sorts of mischief. It’s summer after all! We’ve had playdates, we’ve played in the sprinklers, we’ve done lots of swimming, we’ve had sleep-overs, we’ve had visits to the library, we’ve had a couple of road trips, we’ve had homemade lemonade, iced tea and popsicles, eaten tonnes of watermelon and peaches and corn… you know… summer stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
