<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recipes on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/category/recipes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recipes on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/category/recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Banana Cake with chocolate cream cheese icing</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/11/11/banana-cake-with-chocolate-cream-cheese-icing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/11/11/banana-cake-with-chocolate-cream-cheese-icing/</guid>
      <description>I built a cake earlier this week. I’m doing really well at blogging about it while the cake is still in existence on the kitchen counter! I’m still playing catch-up with blogging about news from the summer, but I wanted to share this before it died in my drafts folder like so many other recipes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marica’s 9th birthday</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/03/11/maricas-9th-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/03/11/maricas-9th-birthday/</guid>
      <description>My oldest turned 9 last month. Where did the time go? I know all mothers always say that, but my oh my, they grow up fast. Gone is the little girl who liked her hair braided all pretty, and who would wear whatever her mother put out for her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pie Day</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/01/01/pie-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/01/01/pie-day/</guid>
      <description>Back in mid-November I had a few girls from church over at our house for a pie making day. We worked hard, had lots of fun and got to enjoy some pretty yummy pies.
For those of you who might be interested, here are the recipes of what we made.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homemade nutella</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/16/homemade-nutella/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/16/homemade-nutella/</guid>
      <description>I’ve always wanted to try making a version of Nutella at home, so recently I tried it. There are oodles of recipes online, and the one I tried is from here. It calls for coconut sugar, which I think is a bit of a fad food (not to mention its sustainability is questionable), so I used regular sugar and maple syrup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some nice things</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/31/some-nice-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/31/some-nice-things/</guid>
      <description>I like autumn. It’s not so hot, there are pretty colors everywhere, and the change of season brings all sorts of nice things like warm slippers and hot drinks, nice decorations and good smelling candles, and fun kids’ crafts…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Malboro Man sandwich</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/20/a-malboro-man-sandwich/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/20/a-malboro-man-sandwich/</guid>
      <description>I’m subsribed to The Pioneer Woman Cooks blog, and with every recipe that comes from there I’m almost drooling. I’ve never had one of her recipes fail, and they’re always a hit. The Malboro Man Sandwich was especially a hit with Ben, and I loved it too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Fat Bacon Sliders</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/11/big-fat-bacon-sliders/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/11/big-fat-bacon-sliders/</guid>
      <description>Bacon is a beautiful thing. Whoever invented it needs a medal. Bacon and eggs, bacon on pizza, bacon in pasta, bacon with pretty much anything is just wonderful. (I’ve even seen bacon chocolate here in New York!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Christmas goodie report, with recipes</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/06/a-christmas-goodie-report-with-recipes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/06/a-christmas-goodie-report-with-recipes/</guid>
      <description>I love baking. I love sharing baking. I love receiving baking. I love eating baking. Who doesn’t?!
Christmas is always a time of the year that I excitedly go totally overboard in the baking department, making way too many goodies and loving every minute of it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nanaimo Bars</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/19/nanaimo-bars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/19/nanaimo-bars/</guid>
      <description>Let me introduce you to a lovely piece of goodness. This little bite of joy is apparently a Canadian treat, and when I saw a recipe for it online some months back, I knew it would be something Ben would enjoy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pizza!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/08/pizza/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/08/pizza/</guid>
      <description>I guess most of you know that there’s nothing much to homemade pizza, except that it can be time consuming. You can put pretty much anything on it, and cover it with cheese and you can call it pizza.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving yumminess</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/28/thanksgiving-yumminess/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/28/thanksgiving-yumminess/</guid>
      <description>Well, Thanksgiving came and went, and we had a lovely day. It was great to have a bonus day where Ben had the day off, and we enjoyed getting to know a friend from church a bit better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green and glorious</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/09/green-and-glorious/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/09/green-and-glorious/</guid>
      <description>Hooray for pesto! What a beautiful thing pesto is. Easy to make, and it gives a wonderful flavour to sandwiches, pastas, risotto, pizza, baked potatoes, salads, chocolate cake, wait, what? Just trust me, it’s good stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blueberry pancakes worth eating</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/11/blueberry-pancakes-worth-eating/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/11/blueberry-pancakes-worth-eating/</guid>
      <description>Blueberries are in season now here in the States and they’re plentiful and cheap. They’re also ridiculously good for you, but that’s really beside the point — what matters is that they taste so good! It’s hard to believe that they can taste better in any way other than plain from the punnet, but these pancakes bring out the blueberry flavour very well and they melt in your mouth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fish Parcels</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/11/fish-parcels/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/11/fish-parcels/</guid>
      <description>I have a quick and easy recipe to share with you. We’re not big fans of fish around here. Yes, I know we should be, it’s healthy and all that… omega 3’s and a bunch of other healthy bits and bobs, but fish just doesn’t really feature on our favourites list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yummy muesli</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/07/yummy-muesli/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/07/yummy-muesli/</guid>
      <description>Guess what I’m making today? Muesli! If you’ve never tried your hand at making your own, may I gently prod you in that direction? You will be done with it and with cleaning your kitchen within half an hour, and you’ll be thanking yourself for doing it every breakfast for the next few weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheesecake and getting old</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/28/cheesecake-and-getting-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/28/cheesecake-and-getting-old/</guid>
      <description>Last Sunday (a week and a half ago, almost), I got another year older. It’s funny how birthday excitement has the tendency to wane as you get older! Though perhaps that’s not a good way for me to look at it — it would be better to think about being blessed with another year instead of having a hum-ho attitude of ‘oh, just another year’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Salmon and Couscous Salad</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/14/spring-salmon-and-couscous-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/14/spring-salmon-and-couscous-salad/</guid>
      <description>I know that I’ve had a lot of recipes on here recently. Maybe that can partly be attributed to the weather — the more time we have inside, the more time I have to do fun stuff in the kitchen, plus it’s not so insanely hot when the oven goes on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuscan Pork with beans</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/04/tuscan-pork-with-beans/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/04/tuscan-pork-with-beans/</guid>
      <description>Can I just draw your attention to something rather delicious?
Slow-cooked Tuscan Pork is the thing! I got the recipe on Femina, so you’d better hop over there if you want it. Let me just tell you that this is worth making.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The beauty of bread</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/21/the-beauty-of-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/21/the-beauty-of-bread/</guid>
      <description>Here in the States, I’ve taken to baking most of our bread from scratch by hand, because I can’t stand the taste of the bread here. Specialty breads here taste great, but I do still have a grocery budget to stick to!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cherry Delight on the menu tonight</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/26/cherry-delight-on-the-menu-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/26/cherry-delight-on-the-menu-tonight/</guid>
      <description>Cherry Delight was introduced to us by Lillian, who made it for one of our Advent dinner desserts. She, in turn, got it from her Grandma Tschetter. It is very delicious, and therefore I feel compelled to share the goodness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy self-crusting pie recipe</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/27/easy-self-crusting-pie-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/27/easy-self-crusting-pie-recipe/</guid>
      <description>I have another easy and yummy recipe to share with you. This is kind of like a quiche, and kind of like a pie… and it is so fast it almost feels like cheating! It’s a Jo Seagar recipe, one that I acquired at the same time as the fudge recipe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>High class mac ‘n cheese recipe (done)</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/10/high-class-mac--n-cheese-recipe-done/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/10/high-class-mac--n-cheese-recipe-done/</guid>
      <description>We recently had an Italian-themed pot-luck lunch at church (we have pot-lucks once a month on the Sunday we have Lord’s Supper) and I wanted to find a recipe that was not just another lasagne. In my online search I came across this recipe, which I thought tasted very yummy indeed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sugar snap pea salad</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/03/sugar-snap-pea-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/03/sugar-snap-pea-salad/</guid>
      <description>When we visited aunt Sharon and uncle Sherwood Hoyt, aunt Sharon made a really nice salad for dinner one evening. I thought it was absolutely delicious and so I’m going to share it here. The recipe can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Really good fudge</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/23/really-good-fudge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/23/really-good-fudge/</guid>
      <description>I haven’t made fudge many times before, but whenever I’ve tried, it’s turned out terribly. Either too soft and runny, or hard and crystallised. Until the day I made this recipe that I obtained in a dubious way…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tasty Recipe and more</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/01/tasty-recipe-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/01/tasty-recipe-and-more/</guid>
      <description>Last night we had some company (a work colleague of Ben’s) and I made a new recipe. I have a very bad habit of trying new recipes when we have people over, but this time it was definitely a winner!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
