<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Culture on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/category/culture/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Culture on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/category/culture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The new GiftyWeddings.com</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/04/06/the-new-giftyweddings-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/04/06/the-new-giftyweddings-com/</guid>
      <description>Most of you know that I (this is Ben posting for a change) run a little wedding gift registry website called GiftyWeddings.com. It’s been going for almost eight years now, helping several couples every month create nice simple gift registries that aren’t tied to a particular store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Side by Side</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/05/01/side-by-side/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/05/01/side-by-side/</guid>
      <description>I’m so glad to have been given the opportunity to review the book Side by Side by Jana Kelley. I met Jana back in 2004 when I spent half a year working in Sudan. Although Jana was not a part of the team I was working with, our paths crossed fairly regularly: we taught a conversational English class together at a tea house for women; and I taught and helped out at the school where her boys attended.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In lieu of Halloween</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/12/05/in-lieu-of-halloween/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/12/05/in-lieu-of-halloween/</guid>
      <description>This year, instead of celebrating Halloween, which is such a massive deal here in the States and which we don’t feel particularly comfortable with joining in on for various reasons, we decided to do things a little differently and have a Fall Party with our good friends, Alfredo and Damaris and their kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A hobbit comes of age</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/08/a-hobbit-comes-of-age/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/08/a-hobbit-comes-of-age/</guid>
      <description>As everyone knows — well, at least everyone who’s a fan of Tolkien — a hobbit comes of age at 33. I turned this ripe old age the other day, and had a fabulous party, mostly organized by Franci, my lovely hobbit-wife.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marica’s recital at Steinway Hall</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/07/18/maricas-recital-at-steinway-hall/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/07/18/maricas-recital-at-steinway-hall/</guid>
      <description>Marica and Esther started piano lessons the week after our piano arrived, and have both been enjoying it a lot, no doubt because of their excellent teacher (who also happens to be our friend!), Shannon Murphy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr Rubik’s back</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/05/08/mr-rubiks-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/05/08/mr-rubiks-back/</guid>
      <description>Marica and I went to the Liberty Science Center in Jersey City last Saturday to see their new Rubik’s Cube exhibition, which was being opened by Ernő Rubik, the inventor of the cube. I own a cube, but still have no idea how to solve it…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elisabeth Elliot, you’re being milked!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/05/05/elisabeth-elliot-youre-being-milked/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/05/05/elisabeth-elliot-youre-being-milked/</guid>
      <description>Reference: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Passion_and_Purity :-)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>East Wind Over Weehawken</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/03/24/east-wind-over-weehawken/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/03/24/east-wind-over-weehawken/</guid>
      <description>The other night we had our temporary landlord over for dinner and as well as having a lovely time, we also found out a bit about some of the art around here. The big painting in the dining room is a replica of The Storm by Pierre Auguste Cot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hacker Christianity</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/12/22/hacker-christianity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/12/22/hacker-christianity/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This is a written version of a pre-Christmas talk I gave at work recently, about the intersection between Christianity and hacker culture. There’s also a video available here — the sound quality’s not brilliant, but feel free to watch it there!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presbyterians of the world, unite!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/11/27/presbyterians-of-the-world-unite/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/11/27/presbyterians-of-the-world-unite/</guid>
      <description>After hours of sweatless toil, I present to you the Plain English Westminster, or PEW if you like. It’s my “translation” of the Westminster Confession of Faith into modern English.
This is a project I’ve been working on for the last couple of years, very on and off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kidnapped!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/03/06/kidnapped/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/03/06/kidnapped/</guid>
      <description>I wasn’t, but Chuck Geschke was.
Let me back up a bit: for Christmas, Franci gave me a true geek book called Masterminds of Programming, which I reviewed in detail here. One of the interviews was with the creators of PostScript, a computer language used to control printers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books we’ve read recently</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/24/books-weve-read-recently/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/24/books-weve-read-recently/</guid>
      <description>For your interest, here’s a list of some of the books we’ve read in the last year or so, with a tiny summary of each. Most of them are really good. I’ve put B after the author’s name if only I’ve read it, F if just Franci’s read it, or BF if we’ve both read it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Enlightenment Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/19/quantum-enlightenment-dynamics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/19/quantum-enlightenment-dynamics/</guid>
      <description>The other day we received an incredible free magazine: NEWLIFE EXPO — America’s Largest Mind, Body, Spirit Expo. Its highly intelligent content, its carefully-placed typos, and its cohesive aesthetic have provided Franci and me with more belly laughs than any comedy magazine ever could.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips for new New Yorkers</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/29/tips-for-new-new-yorkers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/29/tips-for-new-new-yorkers/</guid>
      <description>It takes a lot of adjusting to live in the greatest city in the world, and there are some protocols that you should follow if you want to survive in this city. You might be a kind, generous and gentle person in the privacy of your own home, but follow these tips for how to act in public, and within a couple of weeks you will not only feel like a real New Yorker, but look like it to anyone watching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Autobiography of Benjamin Franklin</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/23/the-autobiography-of-benjamin-franklin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/23/the-autobiography-of-benjamin-franklin/</guid>
      <description>Some time ago Franci picked up a little, falling-apart paperback version of The Autobiography of Benjamin Franklin. As well as having a pretty respectable first name, Franklin was a fascinating character in many respects. Was he a printer, a writer, a politician, or an inventor?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A visit to the New York City Ballet</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/15/a-visit-to-the-new-york-city-ballet-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/15/a-visit-to-the-new-york-city-ballet-2/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend our friend Megan, who dances in the New York City Ballet, gave us two tickets to attend The Nutcracker ballet at the Lincoln Centre, and Ben took Marica to go watch her dance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent is here!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/10/advent-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/10/advent-is-here/</guid>
      <description>I started the blog post draft a few weeks back, and now the season of Advent is about halfway through. Last year we decided to start celebrating Advent in a more deliberate way, building the excitement until Christmas, and enjoying the anticipation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caring for Creation</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/02/caring-for-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/02/caring-for-creation/</guid>
      <description>My friend Matthew Bartlett recently started his own publishing company, and his first book is The Biblical Mandate for Caring for Creation by retired New Zealand minister Dick Tripp. The 158-page book, which can be yours for a mere $24.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The beauty of gratitude</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/23/the-beauty-of-gratitude/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/23/the-beauty-of-gratitude/</guid>
      <description>What a great gift to have a whole feast day dedicated to giving thanks! I’m relishing the opportunity to celebrate Thanksgiving while we’re here in the States. It might even be a tradition we take home to New Zealand with us!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Christianity sexist?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/19/is-christianity-sexist/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/19/is-christianity-sexist/</guid>
      <description>Perhaps the most-prayed Christian prayer is the Lord’s Prayer: “Our Father who art in heaven…” But why Father and not person or parent? Is Christianity sexist?
Our home church denomination recently held a national Synod meeting, and one of the things they discussed was the updated 2011 translation of the NIV Bible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A hairy theme at the Met</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/31/a-hairy-theme-at-the-met/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/31/a-hairy-theme-at-the-met/</guid>
      <description>Every time I go to the Metropolitan Museum of Art I see something I haven’t seen before, and I certainly go back to old favourites. Recently I took some photos with a hairy theme. Some of them are so ridiculous, you’d have to be an old stodge not to even get a slight smile at the lips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some cool photos of the Guggenheim</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/27/some-cool-photos-of-the-guggenheim/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/27/some-cool-photos-of-the-guggenheim/</guid>
      <description>I don’t really care for modern art much, so I’ve never felt a deep desire to go look at what’s inside the Guggenheim museum (I can get my fill at the Met by glimpsing at the modern art section when I walk past there to get to the European sculptures).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Night</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/24/night/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/24/night/</guid>
      <description>“Why are you downcast, O my soul? Why so disturbed within me?” Ps 43:5
That’s what this sculpture by Aristide Maillol brought to mind when I saw it at the Metropolitan Museum of Art.
The artist did an amazing job — it was as if everything about her just felt so sad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Person’s Prayer</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/17/the-persons-prayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/17/the-persons-prayer/</guid>
      <description>Our Caregiver in the spiritual realm,
Transparent be your name.
Your democracy be voted in,
Your social policy be implemented,
In reality as it is in the spiritual realm.
Give us every day our organic tofu,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A pre-engagement visit</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/07/a-pre-engagement-visit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/07/a-pre-engagement-visit/</guid>
      <description>Now that you all know that Lillian and Jeremy are engaged, we can all happily say “Hooray!”. Lillian was here for a very short visit (just under 2 weeks) and flew into JFK, so we got the privilege of hosting the two of them for a few nights before they went off to Philadelphia to go get engaged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luth3r hacks iChurch, makes Bible open source</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/30/luth3r-hacks-ichurch-makes-bible-open-source/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/30/luth3r-hacks-ichurch-makes-bible-open-source/</guid>
      <description>GENEVA TRIBUNE, August 1517.
New things are afoot in the world of Scripture freedom. Two days ago a hacker, who goes under the pseudonym Mart1n Luth3r, released a set of 95 bullet points outlining how to hack iChurch’s core systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How high do your kids rank?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/27/how-high-do-your-kids-rank/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/27/how-high-do-your-kids-rank/</guid>
      <description>Another excellent article from Rachel Jankovic. A good look at how society views children, where your children rank in your priorities, and the calling of motherhood. I encourage you to go read it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I stopped reading a classic</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/22/why-i-stopped-reading-a-classic/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/22/why-i-stopped-reading-a-classic/</guid>
      <description>The Brothers Karamazov by Fyodor Dostoyevsky is a classic, or so I’ve heard. It’s one of those books so great and so worth reading that no one you talk to has actually read it.
A 700-page novel is something of a commitment, but I approached this one with an open mind and a daily subway commute.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lorraine, the not-so Divine</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/20/lorraine-the-not-so-divine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/20/lorraine-the-not-so-divine/</guid>
      <description>Saw this old building on our way to Jeremy’s place in Philadelphia, and couldn’t help noticing the irony.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proof that we are Americanizing</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/20/proof-that-we-are-americanizing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/20/proof-that-we-are-americanizing/</guid>
      <description>I have Uncrustables in my freezer. Yes, ma’am, I tell no lie. Uncrustables in your freezer means that you have attained to the great feat of crossing over to The Other Side. For any of you ignorant folk who do not know about the beauty of Uncrustables, let me introduce you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Up close and personal with Lady Liberty</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/16/up-close-and-personal-with-lady-liberty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/16/up-close-and-personal-with-lady-liberty/</guid>
      <description>The New Colossus By Emma Lazarus, 1883
Not like the brazen giant of Greek fame,
With conquering limbs astride from land to land;
Here at our sea-washed, sunset gates shall stand
A mighty woman with a torch, whose flame</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A too-short visit to The Met</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/06/a-too-short-visit-to-the-met/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/06/a-too-short-visit-to-the-met/</guid>
      <description>When Hannah and Eva were here, we went to the Met the same day we went to the Cloisters. The Met really deserves a day or two to itself, and I definitely plan to go back — the two or so hours we had there were only enough to see a few musical instruments and about 3/4 of the European Painters section.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An uncultured laugh (specially for April Fool’s day)</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/01/an-uncultured-laugh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/01/an-uncultured-laugh/</guid>
      <description>When I went to The Cloisters with Hannah and Eva, there were a few sculptures/carvings that I took pictures of purely to post on here with funny comments, because they sure made us crack up. My apologies go to the artists who did not create their masterpieces for us to laugh at, and to those of you who find Roman Catholic artefacts more meaningful than un-cultured moi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting The Cloisters</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/30/revisiting-the-cloisters/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/30/revisiting-the-cloisters/</guid>
      <description>When Ben’s cousins, Hannah and Eva, were here visiting with us, the three of us took a trip up into Manhattan to see The Cloisters and The Met (The Met will be in another post!).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Should churches care about branding?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/11/should-churches-care-about-branding/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/11/should-churches-care-about-branding/</guid>
      <description>Centuries ago (in internet time) graphic designer David Airey wrote a blog post asking folks whether they’d seen any good church logos. My brother Bryan responded with a thought-provoking comment asking whether churches should even be concerned about “branding”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Franci the judge</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/10/franci-the-judge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/10/franci-the-judge/</guid>
      <description>Now that’s a catchy title if I ever saw one! :-)
This past Saturday I took the train up to a little town called Irvington on the bank of the Hudson river where there was a huge homeschoolers debating tournament going on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is it vague, or is it lazy?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/18/is-it-vague-or-is-it-lazy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/18/is-it-vague-or-is-it-lazy/</guid>
      <description>This article is best read out loud for maximum effect.
I like read this interesting article the other day, and, you know, I thought it was pretty interesting, so I thought I’d like link to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The One True BDFL</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/14/the-one-true-bdfl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/14/the-one-true-bdfl/</guid>
      <description>Note: This blog is mostly read by family and friends, but I wrote this more for my fellow programmers. Knowing me, it’ll be taken the wrong way by both groups of people. :-) By the way, see the first comment for a book give-away!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Having a bad day parenting? Sue McDonald’s!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/19/having-a-bad-day-parenting-sue-mcdonalds/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/19/having-a-bad-day-parenting-sue-mcdonalds/</guid>
      <description>Warning: This article may contain traces of sarcasm.
Maybe she was just having a bad day as a parent. Or who knows, maybe she is getting paid by an advocacy group. But one Mizz Parham from California seems to have a thing against Happy Meals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cloisters</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/13/the-cloisters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/13/the-cloisters/</guid>
      <description>Some of you have no doubt heard of The Metropolitan Museum of Art, or “The Met”, here in New York City. It’s a massive museum of art and culture, along Museum Mile on the east side of Central Park.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
