<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Frugal fun on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/category/frugal-fun/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Frugal fun on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/category/frugal-fun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Knoxville Farmers’ Market</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/18/the-knoxville-farmers-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/18/the-knoxville-farmers-market/</guid>
      <description>Today is our second day at the Hoyt reunion in Georgia. Since I’ve last blogged we’ve visited the Holders in Knoxville, and some friends in Atlanta. I hope to blog about that soon, but I need to catch up with sharing some of the things we did in Knoxville first!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Christmas craft afternoon</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/20/a-christmas-craft-afternoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/20/a-christmas-craft-afternoon/</guid>
      <description>On an unseasonably warm Saturday late in November, a few women from our church gathered at our friend Jen’s house to make some Christmas crafts. It was bliss… lots of good chatting and food while being enjoyably creative and productive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer is here!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/16/summer-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/16/summer-is-here/</guid>
      <description>And we’ve well and truly been out and about enjoying it. We’ve only had two very hot days and for the rest of the time it has been pretty much perfect weather (25 - 30 C).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When you don’t have a sandwich press…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/26/when-you-dont-have-a-sandwich-press/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/26/when-you-dont-have-a-sandwich-press/</guid>
      <description>… make your own with whatever you have on hand!
See, it works pretty well!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More cereal box fun</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/18/more-cereal-box-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/18/more-cereal-box-fun/</guid>
      <description>When we looked for ideas for what kinds of crafts one can make with cereal boxes, back when we made Glitter Girl, we also came across a cute idea of making sandals. I promised Marica we’d do that, and here’s the result.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grocery challenge: week 4. I’m done!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/01/week-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/01/week-4/</guid>
      <description>Let’s just say I’m glad to have life returning to normal! It was a good little exercise in sticking to a budget (or close to, anyway), but I don’t think I’ll be doing that again any time soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grocery Challenge: week 3</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/25/grocery-challenge-week-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/25/grocery-challenge-week-3/</guid>
      <description>This past week seems to have been shorter than the others. Strange how that happens sometimes. Maybe it was because I didn’t have to cook very often! The flu was still having a field day, uh, week at our house and even Ben stayed home for 2 days from work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grocery Challenge: week 2</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/18/grocery-challenge-week-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/18/grocery-challenge-week-2/</guid>
      <description>In some ways, week 2 was a lot easier than week 1. I only bought what I needed, but it seemed that I needed more than $25 worth of stuff a week. You’re probably all thinking “I knew she couldn’t do it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cereal box fun</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/13/cereal-box-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/13/cereal-box-fun/</guid>
      <description>Last week we were all a bit under the weather, but of course when kids are sick they are still full of ideas and energy. So one morning after finishing off a box of cereal, I remembered doing crafts with cereal boxes as a kid and looked online for something to do with the cereal box.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October grocery challenge: week 1</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/11/grocery-challenge-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/11/grocery-challenge-1/</guid>
      <description>I had a very interesting moment on the first day of the challenge. I had hopped over to Tim Challies’ blog and read an article about The Heart of Frugality. I almost immediately wanted to forget about this challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My October grocery challenge</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/05/my-october-grocery-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/05/my-october-grocery-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes I feel like challenging myself in areas I’m not very good at. Like spending a small amount of money on groceries. Which is why it is a challenge! Here’s what I’m doing:
I’ve decided to try to reach the end of October and spend no more than $100 on groceries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your comments, preschool and a jewelery hanger</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/12/your-comments-preschool-and-a-jewelery-hanger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/12/your-comments-preschool-and-a-jewelery-hanger/</guid>
      <description>Some people have told us that they enjoy our blog. Thanks, that’s cool! :-) However, I would encourage you to add your comments — having a blog is a bit like us having a conversation with everyone who reads it, and your comments help this conversation feel a little less one-sided.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rainy day fun</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/27/rainy-day-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/27/rainy-day-fun/</guid>
      <description>When I realised that we have rain forecast for most of this past week, I wondered how on earth I was going to entertain two busy little people indoors? But then I just googled ‘rainy day activities with preschoolers’ and it comes up with a list of stuff to do that will keep you occupied almost all winter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From old to new</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/22/from-old-to-new/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/22/from-old-to-new/</guid>
      <description>Last week I had fun being a bit creative using stuff that was left here from the previous tenant and sprucing them up a bit. The whole Reduce, Recycle and Reuse slogan comes to mind, but also making things pretty for cheap really appeals to me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
