<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Friends on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/category/friends/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Friends on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/category/friends/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A little time travel into the past: May</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/10/10/a-little-time-travel-into-the-past-may/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/10/10/a-little-time-travel-into-the-past-may/</guid>
      <description>May brought an end to our homeschool co-op (but not to our schooling at home — that we continued until the end of June, much to the kids’ chagrin). We have a little tradition where our family takes a few friends out to a local chocolate shop where each of the kids (and moms) can choose a treat on the last day of co-op for the school year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three little flower girls</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/05/09/three-little-flower-girls/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/05/09/three-little-flower-girls/</guid>
      <description>Back in February our 3 girls got to be flower girls for a lovely couple in our church, Kelvin and Joanna. It was a beautiful day — unseasonably warm for February basically the whole week leading up to the wedding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A decade old!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/05/02/a-decade-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/05/02/a-decade-old/</guid>
      <description>In February, Marica turned 10. TEN?? How does a decade go by so fast? Marica is growing up — both taller and also growing in maturity little by little. Or maybe not so little! Her independence in the kitchen is growing, and she’s becoming quite the cook and baker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/01/26/advent/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/01/26/advent/</guid>
      <description>Advent is such a great time of the year. It’s filled with the anticipation of Christmas, warm kitchens overflowing with delicious smells, Christmas crafts, Christmas music playing in the background, parties, friends… (and it’s unfortunately also filled with busyness, usually mostly my own doing!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful autumn</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/12/23/beautiful-autumn-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/12/23/beautiful-autumn-2/</guid>
      <description>Autumn this year was beautiful and mild and felt like a sort of nicer continuation of summer. We were, of course, back at doing school, but we tried to enjoy the nice weather as much as we could.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The rest of the summer</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/12/09/the-rest-of-the-summer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/12/09/the-rest-of-the-summer/</guid>
      <description>(This post is pretty heavy on photos. Just a reminder that if you want to see larger versions of them, to click on a photo and you’ll then be able to view the slideshow of that particular group of photos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MeRF Getaway</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/09/02/merf-getaway/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/09/02/merf-getaway/</guid>
      <description>Back in June, some folks in our church (MeRF = Messiah’s Reformed Fellowship) headed out to Pennsylvania for a getaway at Kirby House, a beautiful old house that was once used by the Kirby family as their summer home in the mountains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurelin’s 3rd birthday</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/08/26/laurelins-3rd-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/08/26/laurelins-3rd-birthday/</guid>
      <description>In all the bustle of the end of the school year and then summer vacation, I’ve neglected to post photos of Laurelin’s 3rd birthday.
Laurelin is now a full-blown 3-year-old and no push-over, in every sense of the word.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finishing up the school year</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/08/19/finishing-up-the-school-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/08/19/finishing-up-the-school-year/</guid>
      <description>It’s taken us a while to get used to this business of school finishing right in the middle of the calendar year and the starting again in August/September when we are so used to the school year following the calendar year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Spring Tea Party</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/05/13/a-spring-tea-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/05/13/a-spring-tea-party/</guid>
      <description>In our living room stands a beautiful wooden display cabinet that has been in my family for 3 generations. It displays a selection of pretty tea cups, teapots, milk pitchers and sugar pots I have been given from my grandma, my mum, and Ben’s grandma Tschetter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easter 2016</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/05/06/easter-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/05/06/easter-2016/</guid>
      <description>This year’s Easter was a busy but lovely one. We kept up the tradition of making hot cross buns and egg dying, which the kids always love,
&amp;nbsp;
and on Easter Sunday we hosted a large crowd of church folk for a yummy dinner, followed by some rousing hymn singing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick, sticky snow</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/04/08/quick-sticky-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/04/08/quick-sticky-snow/</guid>
      <description>It’s been quiet on here for a while. When that happens, it usually means things around here have been a little extra busy, which it indeed has. Some of the highlights of the busyness will be following in the next few weeks, but before the warm weather completely overtakes us I wanted to share some last winter snow pictures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marica’s 9th birthday</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/03/11/maricas-9th-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/03/11/maricas-9th-birthday/</guid>
      <description>My oldest turned 9 last month. Where did the time go? I know all mothers always say that, but my oh my, they grow up fast. Gone is the little girl who liked her hair braided all pretty, and who would wear whatever her mother put out for her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to New Zealand, part 4</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/02/19/visit-to-new-zealand-part-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/02/19/visit-to-new-zealand-part-4/</guid>
      <description>A couple of days after Christmas Ben returned to the US, and the girls and I stayed in NZ for another 3 (full, but great) weeks. We met up with lots of family and friends and had such a great time that for the most part I forgot to take my camera along.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pie Day</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/01/01/pie-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/01/01/pie-day/</guid>
      <description>Back in mid-November I had a few girls from church over at our house for a pie making day. We worked hard, had lots of fun and got to enjoy some pretty yummy pies.
For those of you who might be interested, here are the recipes of what we made.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Esther’s 6th birthday</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/11/27/esthers-6th-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/11/27/esthers-6th-birthday/</guid>
      <description>Esther turned 6 in November. Hard to believe, isn’t it?! Her birthday celebrations were spread out over two days — on Friday at co-op the kids sang Happy Birthday to her and she and Marica handed out cupcakes that Marica had baked (no, Mum, you’re not allowed to help me!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CCEF’s 2015 conference</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/11/06/ccefs-2015-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/11/06/ccefs-2015-conference/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weekends ago, I had the amazing opportunity to travel down to Virginia Beach for this year’s CCEF (Christian Counseling and Educational Foundation) Conference. The topic of this year’s conference was Side by Side: How God helps us help each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A summary of summer, part 3</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/09/19/a-summary-of-summer-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/09/19/a-summary-of-summer-part-3/</guid>
      <description>August was filled to the brim with activity. We said goodbye to our Chinese exchange students, and celebrated Ben’s birthday.
We swam a few times in our friend’s nearby pool, but also did a fun day trip out to go swim at a water hole our friend Sarah knows about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas 2014</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/30/christmas-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/30/christmas-2014/</guid>
      <description>This year was the first year I hosted all of Christmas (meaning both our Christmas Eve and Christmas Day celebrations), and it was fun! We had my parents with us, which was very special, and we also hosted James and Laura Williams and Laura’s friend, Ella.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In lieu of Halloween</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/12/05/in-lieu-of-halloween/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/12/05/in-lieu-of-halloween/</guid>
      <description>This year, instead of celebrating Halloween, which is such a massive deal here in the States and which we don’t feel particularly comfortable with joining in on for various reasons, we decided to do things a little differently and have a Fall Party with our good friends, Alfredo and Damaris and their kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cooking with friends</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/11/07/cooking-with-friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/11/07/cooking-with-friends/</guid>
      <description>When I was in high school, a woman in our church (hi, Jantina!) got a bunch of us young’uns together for a day of cooking at her house. She gave us some basic recipes and tips and together we spent the day cooking and baking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A hobbit comes of age</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/08/a-hobbit-comes-of-age/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/08/a-hobbit-comes-of-age/</guid>
      <description>As everyone knows — well, at least everyone who’s a fan of Tolkien — a hobbit comes of age at 33. I turned this ripe old age the other day, and had a fabulous party, mostly organized by Franci, my lovely hobbit-wife.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On being home</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/08/15/on-being-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/08/15/on-being-home/</guid>
      <description>So yes, as Ben informed you about 2 weeks ago, we’re back in Christchurch! I can hardly believe it’s been two weeks, because it’s been so busy with unpacking and getting right into things here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photoless reporting is not quite my style</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/07/21/photoless-reporting-is-not-quite-my-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/07/21/photoless-reporting-is-not-quite-my-style/</guid>
      <description>I’m finding it hard to keep up the blogging while we’re on the road, as you’ve no doubt realised! Not that it’s going to stop me trying. I’ll start by giving a quick run down of what happened after the Hoyt reunion up to the point where I’ve got photos again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip stop 5: Hoyt Reunion in Georgia</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/07/13/roadtrip-stop-5-hoyt-reunion-in-georgia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/07/13/roadtrip-stop-5-hoyt-reunion-in-georgia/</guid>
      <description>In mid-June, we spent a fantastic week in Georgia with some fantastic people at our Hoyt family reunion. Uncle Stan and Aunt Nora hosted us very well. There were great activities, delicious food, lots of fun times joking around, playing games, catching up and having a blast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip, stop 4: Atlanta</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/30/roadtrip-stop-4-atlanta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/30/roadtrip-stop-4-atlanta/</guid>
      <description>After visiting the Holders in Knoxville, TN, we travelled down to Atlanta. For some reason our GPS took us on the scenic route instead of the Interstate, which was a nice change of pace and a very beautiful drive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Roadtrip, stop 2</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/10/the-roadtrip-stop-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/10/the-roadtrip-stop-2/</guid>
      <description>After our first stop in Connecticut with the Snoeks, we headed down to Philadelphia where we stayed with Lillian and Jeremy and visited with several friends over the course of the weekend.
On the way to Lillian and Jeremy we stopped and Sam and Emily Perez’s home, friends from our church in New York.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The start of The Roadtrip</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/06/the-start-of-the-roadtrip/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/06/the-start-of-the-roadtrip/</guid>
      <description>We had a rather stressful start to our roadtrip. I was overly optimistic (or foolish?) and hoped that everything might just fit into 6 suitcases plus a bunch of little bits and pieces. My reasoning for this was that I couldn’t see us parting with much more — I only kept the things I really wanted to and had gotten rid of more than felt comfortable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We’ve hit the road!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/04/weve-hit-the-road/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/06/04/weve-hit-the-road/</guid>
      <description>The last week has been a crazy whirlwind of activity. We got rid of a lot of stuff, selling some things on Craigslist, selling a bunch of things at our stoop sale and giving loads of stuff away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Packing up, cleaning out, giving away, selling…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/24/packing-up-cleaning-out-giving-away-selling/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/24/packing-up-cleaning-out-giving-away-selling/</guid>
      <description>That’s what I’m doing a lot of at the moment. And I’m seriously worried about this 4 suitcase limit. I’m just praying that our rental car can fit more than that because just our family’s clothing takes up 3 suitcases!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adventures with hippos</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/12/adventures-with-hippos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/12/adventures-with-hippos/</guid>
      <description>In Central Park there is this cool playground that has a herd of hippos made out of fibre glass (?? I guess). The kids always think it’s fun to pretend to ride the hippos.
So do some of the adults.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 years of friendship, and still going strong</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/10/20-years-of-friendship-and-still-going-strong/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/10/20-years-of-friendship-and-still-going-strong/</guid>
      <description>In March, my friend Lizel visited us from South Africa.
Lizel and I have been close friends since we were seven years old, despite living apart for 15 of those. As kids, we would do all sorts of crazy things like pelt the neighbour’s house with mud cookies, or knock on people’s doors and run away, or take whoopie cushions into shops and walk through the aisles making farting noises.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marica turned 5</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/12/marica-turned-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/12/marica-turned-5/</guid>
      <description>How is it that they go from this…
to this…
so unbelievably fast?
Too fast, that’s what. I’m sure someone’s been speeding up the time.
Marica turned 5 in February, but when we were in New Zealand, my mum (Ouma to the kids) threw a birthday party for Marica.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reconnecting with friends and family</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/08/reconnecting-with-friends-and-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/08/reconnecting-with-friends-and-family/</guid>
      <description>When the girls and I were in New Zealand, we had quite the social time visiting friends and family. The kids got so used to going out and visiting people that if we had the odd morning where we weren’t going out they’d ask, “aren’t we going to visit someone today?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More wedding pictures</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/16/more-wedding-pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/16/more-wedding-pictures/</guid>
      <description>Well, I said I’d share some more wedding pictures when I got some time to get them on here. I didn’t get the time, but I made the time, so here they are.
The first lot of photos were taken outside in the harsh sunlight (always a bad move), so unfortunately everyone has sunglass shadows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeremy and Lillian’s wedding day</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/14/jeremy-and-lillians-wedding-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/14/jeremy-and-lillians-wedding-day/</guid>
      <description>On January the 21st Jeremy and Lillian tied the knot, and it was a beautiful day in all respects. It was lovely and sunny (even it if was a bit windy), everything went smoothly and it was just such a joyous day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another wonderful Christmas</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/04/another-wonderful-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/04/another-wonderful-christmas/</guid>
      <description>Christmas feels like such a long time ago… but I really want to share these photos with you from our time with Jeremy’s folks.
We took the bus to Philadelphia from where Jeremy picked us up and drove us out to his parents’ place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gingerbread House fun</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/22/gingerbread-house-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/22/gingerbread-house-fun/</guid>
      <description>Our much loved pastor’s wife, Julie, invited a few moms over to her house last Friday to make gingerbread houses. What a total blast! We made the houses out of graham crackers instead of baked sheets of gingerbread, which was much easier and less time consuming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Christmas craft afternoon</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/20/a-christmas-craft-afternoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/20/a-christmas-craft-afternoon/</guid>
      <description>On an unseasonably warm Saturday late in November, a few women from our church gathered at our friend Jen’s house to make some Christmas crafts. It was bliss… lots of good chatting and food while being enjoyably creative and productive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A visit to the New York City Ballet</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/15/a-visit-to-the-new-york-city-ballet-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/15/a-visit-to-the-new-york-city-ballet-2/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend our friend Megan, who dances in the New York City Ballet, gave us two tickets to attend The Nutcracker ballet at the Lincoln Centre, and Ben took Marica to go watch her dance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More good times</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/17/more-good-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/17/more-good-times/</guid>
      <description>Our last overnight stop on our roadtrip with my parents was at Mr &amp;amp; Mrs Brauning’s place. Mr Brauning is a pastor who came and filled our pulpit for a few months while our home congregation was vacant and the Braunings are loved by many back home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stop 3 on the trip</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/14/stop-3-on-the-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/14/stop-3-on-the-trip/</guid>
      <description>Just a little note: I’m not blogging real-time. I think I might have blogged about something on the same day it happened about twice in the whole time I’ve had this blog. I just don’t have the luxury of lots of time to be able to do that!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road trip report, Days 5 and 6</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/06/road-trip-report-days-5-and-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/06/road-trip-report-days-5-and-6/</guid>
      <description>We left Washington D.C. on a Friday afternoon and drove up to Baltimore. I’m not sure if we saw the wrong side of Baltimore or what, but neither of us were particularly impressed. I guess that wasn’t helped by a fire drill going on at the Art Museum as soon as we walked in, and nobody knowing what was going on, including the staff, which meant we just walked straight back out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road trip report, Day 4</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/30/road-trip-report-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/30/road-trip-report-day-4/</guid>
      <description>So you’re all dying to hear how we became chummy with the President, right? Well, it happened like this: we were walking outside the fence of his big fancy house, admiring the well kept garden and lawns, all lonesome and deserted when suddenly he jumped out of the bushes and shouted “BOO!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road trip report, Day 3</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/26/road-trip-report-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/26/road-trip-report-day-3/</guid>
      <description>Just a little note: I’ve switched to uploading smaller photos on here, to make things faster for me while editing blog posts, and hopefully also for you as subscribers having to download the posts. As far as I can tell the quality is still pretty good, but let me know what you think.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road trip report, Day 1 and 2</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/24/road-trip-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/24/road-trip-report/</guid>
      <description>So like I said, Margaret took me and the girls on a week-long road trip (thanks, Gary!) and boy did we have fun! There was a good amount of banter and hilarity and also some really good conversations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What a great 2 weeks it has been!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/20/what-a-great-2-weeks-it-has-been/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/20/what-a-great-2-weeks-it-has-been/</guid>
      <description>As I mentioned a while back, I was anticipating a visit from a good old friend from Christchurch, Margaret Haverland. Today she is getting ready to leave, after almost 2 weeks here. What a blast it has been!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three peas in  a pod</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/17/three-peas-in-a-pod/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/17/three-peas-in-a-pod/</guid>
      <description>We recently had our friends Rick and Susanna here for dinner while their two oldest kids were visiting grandparents and when bathtime rolled around we stuck our 3 little blondies in the bath. I just had to share the cuteness!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turning 30</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/08/turning-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/08/turning-30/</guid>
      <description>Last Thursday I (Ben) turned 30, and an otherwise ordinary workday was turned into Something Special by my lovely wife. She’d been being secretive about something for a few weeks, so I guessed something was going to happen, but I had no idea what.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Jeremy eats a mushroom</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/18/how-jeremy-eats-a-mushroom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/18/how-jeremy-eats-a-mushroom/</guid>
      <description>When we were visiting Jeremy in Philly, I made some grilled mushrooms on the barbecue with fresh parmesan, salt, pepper, butter and fresh mozzarella cheese, garnished with a fresh basil leaf. Are your mouths watering yet?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
