<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Books on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/category/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Books on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/category/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Book review: Door to Freedom</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/03/03/book-review-door-to-freedom/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/03/03/book-review-door-to-freedom/</guid>
      <description>Back in 2015, I was given the opportunity to review the book Side by Side by Jana Kelley. It was a realistic and an enjoyable read, which I was excited to hear is turning into a trilogy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Greatest Gift</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/11/14/the-greatest-gift/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/11/14/the-greatest-gift/</guid>
      <description>A couple of years ago, I really enjoyed reading through The Greatest Gift by Ann Voskamp for Advent. This year I’m trying to be organized enough to remind you that if this is something you’d like to buy, now’s a good time, with Advent being just two weeks away and all!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books we’ve read recently</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/24/books-weve-read-recently/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/24/books-weve-read-recently/</guid>
      <description>For your interest, here’s a list of some of the books we’ve read in the last year or so, with a tiny summary of each. Most of them are really good. I’ve put B after the author’s name if only I’ve read it, F if just Franci’s read it, or BF if we’ve both read it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Autobiography of Benjamin Franklin</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/23/the-autobiography-of-benjamin-franklin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/23/the-autobiography-of-benjamin-franklin/</guid>
      <description>Some time ago Franci picked up a little, falling-apart paperback version of The Autobiography of Benjamin Franklin. As well as having a pretty respectable first name, Franklin was a fascinating character in many respects. Was he a printer, a writer, a politician, or an inventor?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caring for Creation</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/02/caring-for-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/02/caring-for-creation/</guid>
      <description>My friend Matthew Bartlett recently started his own publishing company, and his first book is The Biblical Mandate for Caring for Creation by retired New Zealand minister Dick Tripp. The 158-page book, which can be yours for a mere $24.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I stopped reading a classic</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/22/why-i-stopped-reading-a-classic/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/22/why-i-stopped-reading-a-classic/</guid>
      <description>The Brothers Karamazov by Fyodor Dostoyevsky is a classic, or so I’ve heard. It’s one of those books so great and so worth reading that no one you talk to has actually read it.
A 700-page novel is something of a commitment, but I approached this one with an open mind and a daily subway commute.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loving the Little Years</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/07/loving-the-little-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/07/loving-the-little-years/</guid>
      <description>I have recently been reading through Loving the Little Years by Rachel Jankovic. It is GOOD. Every single chapter encourages me and exhorts me and redirects my focus off myself and onto Christ. Off what other people think and onto Christ.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What we’re doing and reading</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/28/what-were-doing-and-reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/28/what-were-doing-and-reading/</guid>
      <description>Last night I had an audition for the Brooklyn Conservatory Chorale. I’ve been thinking for a while that I’d like to do some music again, but because we don’t have a piano and I decided not to bring my violin, it has to be singing which I thankfully enjoy doing very much!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My new book</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/07/my-new-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/07/my-new-book/</guid>
      <description>My lovely husband has recently bought me Julia Child’s Mastering the Art of French Cooking. I have read the preface and all the introductory remarks. Now I need to start cooking from it. It’s just been so hot that cooking anything that isn’t a hamburger patty is not very appealing, even if it is French.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
