<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Updates on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/category/updates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Updates on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/category/updates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Reviving a neglected blog</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2019/01/09/reviving-a-neglected-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2019/01/09/reviving-a-neglected-blog/</guid>
      <description>There are times when certain things in life need to take a bit of a break, and this blog was one of them this past year. I’ve always enjoyed writing on here, but it had become just another thing I felt I had to do, and so I made the decision to just give it up for a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time travel into the past: July 2017</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2018/03/14/time-travel-into-the-past-july-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2018/03/14/time-travel-into-the-past-july-2017/</guid>
      <description>Life’s been happening by the spade full around here, and blogging has been severely neglected, sorry. Here’s an attempt at rectifying that!
Back in July last year… hmmm, let’s see if the photos can remind me that far back!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A little time travel into the past: March</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/08/25/a-little-time-travel-into-the-past-march/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/08/25/a-little-time-travel-into-the-past-march/</guid>
      <description>There used to be a time I blogged several times a week. Then it turned into twice a week, then once a week, then once every two weeks, then… whenever I happen to write a blog post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General update</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/07/28/general-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/07/28/general-update/</guid>
      <description>An update written by Ben for a change. After all, Franci has written almost all of the posts on this blog. As it happens, the last one Ben wrote was almost a year ago.
Ben is busy with various things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rambling thoughts</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/02/22/rambling-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/02/22/rambling-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>The year starts off differently here in the northern hemisphere compared to the southern hemisphere. In some ways it doesn’t really feel like a new year — school and work just keeps going after a short break for Christmas; whereas in NZ just about nothing happens the first few weeks of January because 90% of the country is off somewhere on holiday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The job front</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/08/12/the-job-front/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/08/12/the-job-front/</guid>
      <description>In the last couple of months I’ve had a bit of a change job-wise (Franci said it was about time for me to write). I had been a software engineer for Oyster.com — now part of TripAdvisor — for just over six years, and decided it was time for a change and some new work experience while we’re here in the States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random thoughts</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/06/10/random-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/06/10/random-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>The last couple of months have looked a little different to our usual routines. I’ve had a relapse of the Epstein-Barr virus which wiped me out but I seem to be feeling a fair bit better the last week or so; Ben’s been looking at different job options and has had multiple interviews with several different companies (no decision yet, though).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The new GiftyWeddings.com</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/04/06/the-new-giftyweddings-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/04/06/the-new-giftyweddings-com/</guid>
      <description>Most of you know that I (this is Ben posting for a change) run a little wedding gift registry website called GiftyWeddings.com. It’s been going for almost eight years now, helping several couples every month create nice simple gift registries that aren’t tied to a particular store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changing things around</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/05/08/changing-things-around/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/05/08/changing-things-around/</guid>
      <description>You’ll probably have noticed that I’ve been playing around with new blog designs. And you’ll probably also be relieved to know that I’m done now, and that this is what the site will look like for the foreseeable future!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/11/28/thanksgiving-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/11/28/thanksgiving-2/</guid>
      <description>Here in the States, people celebrated Thanksgiving yesterday. We’re actually celebrating it today, so that it could work out for Jeremy and Lillian to be here with us.
So, for that reason, and because there’s cooking to be done, I’ll keep this short and leave you with the lyrics of a hymn whose tune I dislike, but that has powerful words.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer fun</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/09/12/summer-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/09/12/summer-fun/</guid>
      <description>The summer is coming to an end, and we are back in the full swing of homeschooling. We took a nice long summer break. I had great intentions of schooling through the summer, but somehow as it warmed up outside we all just lost steam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A bonus Laurelin feature</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/07/15/a-bonus-laurelin-feature/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/07/15/a-bonus-laurelin-feature/</guid>
      <description>This post is specially for grandparents, aunties and other such doting people who would be interested in these videos of our little Lorax.
Marica loves to play rough and tumble with Laurelin, but she’s very careful not to be too rough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A general update. About time too</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/06/06/a-general-update-about-time-too/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/06/06/a-general-update-about-time-too/</guid>
      <description>Three weeks ago, Laurelin turned one. I started writing a post the week before her birthday and got about two paragraphs in. Life is a bit like that at the moment — some people have hinted or asked directly if we will post regularly again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We’ve moved in!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/04/05/weve-moved-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/04/05/weve-moved-in/</guid>
      <description>Just a quick note to let you all know that we’ve moved into our new apartment where we hope to be for the next year (or more) in Jersey City Heights. We moved in on Monday and it’s been a bit of a shambles around here that is slowly turning into order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another birthday</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/03/27/another-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/03/27/another-birthday/</guid>
      <description>Last week, I celebrated another birthday. The last one of my 20’s. Marica very tactfully said, “Mum, it’s good that you’re not turning 30. Thirty is too old for a woman!”
Ben took the morning off so that we could go to the MVC to get our New Jersey driver’s licences, but the unfortunately the proof of address we took along was not good enough in their books, so we had to leave without the licences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Aliens are back in the Apple</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/02/26/the-aliens-are-back-in-the-apple/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/02/26/the-aliens-are-back-in-the-apple/</guid>
      <description>After two long, but pretty good flights, we’re back in New York. If you told me a year ago that I’d be here now, I would have laughed and said, “Yeah, right!” But here we are after a few whirlwind weeks of getting ready to move.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going, going, (almost) gone!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/02/19/going-going-almost-gone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/02/19/going-going-almost-gone/</guid>
      <description>We’re on our way to the States: our house is under offer, we’ve traveled to Auckland and have had our Green Cards approved, and tomorrow, Lord willing, we fly out to New York.
The last few weeks have been a super busy time, and a bit of an emotional roller coaster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gearing up to go</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/02/10/gearing-up-to-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/02/10/gearing-up-to-go/</guid>
      <description>The last few weeks have gotten exponentially busier as we’re getting ready for our move back to the States. It is strange how something can feel so unreal even in the midst of the busyness. I have days where it’s almost a surprise to me when people ask when we’re leaving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flights booked, date set!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/01/25/flights-booked-date-set/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/01/25/flights-booked-date-set/</guid>
      <description>We started this blog almost four years ago with the words “so we’re going overseas in a month”. They do say history repeats itself…
About six months ago, Ben got a job offer with TripAdvisor who was hoping to acquire Oyster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A weekend visit to Oamaru</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/01/07/a-weekend-visit-to-oamaru/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/01/07/a-weekend-visit-to-oamaru/</guid>
      <description>The last weekend of last year we made the three hour drive down to Oamaru to visit Mum and Dad Hoyt. We always love visiting them! This time around Bevan and Elrike were there with us, and the girls had a great time playing together in a different setting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doing a bit of catch up</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/11/24/doing-a-bit-of-catch-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/11/24/doing-a-bit-of-catch-up/</guid>
      <description>To catch up some of what we’ve been up to over the last year or so, I thought I’d just share some photos of life around here for the last few months of last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What a lovely excuse!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/07/20/what-a-lovely-excuse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/07/20/what-a-lovely-excuse/</guid>
      <description>I’m such a regular blogger, I have to tick the ‘Remember Me’ box every time I log in to the blog! I had high hopes of finishing the road trip blog posts before the baby arrived, but things got in the way (just minor things like a pregnancy, a hospital stay and the like)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why the blog has been rather neglected</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/11/26/why-the-blog-has-been-rather-neglected/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/11/26/why-the-blog-has-been-rather-neglected/</guid>
      <description>Those of you who have been following the blog for any time over the last 2.5 years or so will have noticed that there has been a marked drop in the frequency of posts here. The reason for that has partly been that coming back to New Zealand has made life busier in many ways and that the time to blog has diminished.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I’m in denial</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/07/06/im-in-denial/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/07/06/im-in-denial/</guid>
      <description>Two days ago, I was sitting on my bed editing some photos in Picasa, having just cleared my camera memory stick of about 500 more photos and video clips. The total number of photos taken on our roadtrip so far were well over a thousand and I was doing well keeping up to date with deleting the bad ones, editing the ones that needed a bit of lightening or the like, even if I haven’t been the greatest at updating the blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Packing up, cleaning out, giving away, selling…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/24/packing-up-cleaning-out-giving-away-selling/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/24/packing-up-cleaning-out-giving-away-selling/</guid>
      <description>That’s what I’m doing a lot of at the moment. And I’m seriously worried about this 4 suitcase limit. I’m just praying that our rental car can fit more than that because just our family’s clothing takes up 3 suitcases!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We’re back!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/09/were-back-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/09/were-back-2/</guid>
      <description>The girls and I arrived safely back in New York City on Monday night after three flights over 26 hours. We had a fantastic time back in New Zealand reconnecting with friends and family and enjoying Jeremy and Lillian’s wedding, but we’re very happy to be home with Ben again!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We survived Irene</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/28/we-survived-irene/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/28/we-survived-irene/</guid>
      <description>We’re posting this from a rescue boat (with free wireless internet) that lifted us from the roof of our flooded apartment early this morning. We’re sipping complimentary cocktails as we traverse the streets by boat, witnessing how New York has turned into a lake full of broken branches and leaves, a veritable Venice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When the summer gives you heat…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/10/when-the-summer-gives-you-heat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/10/when-the-summer-gives-you-heat/</guid>
      <description>eat popsicles!
It’s so delicious you have to let your arm and chin taste some too.
It hurts when you bite cold stuff with your teeth!
Look, Mum, a plane! (Depending on the wind direction, we get them coming over every 2 minutes or so to land at JFK.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A quiet Saturday morning</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/06/a-quiet-saturday-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/06/a-quiet-saturday-morning/</guid>
      <description>It’s quiet because I’m home alone, which is a rare event indeed! Ben took the girls to Prospect Park this morning and I have some time to myself here at home. Guess what I’ve chosen to spend my time doing?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy hammocking</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/01/happy-hammocking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/01/happy-hammocking/</guid>
      <description>Hammocking is a verb, didn’t you know? It does not involve mocking ham. Ham is too good to mock.
Enjoying some mum-and-daughter time in the hammock a while back when we were at Jeremy’s place in Philadelphia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A matter of the heart</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/29/a-matter-of-the-heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/29/a-matter-of-the-heart/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been thinking about all sorts of matters relating to the heart — it’s interesting that we describe both things emotional and spiritual with the metaphor of the heart. “His heart is not in the right place”, “she’s lost heart”, “guard your heart”.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
