<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kids on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/category/kids/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kids on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/category/kids/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Time travel into the past: July 2017</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2018/03/14/time-travel-into-the-past-july-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2018/03/14/time-travel-into-the-past-july-2017/</guid>
      <description>Life’s been happening by the spade full around here, and blogging has been severely neglected, sorry. Here’s an attempt at rectifying that!
Back in July last year… hmmm, let’s see if the photos can remind me that far back!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A cool video Marica made</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2018/02/12/a-cool-video-marica-made/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2018/02/12/a-cool-video-marica-made/</guid>
      <description>Marica has been taking photos of everyday beauty (mostly during our time in NZ), editing them, and has turned them into a nice little video, which I’d like to share with you below. Proud Mama moment!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three little flower girls</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/05/09/three-little-flower-girls/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/05/09/three-little-flower-girls/</guid>
      <description>Back in February our 3 girls got to be flower girls for a lovely couple in our church, Kelvin and Joanna. It was a beautiful day — unseasonably warm for February basically the whole week leading up to the wedding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A decade old!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/05/02/a-decade-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/05/02/a-decade-old/</guid>
      <description>In February, Marica turned 10. TEN?? How does a decade go by so fast? Marica is growing up — both taller and also growing in maturity little by little. Or maybe not so little! Her independence in the kitchen is growing, and she’s becoming quite the cook and baker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurelin’s 3rd birthday</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/08/26/laurelins-3rd-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/08/26/laurelins-3rd-birthday/</guid>
      <description>In all the bustle of the end of the school year and then summer vacation, I’ve neglected to post photos of Laurelin’s 3rd birthday.
Laurelin is now a full-blown 3-year-old and no push-over, in every sense of the word.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marica’s 9th birthday</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/03/11/maricas-9th-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/03/11/maricas-9th-birthday/</guid>
      <description>My oldest turned 9 last month. Where did the time go? I know all mothers always say that, but my oh my, they grow up fast. Gone is the little girl who liked her hair braided all pretty, and who would wear whatever her mother put out for her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips on travelling long-haul with little kids</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/12/11/tips-on-travelling-long-haul-with-little-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/12/11/tips-on-travelling-long-haul-with-little-kids/</guid>
      <description>As we prepare to take a trip back to NZ for Christmas, I’m looking back at this post again (originally posted in March 2012) to refresh my memory on what’s useful to take and what to do to make life easier when travelling long haul with kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple picking day</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/12/04/apple-picking-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/12/04/apple-picking-day/</guid>
      <description>On a lovely warm day back in October, the girls and I took a field trip to a farm about an hour’s drive from where we live to go apple and pumpkin picking. The weather was fantastic — it was nice and sunny and not too hot or cold, a real Goldilocks kind of day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Esther’s 6th birthday</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/11/27/esthers-6th-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/11/27/esthers-6th-birthday/</guid>
      <description>Esther turned 6 in November. Hard to believe, isn’t it?! Her birthday celebrations were spread out over two days — on Friday at co-op the kids sang Happy Birthday to her and she and Marica handed out cupcakes that Marica had baked (no, Mum, you’re not allowed to help me!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful autumn</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/11/20/beautiful-autumn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/11/20/beautiful-autumn/</guid>
      <description>I have a love-hate relationship with autumn. I love all the beautiful colors, the cooler weather and the fun things the season brings like apples, cinnamon, pumpkin pie and hot chocolate. But… autumn is the start of a long cold spell that only keeps getting worse for about 5 months before it starts getting better!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What we’re doing in homeschooling this year</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/11/13/what-were-doing-in-homeschooling-this-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/11/13/what-were-doing-in-homeschooling-this-year/</guid>
      <description>We’ve been back in the full swing of the regular school year for a few months now, and I must admit that I find it hard to make the time to blog. It’s great to have the routines of school, but it does leave very little time for extra things, like blogging and other fun stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marica’s newest yummy dish</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/10/30/maricas-newest-yummy-dish/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/10/30/maricas-newest-yummy-dish/</guid>
      <description>Marica recently got a cookbook out of the library and was looking through it one afternoon. She came to me and said, “I’m going to make Stromboli, and I don’t want you to help me.” Sure!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A summary of summer, part 3</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/09/19/a-summary-of-summer-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/09/19/a-summary-of-summer-part-3/</guid>
      <description>August was filled to the brim with activity. We said goodbye to our Chinese exchange students, and celebrated Ben’s birthday.
We swam a few times in our friend’s nearby pool, but also did a fun day trip out to go swim at a water hole our friend Sarah knows about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A summary of summer, part 2</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/09/11/a-summary-of-summer-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/09/11/a-summary-of-summer-part-2/</guid>
      <description>A summary of summer, continued.
In July, we hosted the Holtslags, our pastor from NZ and his family, as well as James and Laura (James is Phillipa’s son, Laura is the Holtslags’ daughter). This time we sent them off to do sight-seeing by themselves, but we still got to have some good conversations over the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April Fool’s Dinner</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/04/03/april-fools-dinner/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/04/03/april-fools-dinner/</guid>
      <description>A few years back, on a whim, I decided to start a fun tradition for April Fool’s Day dinner: dessert for dinner (and no need to have dinner for dessert!). Turns out the kids think this is great, but the adults give a little groan at the thought.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>She’s 8!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/03/13/beautiful-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/03/13/beautiful-snow/</guid>
      <description>Marica turned 8 in February. It’s been so fun to see her grow up a bit more over the last year! I’ve especially enjoyed seeing her sense of humor develop a bit more (starting to understand and appreciate puns and subtleties), and to see her get a little bit more mature and responsible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Medieval Feast</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/03/06/a-medieval-feast/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/03/06/a-medieval-feast/</guid>
      <description>Back in January, the homeschool co-op we attend put on a Medieval Feast. The organizers did a most spectacular job with the decorations, food and everything else that goes into organizing a big event like this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You can’t see me!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/02/20/you-cant-see-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/02/20/you-cant-see-me/</guid>
      <description>At lunch the other day, Laurelin was playing peek-a-boo with her bib, which was hilariously cute, because she’d stare out the neck hole at us thinking she was invisible!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Entrepreneurial Fair</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/09/the-entrepreneurial-fair/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/09/the-entrepreneurial-fair/</guid>
      <description>The Co-op that we attend had an Entrepreneurial Fair early in December, and as much as I would have liked to just be a spectator, my kids were burning to sell stuff (surprise, surprise). So, we made Christmas ornaments, some chocolates and gingerbread men.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autumn baby</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/02/autumn-baby-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/01/02/autumn-baby-2/</guid>
      <description>For our November Frog Pond class, I went a little click-happy with Laurelin while the older girls were busy. She was in a particularly good mood and I was able to get quite a few happy shots of her outside, enjoying the leaves and dirt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Esther’s 5th birthday</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/12/12/esthers-5th-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/12/12/esthers-5th-birthday/</guid>
      <description>It is hard to believe that my little baby Esther…
has grown into a big FIVE year old. How did that happen??
Well, in early November we celebrated her 5th birthday with much less fanfare than I had hoped and planned due to a bunch of us getting super nasty colds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In lieu of Halloween</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/12/05/in-lieu-of-halloween/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/12/05/in-lieu-of-halloween/</guid>
      <description>This year, instead of celebrating Halloween, which is such a massive deal here in the States and which we don’t feel particularly comfortable with joining in on for various reasons, we decided to do things a little differently and have a Fall Party with our good friends, Alfredo and Damaris and their kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some nice things</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/31/some-nice-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/31/some-nice-things/</guid>
      <description>I like autumn. It’s not so hot, there are pretty colors everywhere, and the change of season brings all sorts of nice things like warm slippers and hot drinks, nice decorations and good smelling candles, and fun kids’ crafts…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If your daughter asks you for french toast…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/24/if-your-daughter-asks-you-for-french-toast/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/24/if-your-daughter-asks-you-for-french-toast/</guid>
      <description>If your daughter asks you for French toast, then you’ll be tempted to just say ‘no’. It’s a weekday, after all. But then you’ll remember that you want to be more of a ‘yes’ parent than a ‘no’ parent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marica the entrepreneur</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/13/marica-the-entrepreneur/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/10/13/marica-the-entrepreneur/</guid>
      <description>When Marica was 4, I got a fancy new camera as a very generous gift. Marica then got our old camera, which was a little point and shoot that was on its way out but still in good condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer fun</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/09/12/summer-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/09/12/summer-fun/</guid>
      <description>The summer is coming to an end, and we are back in the full swing of homeschooling. We took a nice long summer break. I had great intentions of schooling through the summer, but somehow as it warmed up outside we all just lost steam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enthralled by the TV</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/29/enthralled-by-the-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/29/enthralled-by-the-tv/</guid>
      <description>My computer desk is just next to the couch, and one day while I was doing things on the computer and the girls were watching a show, I looked over and just had to quickly snap a picture of the girls enjoying it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The squishy baby with the hair</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/22/the-squishy-baby-with-the-hair/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/22/the-squishy-baby-with-the-hair/</guid>
      <description>Laurelin Grace,
you have a sweet face,
I love your squishy fatness
to cuddle and to kiss,
But what makes me fondly stare
is your light, unruly hair!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miss Communication</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/19/miss-communication/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/19/miss-communication/</guid>
      <description>I was folding washing this morning listening to Marica and Esther talk, and just had to share this funny:
E: “Mawica, dose are nithe octoputheth.”
M: “They aren’t octopuses, they’re decorations!
E: “Dey look like octoputheth…”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun day at the Fair</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/15/fun-day-at-the-fair/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/15/fun-day-at-the-fair/</guid>
      <description>On the first weekend of July we took the kids to the Meadowlands State Fair which is pretty close to where we live. The kids were giddy with excitement!
We got there as soon as it opened in the afternoon so it wouldn’t be too busy, and that was a good idea because there weren’t many lines to wait in, but everything got progressively busier during the late afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marica’s recital at Steinway Hall</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/07/18/maricas-recital-at-steinway-hall/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/07/18/maricas-recital-at-steinway-hall/</guid>
      <description>Marica and Esther started piano lessons the week after our piano arrived, and have both been enjoying it a lot, no doubt because of their excellent teacher (who also happens to be our friend!), Shannon Murphy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A bonus Laurelin feature</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/07/15/a-bonus-laurelin-feature/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/07/15/a-bonus-laurelin-feature/</guid>
      <description>This post is specially for grandparents, aunties and other such doting people who would be interested in these videos of our little Lorax.
Marica loves to play rough and tumble with Laurelin, but she’s very careful not to be too rough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reaga</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/07/11/reaga/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/07/11/reaga/</guid>
      <description>Reaga is a mix between reading and yoga. Marica has invented it without even knowing!
The other day I was sitting at the computer doing stuff when I saw something out of the corner of my eye that didn’t look quite right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pretty little gift</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/07/04/pretty-little-gift/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/07/04/pretty-little-gift/</guid>
      <description>Where we live now, we have no garden, which is a bit of a shame. The other day, though, we were outside and the girls were riding their bikes on the sidewalk when Esther brought these little flowers to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurelin’s first birthday</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/06/13/laurelins-first-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/06/13/laurelins-first-birthday/</guid>
      <description>Three weeks ago, Laurelin turned 1. Crazy stuff, how did that happen?
We had a really low-key day, church in the morning, and then a little party with our lovely friends Alfredo and Damaris and their kids (whom I didn’t get a good photo of, sorry!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A general update. About time too</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/06/06/a-general-update-about-time-too/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/06/06/a-general-update-about-time-too/</guid>
      <description>Three weeks ago, Laurelin turned one. I started writing a post the week before her birthday and got about two paragraphs in. Life is a bit like that at the moment — some people have hinted or asked directly if we will post regularly again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr Rubik’s back</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/05/08/mr-rubiks-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/05/08/mr-rubiks-back/</guid>
      <description>Marica and I went to the Liberty Science Center in Jersey City last Saturday to see their new Rubik’s Cube exhibition, which was being opened by Ernő Rubik, the inventor of the cube. I own a cube, but still have no idea how to solve it…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Woody’s disgrace</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/04/28/woodys-disgrace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/04/28/woodys-disgrace/</guid>
      <description>The other day I found this:
It just tickled my funny bone that Esther would dress Woody in a dress! Despite the brave face he’s putting on, he’s secretly mortified.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Peach Fuzz</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/03/14/little-peach-fuzz/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/03/14/little-peach-fuzz/</guid>
      <description>It’s so much fun to have a baby in the house! (Especially now that I’m getting more sleep.)
Laurelin is the cause of many laughs, hugs and smiles.
Her sisters dote on her (and so do her parents!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life in limbo</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/03/10/life-in-limbo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/03/10/life-in-limbo/</guid>
      <description>Since the last time I posted, we’ve moved into our temporary apartment for the month of March, settled into a daily routine with homeschooling in the mornings, and all of us have gotten sick. New climate, new bugs — it was to be expected!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Look how she’s grown!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/12/25/look-how-shes-grown/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/12/25/look-how-shes-grown/</guid>
      <description>Laurelin at 2 weeks.
At 3 months.
At 7 months.
From the 2.2kg baby we brought home to a nice solid 7kg-ish almost-crawler. We’re so thankful for our happy, healthy, smiley Laurelin Grace!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The empty pair of trousers</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/12/04/the-empty-pair-of-trousers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2013/12/04/the-empty-pair-of-trousers/</guid>
      <description>Esther walked past my study this morning and said, “Dad, I see you in your office, but there’s nothing inside your pants!” Almost certainly thinking of this Dr Seuss book, here’s what she had seen:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helping to push</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/18/helping-to-push/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/18/helping-to-push/</guid>
      <description>We were having a picnic in Prospect Park when Lizel was here and there was this man doing his stretches against a tree.
We joked with the kids that the man was trying to push over the tree, and do they want to go and help him?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Special time with Pappa</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/24/special-time-with-pappa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/24/special-time-with-pappa/</guid>
      <description>I think the Pennsylvanian countryside is just so beautiful. It seems very peaceful to me, perhaps because I’m usually on holiday when I’m there.
When we took Lizel there when she visited, Marica stayed with dear friends who took her to a ballet concert, so Esther got to be the only child for a weekend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My daddy is stronger than your daddy</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/16/my-daddy-is-stronger-than-your-daddy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/16/my-daddy-is-stronger-than-your-daddy/</guid>
      <description>I know I’m thoroughly biased, but this photo just melts my heart. Our girls sure are blessed to have such a wonderful daddy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adventures with hippos</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/12/adventures-with-hippos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/04/12/adventures-with-hippos/</guid>
      <description>In Central Park there is this cool playground that has a herd of hippos made out of fibre glass (?? I guess). The kids always think it’s fun to pretend to ride the hippos.
So do some of the adults.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Because we’re so normal</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/15/because-were-so-normal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/15/because-were-so-normal/</guid>
      <description>We sometimes have dinner wearing cabbage leaf hats.
(Well, only if I’m making coleslaw to go with our pulled pork and need to get rid of some cabbage leaves!)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marica turned 5</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/12/marica-turned-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/03/12/marica-turned-5/</guid>
      <description>How is it that they go from this…
to this…
so unbelievably fast?
Too fast, that’s what. I’m sure someone’s been speeding up the time.
Marica turned 5 in February, but when we were in New Zealand, my mum (Ouma to the kids) threw a birthday party for Marica.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More wedding pictures</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/16/more-wedding-pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/02/16/more-wedding-pictures/</guid>
      <description>Well, I said I’d share some more wedding pictures when I got some time to get them on here. I didn’t get the time, but I made the time, so here they are.
The first lot of photos were taken outside in the harsh sunlight (always a bad move), so unfortunately everyone has sunglass shadows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black and white, day 11</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/26/black-and-white-day-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/26/black-and-white-day-11/</guid>
      <description>Opposite hair day. October 2011.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This little piggy</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/03/this-little-piggy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/01/03/this-little-piggy/</guid>
      <description>A black and white shot of Esther’s little feet, shortly before her 2nd birthday.
Happy New Year, everyone! We hope that the new year will be a blessed one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gingerbread House fun</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/22/gingerbread-house-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/22/gingerbread-house-fun/</guid>
      <description>Our much loved pastor’s wife, Julie, invited a few moms over to her house last Friday to make gingerbread houses. What a total blast! We made the houses out of graham crackers instead of baked sheets of gingerbread, which was much easier and less time consuming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Christmas craft afternoon</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/20/a-christmas-craft-afternoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/20/a-christmas-craft-afternoon/</guid>
      <description>On an unseasonably warm Saturday late in November, a few women from our church gathered at our friend Jen’s house to make some Christmas crafts. It was bliss… lots of good chatting and food while being enjoyably creative and productive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lovely hair</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/17/lovely-hair/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/17/lovely-hair/</guid>
      <description>A while back we girls had a fun afternoon of doing each other’s hair. I made Marica’s hair into a triple braid.
She was studiously doing her schoolwork while I took photos of her hair!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent is here!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/10/advent-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/10/advent-is-here/</guid>
      <description>I started the blog post draft a few weeks back, and now the season of Advent is about halfway through. Last year we decided to start celebrating Advent in a more deliberate way, building the excitement until Christmas, and enjoying the anticipation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting into the homeschooling groove</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/05/getting-into-the-homeschooling-groove/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/05/getting-into-the-homeschooling-groove/</guid>
      <description>Since Marica started preschool two days a week last year, I have been doing some casual schoolwork with her at home. When the school year finished and we decided to school her at home rather than send her to yet another school, we started making ‘school work’ more of a part of our daily routine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Esther’s turned two!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/01/esthers-turned-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/01/esthers-turned-two/</guid>
      <description>I was going to start by saying that Esther turned two just last week. But then I realised that it would almost be more accurate to say she turned two just last month. Sometimes I feel disoriented with how fast time goes — my head is still two weeks ago and my body, by default, is here and now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If looks could kill…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/14/if-looks-could-kill/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/14/if-looks-could-kill/</guid>
      <description>then this cheeky face kills me with laughter almost every time I see it.
Figuratively, of course.
She was putting on her pretend grouchy face, only to dissolve into giggles herself!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October, a wonderful month with family</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/03/october-a-wonderful-month-with-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/03/october-a-wonderful-month-with-family/</guid>
      <description>For most of the month of October we had my parents visiting with us, and we had a very good time together.
The highlight of their time here was probably our road trip that we took to the Adirondack mountains, Niagara Falls, Toronto and Pennsylvania to visit our friends the Tysons and the Braunings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Baltimore hotel window view</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/04/a-baltimore-hotel-window-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/04/a-baltimore-hotel-window-view/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been just a little bit busy lately, preparing for another roadtrip (yay!), this time with my parents (double yay!) who should have arrived in San Francisco by now. I hope. I realised I never gave my parents my contact details here in the States before they left.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking kids on a photo shoot can be interesting</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/03/taking-kids-on-a-photo-shoot-can-be-interesting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/03/taking-kids-on-a-photo-shoot-can-be-interesting/</guid>
      <description>And also pretty fun.
Perhaps “photo shoot” is too formal a title for what we did with Jeremy and Lillian, but I still tried to get a heap of photos while at the same time trying to keep an eye on two speedy escape artists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby loves babies</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/21/baby-loves-babies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/21/baby-loves-babies/</guid>
      <description>Ever since Esther has been able to cuddle dolls, she has been a little ‘mother’ to her dolls (when she isn’t destroying them by writing all over them!). It’s rather cute to see her personality come out in this way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three peas in  a pod</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/17/three-peas-in-a-pod/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/17/three-peas-in-a-pod/</guid>
      <description>We recently had our friends Rick and Susanna here for dinner while their two oldest kids were visiting grandparents and when bathtime rolled around we stuck our 3 little blondies in the bath. I just had to share the cuteness!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When the summer gives you heat…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/10/when-the-summer-gives-you-heat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/08/10/when-the-summer-gives-you-heat/</guid>
      <description>eat popsicles!
It’s so delicious you have to let your arm and chin taste some too.
It hurts when you bite cold stuff with your teeth!
Look, Mum, a plane! (Depending on the wind direction, we get them coming over every 2 minutes or so to land at JFK.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How high do your kids rank?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/27/how-high-do-your-kids-rank/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/27/how-high-do-your-kids-rank/</guid>
      <description>Another excellent article from Rachel Jankovic. A good look at how society views children, where your children rank in your priorities, and the calling of motherhood. I encourage you to go read it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to Mr. J</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/15/visit-to-mr-j/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/15/visit-to-mr-j/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weekends ago, we visited our good friend, Jeremy, in Philadelphia.
What a blast — we did some sight-seeing, but also my favourite pastime: having good discussions over good food.
There was of course also an appropriate amount of teasing which Jeremy thrived upon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful encouragement for the mothers among us</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/29/beautiful-encouragement-for-the-mothers-among-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/29/beautiful-encouragement-for-the-mothers-among-us/</guid>
      <description>One of my favourite authors and bloggers (I’ve raved about her before) was invited by Desiring God ministries to write an article for them. I found it very encouraging and helpful, and I hope all the mothers who visit this blog will read this article — you will not be sorry!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glimpses into the last couple of weeks</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/27/glimpses-into-the-last-couple-of-weeks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/27/glimpses-into-the-last-couple-of-weeks/</guid>
      <description>I don’t know why the weeks go by so fast. I have a bunch of photos to share with you from when Ben’s cousin Sharon visited us a month ago, our trip to Connecticut 2 weeks ago and our trip to visit Jeremy in Philadelphia last weekend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer is here!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/16/summer-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/16/summer-is-here/</guid>
      <description>And we’ve well and truly been out and about enjoying it. We’ve only had two very hot days and for the rest of the time it has been pretty much perfect weather (25 - 30 C).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did I tell you that Esther is now walking?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/03/did-i-tell-you-that-esther-is-now-walking/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/03/did-i-tell-you-that-esther-is-now-walking/</guid>
      <description>Well, she certainly is. And she’s fast too. She’s loving the new independence and so am I. Playgrounds are much more fun, despite the scratched knees she inevitably gets!
Walking down Fulton Street. That big tower in the background under construction is the new One World Trade Center.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheeky grin</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/31/cheeky-grin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/31/cheeky-grin/</guid>
      <description>This girly has some awesome facial expressions. This is one of them. :-)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marica the soccer player</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/19/marica-the-soccer-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/19/marica-the-soccer-player/</guid>
      <description>Friends of ours recently invited Marica to join a little informal ‘soccer’ team that will practice just until the start of the summer. Marica has loved her Saturday morning soccer practices and all the games the coach lets them play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Long-distance running inside our apartment</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/16/long-distance-running-inside-our-apartment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/16/long-distance-running-inside-our-apartment/</guid>
      <description>The other day Marica decided to start running laps between our bed and the couch in the lounge, a distance of about six or seven metres. After a few laps she started counting, “1, 2, 3, 4 …” Soon I took over the counting, “14, 15, 16, see if you can get up to 20 …”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Up to no good</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/12/up-to-no-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/12/up-to-no-good/</guid>
      <description>Esther’s fine motor skills are very well developed, at least when it comes to opening things. Somehow she managed to open the coffee packet the other day and spill grounds all over the floor. But then you see that expression and how can’t you laugh?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About servants and serving</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/07/about-servants/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/07/about-servants/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been thinking about my job (as a mother) a fair bit recently. After Monday’s blog post, I felt that I might have given the wrong impression of what life around here looks like. I have a policy (with myself) not to complain or whine on this blog — not about big city life and not about my family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How not to praise your kids</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/14/how-not-to-praise-your-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/14/how-not-to-praise-your-kids/</guid>
      <description>I just finished reading an online article by New York Magazine, How not to talk to your kids. It talked about a lot of research that has been done over the last few years about the effects of praise on children’s performance — how not to praise your kids’ intelligence, but their efforts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Barbie is a big deal</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/24/why-barbie-is-a-big-deal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/24/why-barbie-is-a-big-deal/</guid>
      <description>Today’s post goes out on a limb a bit. It’s probably going to be controversial and many of you won’t agree with me, but these are some thoughts that have been swirling around in my mind for many months, and that some of you might find beneficial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marica’s self-photography</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/16/maricas-self-photography/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/16/maricas-self-photography/</guid>
      <description>Just a little something that I hope you find as funny as I did!
A post explaining the make-up on the eyes is coming soon…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cute kids’ photos</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/28/cute-kids-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/28/cute-kids-photos/</guid>
      <description>While Ben and I were having a blast in the Caribbean, our kids were having a blast at the Murphys’ place. Julie was kind enough to send me some pictures, so I’ll share them here for you to enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marica is 4!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/16/marica-is-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/16/marica-is-4/</guid>
      <description>On Saturday, Marica turned 4 years old. I find that hard to believe that it’s already been 4 years since she was born. And at the same time it feels as if she’s been my big girl forever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A joyful glimpse</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/11/a-joyful-glimpse/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/11/a-joyful-glimpse/</guid>
      <description>I just wanted to share a little moment in our life here, because it’s moments like these that make me so happy and thankful for the gift of being able to be a mother at home with my kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loving the Little Years</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/07/loving-the-little-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/07/loving-the-little-years/</guid>
      <description>I have recently been reading through Loving the Little Years by Rachel Jankovic. It is GOOD. Every single chapter encourages me and exhorts me and redirects my focus off myself and onto Christ. Off what other people think and onto Christ.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who left the toilet open this time?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/04/who-left-the-toilet-open-this-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/04/who-left-the-toilet-open-this-time/</guid>
      <description>I recently discovered Esther in the act of playing with her favourite toy again. She was in her element, and had even put a washcloth and some bath toys in there too. She even washed herself with the washcloth, as you can see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting creative with snow</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/02/getting-creative-with-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/02/getting-creative-with-snow/</guid>
      <description>We’ve had a lot of snow here this winter, and today we’ve got snow and ice rain again! Well, life carries on about as normally as it can and we try to get out when we can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sally Henny Penny</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/28/sally-henny-penny/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/28/sally-henny-penny/</guid>
      <description>Those of you familiar with Beatrix Potter’s stories would appreciate this picture of our very own Sally Henny Penny wearing her yellow stockings. Very soon she will be going barefoot barefoot barefoot!
And no, we hadn’t brushed her hair yet!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A visit to Wonderland</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/21/a-visit-to-wonderland/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/21/a-visit-to-wonderland/</guid>
      <description>Last Friday, a few friends from church met up at Alice’s Tea Cup with their daughters for a fun, girly time of drinking tea, eating good food and some good conversation.
Alice’s Tea Cup is definitely a girly tea room, decorated in pretty colours with cool chandeliers and fairy wings on the walls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Chocolate Monkster</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/13/the-chocolate-monkster/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/13/the-chocolate-monkster/</guid>
      <description>Since turning one, Esther has been introduced to the wonders of chocolate. She loves that stuff with a passion!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The penny queen</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/11/the-penny-queen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/11/the-penny-queen/</guid>
      <description>Marica must have either Dutch or Jewish blood in her. She’s always scouting to find coins on the ground, and the number she has picked up is astounding. Here’s one day’s laundromat loot: a quarter and a penny.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our first New York Christmas</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/30/our-first-new-york-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/30/our-first-new-york-christmas/</guid>
      <description>This year was the first year our little family did not celebrate Christmas with grandparents. I was going to say that we didn’t celebrate with any extended family, but we do have Lillian here, so we’re not entirely family-less!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/22/thanksgiving/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/22/thanksgiving/</guid>
      <description>This week on Thursday it is Thanksgiving. I think it must be my favourite American holiday! A life that is full of thanksgiving is a happy one, no matter what the circumstances, and what can be better than once a year celebrating the good things God has given us with a great big feast?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More cereal box fun</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/18/more-cereal-box-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/18/more-cereal-box-fun/</guid>
      <description>When we looked for ideas for what kinds of crafts one can make with cereal boxes, back when we made Glitter Girl, we also came across a cute idea of making sandals. I promised Marica we’d do that, and here’s the result.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Through Marica’s eyes</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/17/through-maricas-eyes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/17/through-maricas-eyes/</guid>
      <description>Marica absolutely loves being allowed to use the camera to take photos. And I always have a chuckle when I download them and see just what caught her eye. Let’s just say that she has a realistic view and she takes pictures of it — she won’t avoid the messy room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snug as a bug…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/16/snug-as-a-bug/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/16/snug-as-a-bug/</guid>
      <description>in a front-pack on Pappa. Now if those silly teeth will just stop bothering me…
This cutie has cut a molar, even though she hasn’t even cut all her front teeth yet! She also seems to have found her voice, especially when her sister is giving her a hard time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Broadway and a birthday</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/09/broadway-and-a-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/09/broadway-and-a-birthday/</guid>
      <description>This past weekend was a full, but very enjoyable one.
On Friday night, our friend Rick babysat the kids while we went to see Billy Elliot on Broadway. We enjoyed our first Broadway experience. The “show” aspect at least — Ben will have more to say about the story later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A little summary</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/05/a-little-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/05/a-little-summary/</guid>
      <description>We’ve been in New York City for just a little over 5 months now. I can hardly believe it’s been that long, and on the other hand it feels much longer! I thought I’d use this post to update you in a bit more detail about how we’re doing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doing homework</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/04/doing-homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/04/doing-homework/</guid>
      <description>Marica reckons that one of the best things about preschool is that she gets to do homework!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not so many smiles at the moment</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/29/not-so-many-smiles-at-the-moment/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/29/not-so-many-smiles-at-the-moment/</guid>
      <description>As some of you know, Esther has been sick for over 5 weeks now, plagued by colds, teething and then this week some virus that has been giving her pretty high fevers. We’re pretty sure that it’s Roseola because as soon as she got a rash late yesterday afternoon her fever broke.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does it get any cuter than this?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/28/cuter-than-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/28/cuter-than-this/</guid>
      <description>A face full of dinner and eager to get in the water!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Esther’s new favourite toy</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/22/esthers-new-favourite-toy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/22/esthers-new-favourite-toy/</guid>
      <description>Esther loves water. She has also recently started pulling herself up on things. I guess it is to be expected that she would have found the toilet very entertaining!
Esther and the toilet seem to have a magnetic attraction to each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugs</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/19/hugs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/19/hugs/</guid>
      <description>Marica giving Esther a cuddle at uncle Sherwood and aunt Sharon Hoyt’s place in Pennsylvania. Marica loves cuddling Esther, but Esther isn’t always so sure about it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happiness in a box</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/15/happiness-in-a-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/15/happiness-in-a-box/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday afternoon was pretty grey, but then the rainy gloom was seriously cheered up by a special package from Oupa and Ouma Voges. It was filled with special goodies for all of us. Just check this out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cereal box fun</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/13/cereal-box-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/13/cereal-box-fun/</guid>
      <description>Last week we were all a bit under the weather, but of course when kids are sick they are still full of ideas and energy. So one morning after finishing off a box of cereal, I remembered doing crafts with cereal boxes as a kid and looked online for something to do with the cereal box.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calculus for three-year-olds</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/12/calculus-for-three-year-olds/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/12/calculus-for-three-year-olds/</guid>
      <description>The other day Franci and I were talking about subjects we studied in high school, and Marica asked what “calculus” was. Franci said it was a type of maths (Marica’s been learning her written numbers). Marica of course replied that “she could do that”, but Franci said she was probably a bit young for calculus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Esther’s new shoes</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/04/esthers-new-shoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/04/esthers-new-shoes/</guid>
      <description>Esther recently got her first pair of shoes. She’s been a barefoot baby for all the 10 months of her life (not counting socks, of course!) and is taking a little while getting used to them!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sisterly love</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/27/sisterly-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/27/sisterly-love/</guid>
      <description>I love moments like this!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lady Liberty</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/20/lady-liberty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/20/lady-liberty/</guid>
      <description>The other night I was busy in the kitchen setting the table and suddenly wondered why Marica was so quiet. I looked up and saw this.
Totally unprompted, and she got the pose and everything right!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marica’s sayings on Twitter</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/10/maricas-sayings-on-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/10/maricas-sayings-on-twitter/</guid>
      <description>I don’t understand the appeal of Twitter. Just as you’re three quarters of the way through your controversial opening statement, you have t…
But anyway, Franci and I did find a good use for it. You know all those weird and wonderful things three-year-olds say but you always forget to write down?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Day</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/07/first-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/07/first-day/</guid>
      <description>Today is a pretty big day here in the Hoyt household. It’s Marica’s first day at an American preschool!
She was really excited and keen, all smiles walking there and meeting the teachers and putting her bag away and finding her name on the table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tasty Recipe and more</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/01/tasty-recipe-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/01/tasty-recipe-and-more/</guid>
      <description>Last night we had some company (a work colleague of Ben’s) and I made a new recipe. I have a very bad habit of trying new recipes when we have people over, but this time it was definitely a winner!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saturday at Coney Island</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/30/saturday-at-coney-island/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/30/saturday-at-coney-island/</guid>
      <description>On Saturday we went to Coney Island for the day. We tried to pack in as much as possible and first went to the Aquarium, then for a swim at the beach and then off to the best part: some rides at the amusement parks!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rainy day fun</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/27/rainy-day-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/27/rainy-day-fun/</guid>
      <description>When I realised that we have rain forecast for most of this past week, I wondered how on earth I was going to entertain two busy little people indoors? But then I just googled ‘rainy day activities with preschoolers’ and it comes up with a list of stuff to do that will keep you occupied almost all winter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I love my kids</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/18/i-love-my-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/18/i-love-my-kids/</guid>
      <description>I love my kids. They certainly are hard work, and their sinful natures are so raw and need so much refining and shaping and I sometimes feel so hopelessly unqualified to be their mother, but then Marica would run up to me and say “I love you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to the New York Aquarium</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/13/visit-to-the-new-york-aquarium/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/13/visit-to-the-new-york-aquarium/</guid>
      <description>We visited the New York Aquarium in Coney Island recently. From where we were at our old place in Brooklyn, it’s about an hour on the subway to get there.
There’s a great board walk with lots of shops selling food and trinkets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend trip to New Jersey</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/24/weekend-trip-to-new-jersey/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/24/weekend-trip-to-new-jersey/</guid>
      <description>I promised that I’d share about our time with the Stoltes in New Jersey this past weekend. I can’t believe it’s already Wednesday — and I’m only getting around to this now.
Public transport around here is really good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dear Roseola, thanks for not being Chickenpox (or worse, Measles)</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/19/dear-roseola-thanks-for-not-being-chickenpox-or-worse-measles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/19/dear-roseola-thanks-for-not-being-chickenpox-or-worse-measles/</guid>
      <description>This week has been a bit trying as Marica has been quite unwell. Monday and Tuesday she had a high fever and was listless and irritable. The listlessness and irritability has continued all week and on Thursday she broke out with a rash which we initially thought was a very bad case of chickenpox.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kids!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/16/kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/16/kids/</guid>
      <description>This post is about the cool new things our kids can do. :-)
Marica has learned to recognise the numbers 1-6 and is quickly learning 7-10 as well. I think this has a lot to do with the fact that we let her push the buttons in the elevator.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
