<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Apartment living on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/category/apartment-living/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Apartment living on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/category/apartment-living/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Settling in. Or at least trying to</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/04/24/settling-in-or-at-least-trying-to/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/04/24/settling-in-or-at-least-trying-to/</guid>
      <description>Our container with all our stuff arrived last Wednesday from New Zealand. It’s great to have our things again, but also very odd. It all seems so out of place. The furniture looks about as comfortable in our apartment as a fat girl in a skinny girl’s clothes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We’ve moved in!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/04/05/weve-moved-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/04/05/weve-moved-in/</guid>
      <description>Just a quick note to let you all know that we’ve moved into our new apartment where we hope to be for the next year (or more) in Jersey City Heights. We moved in on Monday and it’s been a bit of a shambles around here that is slowly turning into order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life in limbo</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/03/10/life-in-limbo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/03/10/life-in-limbo/</guid>
      <description>Since the last time I posted, we’ve moved into our temporary apartment for the month of March, settled into a daily routine with homeschooling in the mornings, and all of us have gotten sick. New climate, new bugs — it was to be expected!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Packing up, cleaning out, giving away, selling…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/24/packing-up-cleaning-out-giving-away-selling/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/24/packing-up-cleaning-out-giving-away-selling/</guid>
      <description>That’s what I’m doing a lot of at the moment. And I’m seriously worried about this 4 suitcase limit. I’m just praying that our rental car can fit more than that because just our family’s clothing takes up 3 suitcases!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting excited about Christmas</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/12/getting-excited-about-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/12/12/getting-excited-about-christmas/</guid>
      <description>I love the month of December here in New York — I think it’s even my favourite time of the year, even better than beautiful spring-time April. It’s cold, but everyone seems to be in good spirits (as opposed to grumpy January!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving yumminess</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/28/thanksgiving-yumminess/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/28/thanksgiving-yumminess/</guid>
      <description>Well, Thanksgiving came and went, and we had a lovely day. It was great to have a bonus day where Ben had the day off, and we enjoyed getting to know a friend from church a bit better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another beautiful zinnia</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/25/another-beautiful-zinnia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/25/another-beautiful-zinnia/</guid>
      <description>It boggles my mind that God would put such intricate beauty into a simple flower… layer upon layer, curly baby petals… in a pot I too often forget to water.
But then again, it really shouldn’t surprise me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A garden grows in Brooklyn</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/06/a-garden-grows-in-brooklyn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/06/a-garden-grows-in-brooklyn/</guid>
      <description>We are among the few privileged New Yorkers who have our own private backyard. Private as in access (no one else uses our backyard), not private in the sense that nobody can see us, because we certainly have plenty of window eyes all around!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Long-distance running inside our apartment</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/16/long-distance-running-inside-our-apartment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/16/long-distance-running-inside-our-apartment/</guid>
      <description>The other day Marica decided to start running laps between our bed and the couch in the lounge, a distance of about six or seven metres. After a few laps she started counting, “1, 2, 3, 4 …” Soon I took over the counting, “14, 15, 16, see if you can get up to 20 …”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musings on New York, the weather, and teeth.</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/26/musings-on-new-york-the-weather-and-teeth/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/26/musings-on-new-york-the-weather-and-teeth/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been sharing a lot of photos and telling you about stuff we’ve seen and experienced lately (and there’s a lot more to come!), but I thought I’d just give you a little update on how we’re all doing, as well as some related thoughts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The beauty of bread</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/21/the-beauty-of-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/21/the-beauty-of-bread/</guid>
      <description>Here in the States, I’ve taken to baking most of our bread from scratch by hand, because I can’t stand the taste of the bread here. Specialty breads here taste great, but I do still have a grocery budget to stick to!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting creative with snow</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/02/getting-creative-with-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/02/getting-creative-with-snow/</guid>
      <description>We’ve had a lot of snow here this winter, and today we’ve got snow and ice rain again! Well, life carries on about as normally as it can and we try to get out when we can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/22/thanksgiving/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/22/thanksgiving/</guid>
      <description>This week on Thursday it is Thanksgiving. I think it must be my favourite American holiday! A life that is full of thanksgiving is a happy one, no matter what the circumstances, and what can be better than once a year celebrating the good things God has given us with a great big feast?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keep sweeping</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/19/keep-sweeping/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/19/keep-sweeping/</guid>
      <description>My kitchen/dining room floor gets swept at least once a day. Usually more, but at least once. I never cease to be amazed at how much junk can land on the floor in just a day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Through Marica’s eyes</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/17/through-maricas-eyes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/17/through-maricas-eyes/</guid>
      <description>Marica absolutely loves being allowed to use the camera to take photos. And I always have a chuckle when I download them and see just what caught her eye. Let’s just say that she has a realistic view and she takes pictures of it — she won’t avoid the messy room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enjoying Fall</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/15/enjoying-fall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/15/enjoying-fall/</guid>
      <description>Two weekends ago we visited friends from church for lunch who recently got married, Franco and Neli. Franco grew up in NYC and Neli is from Peru. They’re a really lovely couple!
Franco and Neli live in a tall apartment building a block away from Central Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A little summary</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/05/a-little-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/05/a-little-summary/</guid>
      <description>We’ve been in New York City for just a little over 5 months now. I can hardly believe it’s been that long, and on the other hand it feels much longer! I thought I’d use this post to update you in a bit more detail about how we’re doing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This is the way we wash our clothes…</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/26/this-is-the-way-we-wash-our-clothes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/26/this-is-the-way-we-wash-our-clothes/</guid>
      <description>wash our clothes, wash our clothes. This is the way we wash our clothes, living in New York City!
At our apartment, we don’t have facilities to do washing other than by hand. In fact, our rental contract specifies that we are not allowed to have a washing machine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tornado in Brooklyn</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/18/tornado-in-brooklyn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/18/tornado-in-brooklyn/</guid>
      <description>While Christchurch is still having earthquakes, here in Brooklyn we had our very own tornado (or super-severe storm — the weather service isn’t sure which). The winds and rain whipped up all of a sudden, picked up huge branches and even trees and threw them across the streets, and then twenty minutes later it was dead calm again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two nights &#43; 14 people &#43; 1 (small) New York apartment = Lots of fun!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/14/two-nights/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/14/two-nights/</guid>
      <description>It’s really hard to believe that it’s almost been two weeks since the van Wichens descended on our place. For those who don’t know, Laurel is Ben’s oldest sister and their family is touring the States for 10 weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tasty Recipe and more</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/01/tasty-recipe-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/01/tasty-recipe-and-more/</guid>
      <description>Last night we had some company (a work colleague of Ben’s) and I made a new recipe. I have a very bad habit of trying new recipes when we have people over, but this time it was definitely a winner!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our new place (with photo tour)</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/10/our-new-place/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/10/our-new-place/</guid>
      <description>On Thursday the first of July we moved into our new rental place. Now, 10 days later we are starting to feel a bit more settled. Thursday was a very busy day. But perhaps I should tell you about Wednesday first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Saga of the Air Conditioning</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/08/the-saga-of-the-air-conditioning/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/08/the-saga-of-the-air-conditioning/</guid>
      <description>I was going to do a post with pictures about our new place, but alas, I haven’t gotten around to taking pictures, so I’ll try to do that in the next day or two.
So we moved into our new place last Thursday, and let me tell you, it has been a full week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We have an apartment!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/28/we-have-an-apartment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/28/we-have-an-apartment/</guid>
      <description>Yes, yesterday we signed the contract to rent a “Garden Apartment”. It’s the bottom floor in the brown building on the right in this photo (thanks to Google Maps), under the stairs where the little “A” is:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Showing you around (a photo post)</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/07/showing-you-around/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/07/showing-you-around/</guid>
      <description>First off, if you have dail-up, I apologise. This post is going to be laden with photos!
The other day, Ben caught Marica on camera looking out the window of our 5th floor apartment:
The nice building across the road is the HSBC bank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apartment hunting</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/05/apartment-hunting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/05/apartment-hunting/</guid>
      <description>There is not a whole lot to tell you about yet, but finding an apartment in NYC is hard work. Especially without the ease of a car! On Wednesday I packed up the kids and we set of to look at some apartments in Prospect Heights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The city that never sleeps</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/05/31/the-city-that-never-sleeps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/05/31/the-city-that-never-sleeps/</guid>
      <description>I can’t believe we’ve only been in NYC for 4 nights — it feels much longer. I’m sure that this is because we haven’t exactly slept very well. Jet lag aside, we’ve had some interesting night-time sound experiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye Christchurch, Hello New York</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/05/28/goodbye-christchurch-hello-new-york/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/05/28/goodbye-christchurch-hello-new-york/</guid>
      <description>It’s been a hectic last few days! The days leading up to our departure were filled with last-minute packing and cleaning (thanks to everyone who helped!) and lots of goodbyes. I hate goodbyes, but as far as they go, the ones we had were good byes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
