<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Easter on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/category/easter/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Easter on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/category/easter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A little time travel into the past: April</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/09/24/a-little-time-travel-into-the-past-april/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/09/24/a-little-time-travel-into-the-past-april/</guid>
      <description>In April, we had a wonderful visit from my parents. It was great to spend time together again — especially for the grandkids to have their grandparents around! Spring really was a great time for a visit — not too hot and not too cold, and it’s so beautiful with all the blossoms and flowers out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easter 2016</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/05/06/easter-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/05/06/easter-2016/</guid>
      <description>This year’s Easter was a busy but lovely one. We kept up the tradition of making hot cross buns and egg dying, which the kids always love,
&amp;nbsp;
and on Easter Sunday we hosted a large crowd of church folk for a yummy dinner, followed by some rousing hymn singing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enjoying a spot of sewing</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/04/17/enjoying-a-spot-of-sewing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2015/04/17/enjoying-a-spot-of-sewing/</guid>
      <description>The week before Easter I decided that I’d love for the girls to have new dresses for Easter (which is a bit of an American church tradition, it seems to me), but I really didn’t want to fork out $30 a dress (times three!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easter</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/29/easter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/29/easter/</guid>
      <description>Easter this year was probably the most different for us as a family than what we’ve had before. Ben didn’t get Good Friday off, so it was really strange not to be able to go to church together as a family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating Easter</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/18/celebrating-easter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/18/celebrating-easter/</guid>
      <description>Let me just start by saying that I loooove living in the northern hemisphere! The seasons and church calendar finally make sense! Christmas with snow, Easter with blossoms, summer holiday that doesn’t mix with Christmas. Celebrating Christmas here was great in that sense, and Easter is looking promising too.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
