<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Meditations on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/category/meditations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Meditations on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/category/meditations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Living with a veneer of glamour</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/04/07/living-with-a-veneer-of-glamour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/04/07/living-with-a-veneer-of-glamour/</guid>
      <description>The chandeliers in the apartment we stayed at for the first month reminded me (by way of trying to appear more beautiful than they actually are) of a piece I wrote a while back that I’ve meant to put up here on the blog and never got around to doing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 3-step guide for mothers who want to Do It All</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/10/the-3-step-guide-for-mothers-who-want-to-do-it-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2012/05/10/the-3-step-guide-for-mothers-who-want-to-do-it-all/</guid>
      <description>Yes, you too can Do It All! Small children? A big workload? Stack of dishes in the sink? Pile of bills to pay? No problem! Just follow my easy 3-step program and soon you too could be one of those special people who can Do It All!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Night</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/24/night/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/24/night/</guid>
      <description>“Why are you downcast, O my soul? Why so disturbed within me?” Ps 43:5
That’s what this sculpture by Aristide Maillol brought to mind when I saw it at the Metropolitan Museum of Art.
The artist did an amazing job — it was as if everything about her just felt so sad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The night I met Daniel</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/10/the-night-i-met-daniel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/10/10/the-night-i-met-daniel/</guid>
      <description>I don’t usually share particularly personal experiences here on the blog, but this is a bit of an exception as I thought some of you might find it strangely encouraging too.
In the last few weeks, I have had a profound sense of the weight and enormity of my sin and selfishness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ten years on</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/11/ten-years-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/09/11/ten-years-on/</guid>
      <description>This week, and especially today, New Yorkers remember the day on which Muslim terrorists hijacked planes and flew into the World Trade Center towers, killing almost 3000 civilians. I’m not going to delve into the politics and debates surrounding it, but rather give you my perspective on what it’s like living here at a time like this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another beautiful zinnia</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/25/another-beautiful-zinnia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/25/another-beautiful-zinnia/</guid>
      <description>It boggles my mind that God would put such intricate beauty into a simple flower… layer upon layer, curly baby petals… in a pot I too often forget to water.
But then again, it really shouldn’t surprise me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Childlike trust</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/13/childlike-trust/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/07/13/childlike-trust/</guid>
      <description>Trust is knowing that we are small and God is big and that He will not let us go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful encouragement for the mothers among us</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/29/beautiful-encouragement-for-the-mothers-among-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/06/29/beautiful-encouragement-for-the-mothers-among-us/</guid>
      <description>One of my favourite authors and bloggers (I’ve raved about her before) was invited by Desiring God ministries to write an article for them. I found it very encouraging and helpful, and I hope all the mothers who visit this blog will read this article — you will not be sorry!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who sped up time?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/28/who-sped-up-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/28/who-sped-up-time/</guid>
      <description>How is it possible that we have been in New York City for a year already? Yes, everyone, it’s been a YEAR! When we arrived a year ago, I must admit that I viewed our ‘adventure’ with some trepidation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About servants and serving</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/07/about-servants/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/05/07/about-servants/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been thinking about my job (as a mother) a fair bit recently. After Monday’s blog post, I felt that I might have given the wrong impression of what life around here looks like. I have a policy (with myself) not to complain or whine on this blog — not about big city life and not about my family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musings on New York, the weather, and teeth.</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/26/musings-on-new-york-the-weather-and-teeth/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/04/26/musings-on-new-york-the-weather-and-teeth/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been sharing a lot of photos and telling you about stuff we’ve seen and experienced lately (and there’s a lot more to come!), but I thought I’d just give you a little update on how we’re all doing, as well as some related thoughts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Barbie is a big deal</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/24/why-barbie-is-a-big-deal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/03/24/why-barbie-is-a-big-deal/</guid>
      <description>Today’s post goes out on a limb a bit. It’s probably going to be controversial and many of you won’t agree with me, but these are some thoughts that have been swirling around in my mind for many months, and that some of you might find beneficial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just do the next thing</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/24/just-do-the-next-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/24/just-do-the-next-thing/</guid>
      <description>There are times in life when we get overwhelmed. Sometimes we have too much work to do, sometimes we’re ill, sometimes we’re just dog tired, sometimes earthquakes strike. The world keeps spinning, life carries on and we have to somehow deal with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The beauty of bread</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/21/the-beauty-of-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/21/the-beauty-of-bread/</guid>
      <description>Here in the States, I’ve taken to baking most of our bread from scratch by hand, because I can’t stand the taste of the bread here. Specialty breads here taste great, but I do still have a grocery budget to stick to!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The One True BDFL</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/14/the-one-true-bdfl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/14/the-one-true-bdfl/</guid>
      <description>Note: This blog is mostly read by family and friends, but I wrote this more for my fellow programmers. Knowing me, it’ll be taken the wrong way by both groups of people. :-) By the way, see the first comment for a book give-away!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A joyful glimpse</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/11/a-joyful-glimpse/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/02/11/a-joyful-glimpse/</guid>
      <description>I just wanted to share a little moment in our life here, because it’s moments like these that make me so happy and thankful for the gift of being able to be a mother at home with my kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Clutter</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/17/time-clutter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/17/time-clutter/</guid>
      <description>I often feel slightly frustrated at the seeming lack of time I have for doing things like reading, crafting or doing special fun things with the kids. Part of my lack of time is certainly due to the demands of daily life as a wife and a stay-at-home mother of two busy little people, but some of it is most certainly due to me wasting time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Six blessed and beautiful years</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/15/six-blessed-and-beautiful-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/01/15/six-blessed-and-beautiful-years/</guid>
      <description>Today, 6 years ago, I married my best friend.
Life with Ben has been like a beautiful dance, a dance he leads to help us move forward as one. There has been the odd difficult patch because we are living life in a fallen world, after all, but on the whole it has been six years that God has packed with blessing upon blessing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/24/merry-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/24/merry-christmas/</guid>
      <description>Today we celebrate the birth of The Biggest Present ever given. A Saviour to free us from sin, to take away the wrath we deserve and puts it on Himself, a death-conquering King who calls us His brothers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time is like mercury</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/11/time-is-like-mercury/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/11/time-is-like-mercury/</guid>
      <description>Time is like mercury. You can’t hold on to it and it keeps slipping away, especially at this time of the year. End of year functions, social events, Christmas shopping, Christmas baking, the usual daily tasks…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/22/thanksgiving/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/22/thanksgiving/</guid>
      <description>This week on Thursday it is Thanksgiving. I think it must be my favourite American holiday! A life that is full of thanksgiving is a happy one, no matter what the circumstances, and what can be better than once a year celebrating the good things God has given us with a great big feast?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keep sweeping</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/19/keep-sweeping/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/11/19/keep-sweeping/</guid>
      <description>My kitchen/dining room floor gets swept at least once a day. Usually more, but at least once. I never cease to be amazed at how much junk can land on the floor in just a day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stronger than Circumstances: Contentment and joy</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/14/stronger-than-circumstances/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/10/14/stronger-than-circumstances/</guid>
      <description>Just a little heads-up to our readers that this post is dealing with the topic of Christian contentment and is therefore explicitly religious. :-)
Today I’m delving into something totally different. This post won’t have many photos, and it won’t be about what we’ve been up to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Firefly</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/30/little-firefly/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/30/little-firefly/</guid>
      <description>A (cheesy) little poem I wrote one very hot night sitting outside in my Brooklyn backyard.
—————————————————————————————————————————————-
Little firefly,
What are you doing here?
Don’t you belong
in open fields
by sliding streams
under uninterrupted skies?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What we’re doing and reading</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/28/what-were-doing-and-reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/28/what-were-doing-and-reading/</guid>
      <description>Last night I had an audition for the Brooklyn Conservatory Chorale. I’ve been thinking for a while that I’d like to do some music again, but because we don’t have a piano and I decided not to bring my violin, it has to be singing which I thankfully enjoy doing very much!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is smoking a sin?</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/24/is-smoking-a-sin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/08/24/is-smoking-a-sin/</guid>
      <description>Quite probably for you, it is. :-)
I just read this short address by Doug Wilson to a bunch of Christian college students and found it a refreshing argument against smoking rather than the usual ‘it ruins your body’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dear Roseola, thanks for not being Chickenpox (or worse, Measles)</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/19/dear-roseola-thanks-for-not-being-chickenpox-or-worse-measles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/19/dear-roseola-thanks-for-not-being-chickenpox-or-worse-measles/</guid>
      <description>This week has been a bit trying as Marica has been quite unwell. Monday and Tuesday she had a high fever and was listless and irritable. The listlessness and irritability has continued all week and on Thursday she broke out with a rash which we initially thought was a very bad case of chickenpox.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Like a little child</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/10/like-a-little-child/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/06/10/like-a-little-child/</guid>
      <description>Last night as I was putting Esther to bed, Marica peeked into the door and said out of the blue and quite matter of factly with her little double-jointed forefinger pointing upwards that “Wanneer ek doodgaan, ek gaan hemel toe by Jesus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balm for anxious thoughts</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/05/28/balm-for-anxious-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/05/28/balm-for-anxious-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>This morning, as I sit here alone with an apartment full of beautiful sleeping people, my mind is full of anxious thoughts. Things like, where will we end up living? Will I even like it here?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
