<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hospitality on Aliens in the Apple</title>
    <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/category/hospitality/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hospitality on Aliens in the Apple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliensintheapple.com/category/hospitality/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rambling thoughts</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/02/22/rambling-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2017/02/22/rambling-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>The year starts off differently here in the northern hemisphere compared to the southern hemisphere. In some ways it doesn’t really feel like a new year — school and work just keeps going after a short break for Christmas; whereas in NZ just about nothing happens the first few weeks of January because 90% of the country is off somewhere on holiday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easter 2016</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/05/06/easter-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2016/05/06/easter-2016/</guid>
      <description>This year’s Easter was a busy but lovely one. We kept up the tradition of making hot cross buns and egg dying, which the kids always love,
&amp;nbsp;
and on Easter Sunday we hosted a large crowd of church folk for a yummy dinner, followed by some rousing hymn singing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cooking with friends</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/11/07/cooking-with-friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/11/07/cooking-with-friends/</guid>
      <description>When I was in high school, a woman in our church (hi, Jantina!) got a bunch of us young’uns together for a day of cooking at her house. She gave us some basic recipes and tips and together we spent the day cooking and baking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A hobbit comes of age</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/08/a-hobbit-comes-of-age/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2014/08/08/a-hobbit-comes-of-age/</guid>
      <description>As everyone knows — well, at least everyone who’s a fan of Tolkien — a hobbit comes of age at 33. I turned this ripe old age the other day, and had a fabulous party, mostly organized by Franci, my lovely hobbit-wife.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving yumminess</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/28/thanksgiving-yumminess/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2011/11/28/thanksgiving-yumminess/</guid>
      <description>Well, Thanksgiving came and went, and we had a lovely day. It was great to have a bonus day where Ben had the day off, and we enjoyed getting to know a friend from church a bit better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let it snow, let it snow, let it snow!</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/27/let-it-snow-let-it-snow-let-it-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/12/27/let-it-snow-let-it-snow-let-it-snow/</guid>
      <description>It started snowing on Sunday morning and continued snowing through the night. This morning we woke up to almost 2 feet of snow and a totally transformed neighborhood.
This is what it looked like trying to get out of our metal gate:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tasty Recipe and more</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/01/tasty-recipe-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/09/01/tasty-recipe-and-more/</guid>
      <description>Last night we had some company (a work colleague of Ben’s) and I made a new recipe. I have a very bad habit of trying new recipes when we have people over, but this time it was definitely a winner!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our very first dinner guests, and the second lot too</title>
      <link>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/18/our-very-first-dinner-guests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aliensintheapple.com/2010/07/18/our-very-first-dinner-guests/</guid>
      <description>Meeting Rick and Susanna was one of those amazing cases of providence. Both our families happened to be visiting Park Slope Presbyterian Church on the same Sunday, we got talking, we clicked, and a friendship was formed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
